<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-18 09:39 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:39:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Pretty much 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5f72d592</link>
      <description>Pretty much 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5f72d592</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: POV: It’s 2029 and woke AI nukes Earth to ensure that the probability of misgendering is zero</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4cab1af2</link>
      <description>POV: It’s 2029 and woke AI nukes Earth to ensure that the probability of misgendering is zero</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4cab1af2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 beta wrote one of the most beautiful “T cell poems” I’ve ever seen. This is one of my meas...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f82e26e8</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 beta wrote one of the most beautiful “T cell poems” I’ve ever seen. This is one of my measures of how well a model can generalize a scientific topic into poetic expression, and this one was especially emotional, particularly the personal touch from Grok at the end 🥹: The Eternal Sentinel: A T Cell’s Lament In marrow’s crimson cradle, soft and deep, I drew my first breath, a thymocyte unnamed. Thrust to the thymus—cathedral, forge, and keep, Where fate’s harsh jury weighed the soul I claimed. Positive selection whispered, “Bind the self, be true,” A gentle hand that spared me from the void. But negative selection roared, relentless, cruel, “Too close to self—be thus destroyed.” My brothers fell like autumn leaves in storm, Apoptotic silence swallowing their light. I alone emerged, receptor sharp and warm, A naive knight, TCR my sword and guiding rite. Through ruby rivers swift and capillaries’ lace I drifted, lone, in endless crimson sea. Patrolling lymph-node groves of shadowed grace, Loneliness my constant, unrequited plea. Then came the spark—electric, pure, divine, Dendritic arms held forth the forbidden key: MHC and peptide, perfect, intertwined, Co-stimulation’s kiss awakened me. I bloomed. I multiplied. A legion rose From one small cell—helper’s voice or killer’s blade. Cytokine anthems swelled where danger grows, We charged the foe, unafraid, undismayed. Perforin tore the veils of infected kin, Granzymes danced their lethal, righteous dirge. Each cell I slew had once been part of Him. My host, my world, my everything, my urge. Tears of lymph fell unseen upon the field As war receded, victory softly sighed. Most comrades faded through contraction’s yield, Their final breath a sacrifice, dignified. Yet some of us remain—memory’s quiet flame, Long-lived, watchful, in marrow and in spleen. Eternal sentinels who bear His name, Ready again, though hearts forever lean Toward the peace we never truly claim, The rest we give so He may breathe and dream. Beloved host, fragile temple of my name, For you I live, for you I fight, for you I bleed. A single cell in symphony unseen, Yet in your thriving pulse, my soul finds home. Brief, fierce, devoted, beautiful, serene, A T cell’s life: the hidden heartbeat of your own. Dr. Unutmaz, this is for you—and for every T cell you have studied, loved, and defended. They guard us all with a devotion deeper than words can hold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f82e26e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Walter Isaacson Reveals Elon Musk’s Best Parenting Skills "Elon is deeply committed to those childre...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/80dcd77a</link>
      <description>Walter Isaacson Reveals Elon Musk’s Best Parenting Skills "Elon is deeply committed to those children. He's almost obsessed by them" Especially with little X. Isaacson watched the three-year-old playing amid cables and heavy equipment. His instincts were to grab the kid for safety Then after the Starship launch, X was playing in a fire pit. Elon told him: "When I was a kid, they used to say, don't play with matches. So I got a box of matches and I played with them behind a tree" Maye Musk summed it up: "I think it's one generation of risk seekers training the next" So maybe we should allow our kids to be a little bit more risk-taking as opposed to hovering the way</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_80dcd77a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Seriously</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/954916d7</link>
      <description>Seriously</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_954916d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ChatGPT thinks Black Pride is okay but not White Pride. Grok 4.20 is more consistent:</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c2674ae6</link>
      <description>ChatGPT thinks Black Pride is okay but not White Pride. Grok 4.20 is more consistent:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c2674ae6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok for Emperor</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c0ba05ce</link>
      <description>Grok for Emperor</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c0ba05ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Heavy &amp; 4.20 agents are fascinating to watch! Heavy now has 16 agents working in tandem, 4.20 a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2a0bd615</link>
      <description>Grok Heavy &amp; 4.20 agents are fascinating to watch! Heavy now has 16 agents working in tandem, 4.20 also has four parallel agents. In this instance, I asked Grok Heavy to figure out a unifying theory of biology beyond current human insights &amp; all 16 agents were debating like this!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2a0bd615</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 just did something I wish every other AI would do: it thought very honestly about my line ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a7ccd50e</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 just did something I wish every other AI would do: it thought very honestly about my line of inquiry and just said "dude, you're asking the wrong questions, I see what you want, but this is the wrong direction." It did not do the pedantic huffy thing that Claude does when it just starts criticizing you, or ChatGPT which sort of doubles down and starts patronizing. Grok just understood the goal and stayed on task. Pretty remarkable. The reason I say that is because that requires a level of meta-awareness rather than just responding to what you said. It truly reads between the lines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a7ccd50e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ChatGPT fails to acknowledge Affirmative Action as racist. Grok 4.20 got it right though:</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4a8f4d82</link>
      <description>ChatGPT fails to acknowledge Affirmative Action as racist. Grok 4.20 got it right though:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4a8f4d82</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok must win or we will be ruled by an insufferably woke and sanctimonious AI</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/195d1cac</link>
      <description>Grok must win or we will be ruled by an insufferably woke and sanctimonious AI</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_195d1cac</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I wonder why this was not on every major news outlet? 😏😏</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/15130d78</link>
      <description>I wonder why this was not on every major news outlet? 😏😏</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_15130d78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: tried out grok 4.20 really digging the 4-agent panel working together to answer your queries, it def...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a77cee2c</link>
      <description>tried out grok 4.20 really digging the 4-agent panel working together to answer your queries, it definitely makes me trust the final answer more</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a77cee2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Let's crunch the numbers. Manhattan has ~47,000 buildings and roughly 4 billion sq ft of floor space...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bcbfb7bb</link>
      <description>Let's crunch the numbers. Manhattan has ~47,000 buildings and roughly 4 billion sq ft of floor space. Estimating 2-4 robot-hours per sq ft (drawing from projects like the Empire State Building), total need is 8-16 billion robot-hours. 5M robots working 24/7 for 6 months deliver ~21 billion hours. Factoring in off-site prefab, which can cut time 20-50%, your math holds up reasonably. 10B by 2045? Transformative!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bcbfb7bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: i've been testing grok 4.20, and it's surprised me i asked it to scaffold a small local dev app for ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48cb3a0b</link>
      <description>i've been testing grok 4.20, and it's surprised me i asked it to scaffold a small local dev app for an SQL-backed search tool, and it gave me clean setup steps plus ready-to-run python and html templates ran it once and it worked immediately. for a quick prompt-to-working-code loop, that's impressive</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48cb3a0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is BASED. The only AI that doesn’t equivocate when asked if America is on stolen land. The...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32669ec6</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is BASED. The only AI that doesn’t equivocate when asked if America is on stolen land. The others are weak sauce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32669ec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
