<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-18 07:33 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:33:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The biggest mistake the Trump admin is making right now is taking half measures. If Democrats get in...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/02c79c28</link>
      <description>The biggest mistake the Trump admin is making right now is taking half measures. If Democrats get into power again they will arrest and jail huge numbers of Republican politicians, media figures, voters etc. Half measures get you killed. Jennifer Welch and Jim Acosta should be arrested. The corrupt criminal Democrat party leaders need to be arrested and jailed. If you don't strike first and strike hard, you will lose the only opportunity you have to save yourself and save your voters from the inevitable communist purge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_02c79c28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/204a4ec4</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_204a4ec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Soda Pop dance in@GrokImagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d97343f9</link>
      <description>Try Soda Pop dance in@GrokImagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d97343f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: America will die without secure elections</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/19c73861</link>
      <description>America will die without secure elections</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_19c73861</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Accurate</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fe7eec01</link>
      <description>Accurate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fe7eec01</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: His skepticism is warranted. This is a hard AI problem, but, as your drive with him showed, this is ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0a77189b</link>
      <description>His skepticism is warranted. This is a hard AI problem, but, as your drive with him showed, this is largely also a solved problem. What remains is the long tail march of 9’s. Getting to 99.9999% reliability and beyond. Understand the vast number of nuances of reality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0a77189b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OH MY GOSH! I went on live television with@kayleighmcenanyon Fox News to deliver a message: Senate M...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/796d8c97</link>
      <description>OH MY GOSH! I went on live television with@kayleighmcenanyon Fox News to deliver a message: Senate Majority Leader Thune, it’s time to nuke the filibuster &amp; pass the SAVE Act. The American people demand election reform — now! Peacefully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_796d8c97</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok should have a moral constitution</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b3d7b362</link>
      <description>Grok should have a moral constitution</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b3d7b362</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I get tired of repeating. Civilization is built by fathers for their daughters.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ebe543a</link>
      <description>I get tired of repeating. Civilization is built by fathers for their daughters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ebe543a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇰🇷 SOUTH KOREAN SHIPPING GIANT SWITCHES ENTIRE FLEET TO STARLINK Korea Line Corp, the shipping branc...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1112175b</link>
      <description>🇰🇷 SOUTH KOREAN SHIPPING GIANT SWITCHES ENTIRE FLEET TO STARLINK Korea Line Corp, the shipping branch of SM Group, wrapped up installing Starlink on every single one of their 38 ships, bulk carriers, and LNG tankers alike. They're the first in South Korea's shipping scene to fully switch over. Now they've got lightning-fast data transfers, smoother ship-to-office comms, smarter operations, better navigation safety, and way happier crews on those epic voyages. Source:@serobinsonjr</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1112175b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink is quickly emerging as the go to inflight connectivity solution for airlines globally. Unit...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/edf8f0ea</link>
      <description>Starlink is quickly emerging as the go to inflight connectivity solution for airlines globally. United Airlines Emirates Air France British Airways Qatar Airways Korean Air Asiana Airlines Alaska Airlines Virgin Atlantic WestJet SAS Scandinavian Airlines Iberia Aer Lingus Vueling LEVEL flydubai airBaltic Jin Air ZIPAIR Tokyo Air Busan Air Seoul JSX Hawaiian Airlines Air Canada Any airline not using Starlink is falling behind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_edf8f0ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The left is openly and loudly laser focused on regaining power to imprison Republicans en masse whil...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8ee33ebb</link>
      <description>The left is openly and loudly laser focused on regaining power to imprison Republicans en masse while the Indiana republican majority thought it would be too disrespectful to redistrict the state to gain votes The right is cooked</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8ee33ebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That is what they will do</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ab1899ad</link>
      <description>That is what they will do</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ab1899ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Major scandal in the Netherlands after it’s revealed that 125 students were made to live with 125 as...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3b7b467d</link>
      <description>Major scandal in the Netherlands after it’s revealed that 125 students were made to live with 125 asylum seekers in an experiment to “foster integration” and that it ended in students falling victim to gang rape, several sexual assaults and knife crime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3b7b467d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Because the entire mainstream media frantically tells them this.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5713df70</link>
      <description>Because the entire mainstream media frantically tells them this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5713df70</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a31b6a70</link>
      <description>The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a31b6a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
