<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-26 05:54 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:54:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is Katie Abraham She was k*lled by an illegal immigrant when he crashed into her drunk driving ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ca9b1285</link>
      <description>This is Katie Abraham She was k*lled by an illegal immigrant when he crashed into her drunk driving in Illinois She was only 20. Her life mattered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ca9b1285</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine 🌐</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/38692b71</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine 🌐</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_38692b71</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Empathy is good Empathy that allows for massive destruction is suicidal empathy We must be able to k...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b68bb4b</link>
      <description>Empathy is good Empathy that allows for massive destruction is suicidal empathy We must be able to know and articulate the difference.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b68bb4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: MrBeast talks about his admiration and appreciation for what Elon Musk is doing and aims to accompli...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e14bf148</link>
      <description>MrBeast talks about his admiration and appreciation for what Elon Musk is doing and aims to accomplish with SpaceX. “Name one thing that's more badass than that, that someone on Earth is currently doing. He’s literally going to create a colony on another planet.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e14bf148</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Falcon 9 launches 25@Starlinksatellites from California</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ad7459f2</link>
      <description>Falcon 9 launches 25@Starlinksatellites from California</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ad7459f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 This woman nails it while Legacy media ignores it. “Did you guys hear about the illegal immigrant ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5835fcee</link>
      <description>🚨 This woman nails it while Legacy media ignores it. “Did you guys hear about the illegal immigrant that was arrested in Georgia yesterday for brutally raping an 11-year-old girl at knifepoint and forcing her ten year old little sister to watch after breaking into their bedroom? Hmm, probably not, because you dumbasses have been so stuck on the five year old that was supposedly detained by ICE that with a 30 second Google search, you would have figured out that his dad actually ran and abandoned him and ICE wasn't going to leave a five-year-old by himself. You guys are so clinically stupid it hurts.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5835fcee</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink melts snow to work in the coldest weather</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2ed33954</link>
      <description>Starlink melts snow to work in the coldest weather</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2ed33954</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: As I like to say it’s the “human for scale” shot. It’s hard to convey how big Starship really is, bu...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4ccb29f4</link>
      <description>As I like to say it’s the “human for scale” shot. It’s hard to convey how big Starship really is, but this helps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4ccb29f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: MAKE LIFE MULTI-PLANETARY WITH THE KEY THRESHOLD TO SUSTAIN EVEN WITHOUT SUPPLY SHIPS FRO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7a60d748</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: MAKE LIFE MULTI-PLANETARY WITH THE KEY THRESHOLD TO SUSTAIN EVEN WITHOUT SUPPLY SHIPS FROM EARTH "The goal is to make life multi-planetary. The key threshold for that is if the supply ships from Earth stop coming for any reason, Mars does not die out That is the critical "Great Filter," if you talk about things in terms of the Fermi Paradox "The Great Filter is Mars being self-sustaining without any supply ships from Earth" Until we reach that point, we are really just a one-planet civilization with an extension. If Mars becomes self-sustaining, then even in a worst-case scenario of Earth’s civilization either dying with a bang or a whimper Mars would have a much better chance of surviving So, the intent here overall is to ensure that the light of consciousness, which appears to be just a tiny candle in a vast darkness"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7a60d748</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: WHY WE SHOULD GO TO MARS: ELON MUSK ON SECURING THE FUTURE OF CONSCIOUSNESS Going to Mars isn’t abou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6abb7a34</link>
      <description>WHY WE SHOULD GO TO MARS: ELON MUSK ON SECURING THE FUTURE OF CONSCIOUSNESS Going to Mars isn’t about escape—it’s about insurance. It’s about making sure the light of consciousness doesn’t go out if something catastrophic happens on Earth. Elon has consistently framed the Mars mission as the single most important step humanity can take to ensure long-term survival and expansion. “The key branching point for human destiny or destiny of consciousness as a whole is that Mars is self-sustaining, even if the resupply ships from Earth stop coming. You’re not multiplanetary until the planet can grow by itself. Because there’s always some risk of technology on Earth falling below a certain level or of a nuclear war or a meteor. You haven’t secured the future of civilization and consciousness until both planets can survive independently.” This is why Mars matters: • Backup for humanity — A second home protects against single-point failures (asteroids, supervolcanoes, pandemics, nuclear conflict, AI misalignment, etc.). • Self-sustaining civilization — Once Mars can grow its own population and industry without constant Earth resupply, consciousness becomes multiplanetary and far more resilient. • Inspiration &amp; progress driver — The challenge forces breakthroughs in energy, life support, materials, AI, and closed-loop systems that benefit Earth too. • Long-term species survival — Staying on one fragile planet forever is a gamble with extinction-level risks. Mars turns that into a hedge. Every Starship launch, every refueling test, every iteration brings us closer to that branching point. It’s not luxury—it’s the ultimate act of responsibility toward future generations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6abb7a34</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine understands beauty ✨</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bba23c84</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine understands beauty ✨</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bba23c84</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s so hard to get the moderation just right 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/036bea2d</link>
      <description>It’s so hard to get the moderation just right 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_036bea2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "We're all fucked!" Rioter signal chat was exposed for all their internal plans targetting ICE agent...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3c2621cb</link>
      <description>"We're all fucked!" Rioter signal chat was exposed for all their internal plans targetting ICE agents (names, threats, illegal acts). Now they panic, talk about fleeing the state, or country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3c2621cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine just nailed the entire spectrum of human emotion in photorealistic detail… This level o...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/74175c08</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine just nailed the entire spectrum of human emotion in photorealistic detail… This level of emotional clarity and realism is wild. The future of AI art is here. 🔥@grok@elonmusk@xai</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_74175c08</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If the Milky Way was the size of North America, the Sun would be:</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e6559f4e</link>
      <description>If the Milky Way was the size of North America, the Sun would be:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e6559f4e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starship is a modern-day Noah's Ark The ancient flood was water. The modern "flood" could be nuclear...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2ecc40cd</link>
      <description>Starship is a modern-day Noah's Ark The ancient flood was water. The modern "flood" could be nuclear, biological, or something we haven't even seen yet Starship is currently the only insurance policy we have to preserve human consciousness It’s not about abandoning Earth; it’s about ensuring survival</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2ecc40cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starship launch in 6 weeks</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/94745092</link>
      <description>Starship launch in 6 weeks</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_94745092</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Davos discussion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea7c03ad</link>
      <description>Davos discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea7c03ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
