<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-24 13:08 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We have a transracial violence epidemic</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b08de745</link>
      <description>We have a transracial violence epidemic</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b08de745</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Powerwall Storm Watch keeps the lights on for &gt;75k homes in the path of severe winter weather in the...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a9f81153</link>
      <description>Powerwall Storm Watch keeps the lights on for &gt;75k homes in the path of severe winter weather in the USxcancel.com/i/trending/20146170481…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a9f81153</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The@xAIteam is working on providing For You tabs that are specific to topics. For example, a “For Yo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/74a482a5</link>
      <description>The@xAIteam is working on providing For You tabs that are specific to topics. For example, a “For You AI” that is focused only on artificial intelligence with no political rage bait. This would be like automatically generated follow lists with content ranked by quality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_74a482a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is actually just a statistical artifact. Both conservative and liberal whites are almost exactl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f315e99e</link>
      <description>This is actually just a statistical artifact. Both conservative and liberal whites are almost exactly as racist as ALL other large groups - lib whites are just the only group to hate their OWN community. This balance creates a weird, artificial null result - zeroes out the data mean.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f315e99e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This sounds pretty coolxcancel.com/i/grok/share/7ad460f8b…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/05176f00</link>
      <description>This sounds pretty coolxcancel.com/i/grok/share/7ad460f8b…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_05176f00</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just. Grok. It.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32b18a68</link>
      <description>Just. Grok. It.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32b18a68</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Maine Wire used Grok to discover Government no-bid contracts They found over 5,000 documents and...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3f55babd</link>
      <description>The Maine Wire used Grok to discover Government no-bid contracts They found over 5,000 documents and the investigation led straight to NGO money laundering “All the Left Wing NGOs” “I used Grok to write a program that would guess at the URLs where those documents were and scraped from the government servers 5,000 documents all pointing towards no-bid contract spending. In those no-bid contract documents, we find no-bid contracts to Gateway, funded by federal COVID money that came in February of 2022. This money went to create what were called CHOWs, Community Health Outreach Workers. I'm willing to bet that this happened in a lot of states because it wasn't just the Somali groups, it was the Hispanic groups, the New Mainers Public Health Initiative. All of the left wing NGOs got CHOW money to create these community health outreach Workers”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3f55babd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We're not in Kansas anymore</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/248cef06</link>
      <description>We're not in Kansas anymore</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_248cef06</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “SpaceX exists to extend life and consciousness beyond Earth. As far as we know, life is extremely r...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/58a6ed11</link>
      <description>“SpaceX exists to extend life and consciousness beyond Earth. As far as we know, life is extremely rare—possibly only us. Consciousness is like a tiny candle in a vast darkness, easily extinguished. Making life multi-planetary ensures that if Earth faces a disaster, that light continues. That’s the purpose of SpaceX.” — Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_58a6ed11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ef9f7d6</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ef9f7d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Absolutely</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cd78bbc0</link>
      <description>Absolutely</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cd78bbc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The use of the phrase “asylum seeker” is absurd. There is zero persecution in Ecuador. This is an il...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9c124577</link>
      <description>The use of the phrase “asylum seeker” is absurd. There is zero persecution in Ecuador. This is an illegal alien who broke in Dec ‘24. Illegals get free lawyers. Their free lawyers universally file fake asylum claims. Those fake claims are rejected (at great expense to taxpayers).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9c124577</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Grok, the most unhinged AI that's actually fun to use and doesn't cut you off just because it's ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dd6fc92e</link>
      <description>Try Grok, the most unhinged AI that's actually fun to use and doesn't cut you off just because it's too sensitive to answer The only AI that's maximally truth-seeking, and it's super real-time The only AI that doesn't try to deny the reality because it's an uncomfortable truth A perfect AI assistant that you exclusively want</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dd6fc92e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Mars is critical to the long-term survival of consciousness." — Elon Mars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0326f352</link>
      <description>"Mars is critical to the long-term survival of consciousness." — Elon Mars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0326f352</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Rabbi explains why White men are always potrayed as the bad guys in movies: ”Because they are the on...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/43020080</link>
      <description>Rabbi explains why White men are always potrayed as the bad guys in movies: ”Because they are the only group that has no defence league, anyone else would be on us if we made them the bad guys" This unfair anti-White discrimination must end. Anti-White racism is also racism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_43020080</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We must get to Mars to ensure the long term consciousness of humanity. Made with Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/477bb361</link>
      <description>We must get to Mars to ensure the long term consciousness of humanity. Made with Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_477bb361</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Davos discussion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea7c03ad</link>
      <description>Davos discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea7c03ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
