<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-01 19:29 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:29:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s spreading.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/afba6aee</link>
      <description>It’s spreading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_afba6aee</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Welcome to Texas! No one will fight harder for the independent and free spirit of Texas than people ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a96e9761</link>
      <description>Welcome to Texas! No one will fight harder for the independent and free spirit of Texas than people who know it’s like when that’s taken away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a96e9761</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And this is how anyone of honor should be!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b9fb4da6</link>
      <description>And this is how anyone of honor should be!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b9fb4da6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I call him “Traitor Tim” for a reason. Tim Walz is a traitor to America.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f1c76c9e</link>
      <description>I call him “Traitor Tim” for a reason. Tim Walz is a traitor to America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f1c76c9e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the way</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d23c0dbd</link>
      <description>This is the way</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d23c0dbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Somalis are 0.37% of the Washington population on the high end. DCYF records reflect that roughly 10...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8524d3b4</link>
      <description>Somalis are 0.37% of the Washington population on the high end. DCYF records reflect that roughly 10% of daycare businesses list Somali as a primary language. I find that odd.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8524d3b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I paid so much in taxes one year that it broke the IRS computer (actually). Too many digits. They ha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0b2aca72</link>
      <description>I paid so much in taxes one year that it broke the IRS computer (actually). Too many digits. They had to update the software to get it processed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0b2aca72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It ends now</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9e07c11a</link>
      <description>It ends now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9e07c11a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Kind hot ngl</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/485e3bce</link>
      <description>Kind hot ngl</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_485e3bce</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2025 was sick! 2026 is about to be orders of magnitude “sicker”! S/O to the tremendous@xai@xAIMemphi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/99b57e4a</link>
      <description>2025 was sick! 2026 is about to be orders of magnitude “sicker”! S/O to the tremendous@xai@xAIMemphisteams along with our partners!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_99b57e4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Back in January, nobody had heard of Grok. We basically just had Grok 2 and an image gen model. To p...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ff0d4b4</link>
      <description>Back in January, nobody had heard of Grok. We basically just had Grok 2 and an image gen model. To put it bluntly, we were playing catchup. 1 year later, our team has built the world's largest GPU cluster, benchmark-topping reasoning models, Grok Voice, Grok Imagine, beautiful mobile apps, X/web apps, a robust API, and more. And we're only just getting started. Thank you all for being a part of our journey so far, and buckle up. 2026 is going to be a massive year for xAI 🚀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ff0d4b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "I will fight to my last drop of blood to ensure that 🇺🇸 remains the land of freedom and opportunity...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9010dcc0</link>
      <description>"I will fight to my last drop of blood to ensure that 🇺🇸 remains the land of freedom and opportunity” Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9010dcc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Happy New Year! 2026 will be a banger</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/77c921e9</link>
      <description>Happy New Year! 2026 will be a banger</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_77c921e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink is beginning a significant reconfiguration of its satellite constellation focused on increa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2b1b9775</link>
      <description>Starlink is beginning a significant reconfiguration of its satellite constellation focused on increasing space safety. We are lowering all@Starlinksatellites orbiting at ~550 km to ~480 km (~4400 satellites) over the course of 2026. The shell lowering is being tightly coordinated with other operators, regulators, and USSPACECOM. Lowering the satellites results in condensing Starlink orbits, and will increase space safety in several ways. As solar mininum approaches, atmospheric density decreases which means the ballistic decay time at any given altitude increases - lowering will mean a &gt;80% reduction in ballistic decay time in solar minimum, or 4+ years reduced to a few months. Correspondingly, the number of debris objects and planned satellite constellations is significantly lower below 500 km, reducing the aggregate likelihood of collision. Starlink satellites have extremely high reliability, with only 2 dead satellites in its fleet of over 9000 operational satellites. Nevertheless, if a satellite does fail on orbit, we want it to deorbit as quickly as possible. These actions will further improve the safety of the constellation, particularly with difficult to control risks such as uncoordinated maneuvers and launches by other satellite operators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2b1b9775</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: As a response to socialism, Miami will replace NYC as the finance capital and Austin will replace SF...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/425f3f28</link>
      <description>As a response to socialism, Miami will replace NYC as the finance capital and Austin will replace SF as the tech capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_425f3f28</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok just surpassed 80 million posts on 𝕏. More than 1 million new posts in just 24 hours....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ca1b12c0</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok just surpassed 80 million posts on 𝕏. More than 1 million new posts in just 24 hours. 🚀 80,000,000 - that number says everything about how widely people use it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ca1b12c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ilhan Omar wasn't some poor, oppressed refugee that Americ saved. Her family was part of the TYRANNI...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1c84d9d3</link>
      <description>Ilhan Omar wasn't some poor, oppressed refugee that Americ saved. Her family was part of the TYRANNICAL Somali government that was EJECTED from Somalia. Her family WERE the oppressors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1c84d9d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2026 will be a banger</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c31ec364</link>
      <description>2026 will be a banger</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c31ec364</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/723dfe9f</link>
      <description>xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try@Grok. Download latest app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_723dfe9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
