<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-16 16:58 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:58:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia traffic surges more than 10,000% since November, as Wikipedia's monopoly comes ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b7ad3233</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia traffic surges more than 10,000% since November, as Wikipedia's monopoly comes to an end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b7ad3233</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Diversity, equity, and inclusion are three wonderful sounding words that are, in fact, a scheme to ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4eb9e51b</link>
      <description>"Diversity, equity, and inclusion are three wonderful sounding words that are, in fact, a scheme to do the exact opposite"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4eb9e51b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨OpenAI is warning investors to expect “outlandish” claims from Elon Musk as the April trial approac...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d61f514a</link>
      <description>🚨OpenAI is warning investors to expect “outlandish” claims from Elon Musk as the April trial approaches. Translation: Scam Altman freaking out, he's nervous 😅 Elon’s lawsuit is exposing how a “nonprofit” became a $500B for-profit machine. Even the judge said the case is “extremely concerning” 👀 He’s shining light where others won’t 👊</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d61f514a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If not for 𝕏, you'd never see this story</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e66e6144</link>
      <description>If not for 𝕏, you'd never see this story</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e66e6144</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/324bd559</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_324bd559</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A Minnesota healthcare company has been receiving taxpayer money for 26 years but the company’s loca...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/385f8278</link>
      <description>A Minnesota healthcare company has been receiving taxpayer money for 26 years but the company’s location doesn’t even exist. It turns out Minnesota was turned into the Ukraine of America: A money laundering playground for corrupt elites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_385f8278</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: UK officials are threatening to ban X because this platform allows free speech. Governments should n...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5d6bd4fe</link>
      <description>UK officials are threatening to ban X because this platform allows free speech. Governments should not use legitimate concerns about child safety as a pretext to shut down or ban political debate in the modern town square. Documents obtained by the Committee show that UK authorities—like all governments—seek first and foremost to censor criticism of the government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5d6bd4fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That’s what’s happened</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/84c59777</link>
      <description>That’s what’s happened</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_84c59777</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEW: Minnesota day care worker confesses to intentionally suffocating an 11-month-old boy because sh...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a8173c2d</link>
      <description>NEW: Minnesota day care worker confesses to intentionally suffocating an 11-month-old boy because she wanted attention. 18-year-old Theah Loudemia Russell is in custody and will face a second-degree murder charge for the death of 11-month-old Harvey Muklebust. Savage Police say that back in September, they responded to a call to find an unresponsive 4-month-old. Three days later, they responded to another call and found Muklebust, who was not breathing. He was taken to the hospital, where he died. According to authorities, Russell had a history of "attention-seeking behavior," including "nonsensical" 911 calls, firestarting, and "erratic behavior toward other children." During an interview with police, Russell admitted to "intentionally suffocating" Muklebust and the other child "in an attention-seeking act." Horrific.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a8173c2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Undersecretary Sarah Rogers and I discuss this email from@Keir_Starmer's COS Morgan McSweeney to@brh...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4e44eb6f</link>
      <description>Undersecretary Sarah Rogers and I discuss this email from@Keir_Starmer's COS Morgan McSweeney to@brhodesdiscussing collaboration against "right wing culture wars." A senior Starmer staffer is cc'd on email. QUESTION: Are Brits interfering in US domestic politics?@ryangrim@TheCanaryUK@SamCoatesSky@jsolomonReports@benclerkin@afshinrattansi@JoshTBoswell@freddiesayers@joshrogin</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4e44eb6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: UK GOVERNMENT IS COMMITTING A HORRIFYING CRIME AGAINST HUMANITY Nearly 280k babies aborted in Englan...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/63993d1e</link>
      <description>UK GOVERNMENT IS COMMITTING A HORRIFYING CRIME AGAINST HUMANITY Nearly 280k babies aborted in England &amp; Wales in just one year in 2023 - the highest number ever recorded At the same time, the Labour Govt has voted to decriminalise self-induced abortions. A woman can now end a pregnancy after 24 weeks (even up to birth) without facing prosecution At the same time: • “Buffer zones” around abortion clinics make it illegal to silently pray or offer help within 150 metres • People have been arrested simply for praying quietly in their own heads • Pro-life counsellors offering alternatives are criminalised • Anyone trying to persuade a woman against abortion risks arrest The state is actively facilitating the destruction of life, while criminalising conscience, prayer, and peaceful persuasion Over a quarter of a million lives gone in one year. This is horrifying</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_63993d1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Major security breachxcancel.com/i/grok/share/64379ef4f…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8f93abef</link>
      <description>Major security breachxcancel.com/i/grok/share/64379ef4f…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8f93abef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fraudsters are taking advantage of SNAP aka “food stamps” by filing in 5 different states using dead...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/73d9137d</link>
      <description>Fraudsters are taking advantage of SNAP aka “food stamps” by filing in 5 different states using dead people’s information and then selling the food stamps for money</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_73d9137d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is a whole of government effort and the result of@realDonaldTrumpleadership letting good cops b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cac48349</link>
      <description>This is a whole of government effort and the result of@realDonaldTrumpleadership letting good cops be cops. At the@FBIfor example we had a 31% increase in fentanyl seizures 2025, 2,100 kilos - what would’ve been enough to kill 150+ million Americans. Real lives being saved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cac48349</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Feeling Optimustic about the future!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/627d016d</link>
      <description>Feeling Optimustic about the future!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_627d016d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
