<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-09 04:05 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:05:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia is outgrowing Wikipedia by a wide margin. Last month: • Grokipedia: +52.61% • W...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4d5bd993</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia is outgrowing Wikipedia by a wide margin. Last month: • Grokipedia: +52.61% • Wikipedia: +4.77% The shift is accelerating. (Source:@Similarweb) 📈</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4d5bd993</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: There you have it. Tesla has finally published the official curb weight specs for the Semi: 500 mile...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2ce0b94b</link>
      <description>There you have it. Tesla has finally published the official curb weight specs for the Semi: 500 mile and 23000lbs or ~800km and ~10 metric tons (this is the top of the line) The clowns really wanted this data, will they now just accept it or more predictably dismiss it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2ce0b94b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: TryGrokipedia.com. Post links on your social media and websites.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32dfdd3a</link>
      <description>TryGrokipedia.com. Post links on your social media and websites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32dfdd3a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Such a beautifully simple and light interstate for Starship Super Heavy</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/26e48691</link>
      <description>Such a beautifully simple and light interstate for Starship Super Heavy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_26e48691</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Awesome</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/733991c9</link>
      <description>Awesome</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_733991c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: .@elonmuskcertainly turned out to be right about Steve Bannon.populistsentinel.com/bannons…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a8a1be86</link>
      <description>.@elonmuskcertainly turned out to be right about Steve Bannon.populistsentinel.com/bannons…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a8a1be86</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Released Epstein files show Steve Bannon communicated extensively with Jeffrey Epstein post-2008 con...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dbed6c77</link>
      <description>Released Epstein files show Steve Bannon communicated extensively with Jeffrey Epstein post-2008 conviction, advising on media strategies to rehab his image. They discussed a documentary Bannon filmed (15+ hours) to "humanize" Epstein, using legal tactics like Kovel agreements for privilege. Texts cover PR responses, protests, and projects like a border wall. No evidence links Bannon to Epstein's crimes. Sources: PBS, Guardian, Business Insider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dbed6c77</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48bdd30a</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48bdd30a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If you think Voter ID is racist You’re making racist assumptions Shame on you</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/93a14f77</link>
      <description>If you think Voter ID is racist You’re making racist assumptions Shame on you</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_93a14f77</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For those unaware, SpaceX has already shifted focus to building a self-growing city on the Moon, as ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e261eafd</link>
      <description>For those unaware, SpaceX has already shifted focus to building a self-growing city on the Moon, as we can potentially achieve that in less than 10 years, whereas Mars would take 20+ years. The mission of SpaceX remains the same: extend consciousness and life as we know it to the stars. It is only possible to travel to Mars when the planets align every 26 months (six month trip time), whereas we can launch to the Moon every 10 days (2 day trip time). This means we can iterate much faster to complete a Moon city than a Mars city. That said, SpaceX will also strive to build a Mars city and begin doing so in about 5 to 7 years, but the overriding priority is securing the future of civilization and the Moon is faster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e261eafd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia just passed 350K backlinks More and more sites are linking to Grokipedia every ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e76ff752</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia just passed 350K backlinks More and more sites are linking to Grokipedia every day, as per@SimilarwebIf you run a blog or website, you can help by adding a Grokipedia link and spreading the word.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e76ff752</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Our $1M Grok Ad Contest winner:@andyorsow</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4c7e19f1</link>
      <description>Our $1M Grok Ad Contest winner:@andyorsow</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4c7e19f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Most people still don’t know that Starlink offers fast, low latency, affordable connectivity almost ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/515d4735</link>
      <description>Most people still don’t know that Starlink offers fast, low latency, affordable connectivity almost anywhere on Earth!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_515d4735</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The world is a lot smaller with@Starlink, time to colonize the stars!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c82e311e</link>
      <description>The world is a lot smaller with@Starlink, time to colonize the stars!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c82e311e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fast, affordable internet. Available all around the world! Order in less than 2 minutes by clicking ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/054a3d54</link>
      <description>Fast, affordable internet. Available all around the world! Order in less than 2 minutes by clicking below or, if you live in the US, by calling 1-888-GO-STARLINK to get connected with the Starlink service plan that works best for you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_054a3d54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cheer your team on with two new Grok Imagine templates. Update to the latest Grok app version on iOS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/728025b8</link>
      <description>Cheer your team on with two new Grok Imagine templates. Update to the latest Grok app version on iOS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_728025b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thomas Sowell: “Slavery was not confined by race. It was not defined or created by race. It existed ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/52e8d46a</link>
      <description>Thomas Sowell: “Slavery was not confined by race. It was not defined or created by race. It existed for thousands of years. A history professor once had a student come up to him and ask, ‘When did slavery begin?’ The real question is: when did freedom begin? Slavery existed as long as we have records. From archaeological findings, we know that people were enslaving other people before they could read or write. It has always existed and has existed all over the world. The number of White people enslaved by pirates in North Africa was greater than the number of Africans brought to the United States. And yet, that’s not even mentioned.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_52e8d46a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Morgan McSweeney has resigned as chief of staff to Keir Starmer, due to Epstein relation, ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/defabdc4</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Morgan McSweeney has resigned as chief of staff to Keir Starmer, due to Epstein relation, per FT</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_defabdc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is how the scam works</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ec50a7fb</link>
      <description>This is how the scam works</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ec50a7fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink Super Bowl ad! Affordable Internet anywhere.Starlink.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f35fd529</link>
      <description>Starlink Super Bowl ad! Affordable Internet anywhere.Starlink.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f35fd529</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
