<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-20 05:51 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Anti-ICE protestors protecting convicted child molesters is pure evil</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f7687805</link>
      <description>Anti-ICE protestors protecting convicted child molesters is pure evil</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f7687805</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Seems to be everywhere</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5cd54eee</link>
      <description>Seems to be everywhere</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5cd54eee</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Scrappy out here looking for my metal and rubber parts 📹kaislumps</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/613e1b70</link>
      <description>Scrappy out here looking for my metal and rubber parts 📹kaislumps</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_613e1b70</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: She is 100% correct.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/43eb322c</link>
      <description>She is 100% correct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_43eb322c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Leftist agitators are not peacefully protesting immigration policies, they are purposefully interfer...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d6af3feb</link>
      <description>Leftist agitators are not peacefully protesting immigration policies, they are purposefully interfering with the apprehension of child rapist and woman beaters. These are the types of people roaming St. Paul, MN thanks to the radical left! SICK!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d6af3feb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Without the SAVE Act, efforts to elect Republicans are a lie</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/73bf2932</link>
      <description>Without the SAVE Act, efforts to elect Republicans are a lie</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_73bf2932</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The United States processed 27 million online voter registration applications between 2018 and 2020....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/99d0b084</link>
      <description>The United States processed 27 million online voter registration applications between 2018 and 2020. These 27 million online applications required no proof of citizenship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_99d0b084</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Globe Telecom has signed a deal with@Starlinkto launch direct-to-cell satellite connectivity (...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b1324e84</link>
      <description>NEWS: Globe Telecom has signed a deal with@Starlinkto launch direct-to-cell satellite connectivity (Starlink Mobile) in the Philippines within the next few months. The operator said in a statement it will be the first to offer Starlink’s satellite-to-mobile service in the Philippines and Southeast Asia, and the second in Asia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b1324e84</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I just watched a video of a girl who was put on testosterone at 14 talk about her voice changing and...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d2192a9b</link>
      <description>I just watched a video of a girl who was put on testosterone at 14 talk about her voice changing and how no one told her that testosterone doesn’t just lower your voice. It literally thickens the vocal cords, and the female larynx is not built to accommodate that, now it hurts for her to even speak. I had no idea and I wonder how much other crap like this nobody is being told. Putting children on this crap and changing their lives forever should be a crime for both parents and doctors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d2192a9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thanks for leading the way in the House,@timburchett! We MUST pass the SAVE Act to secure our electi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8653e879</link>
      <description>Thanks for leading the way in the House,@timburchett! We MUST pass the SAVE Act to secure our elections and save our country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8653e879</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If we can’t get Republicans to pass the most inoffensive, common-sense bill in history, one that’s s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d8dccdc0</link>
      <description>If we can’t get Republicans to pass the most inoffensive, common-sense bill in history, one that’s supported by the vast majority of Americans, what use are they? Why should anyone vote for any of them again?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d8dccdc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We know the algorithm is dumb and needs massive improvements, but at least you can see us struggle t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/09a67e72</link>
      <description>We know the algorithm is dumb and needs massive improvements, but at least you can see us struggle to make it better in real-time and with transparency. No other social media companies do this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_09a67e72</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: 𝕏 has open sourced its For You feed algorithm, the same production system running today an...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/97a1b492</link>
      <description>BREAKING: 𝕏 has open sourced its For You feed algorithm, the same production system running today and powered by Grok from xAI. The full code is live on GitHub and will be refreshed every 4 weeks. Your feed blends posts from accounts you follow with posts discovered across all of 𝕏, then ranks them using a Grok based transformer that predicts how likely you are to like, reply, repost, click, or watch. Instead of one simple score, the model predicts many actions and combines them for a more nuanced ranking. Everything learns directly from user behavior. Intelligence lives inside the model, not scattered pipelines. The system is modular, transparent, and stable, with each post scored independently so results are cacheable and consistent. This is one of the most open looks ever at a large scale social feed ranking system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_97a1b492</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: One of the dumbest things ever</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/11443ed2</link>
      <description>One of the dumbest things ever</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_11443ed2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 2017, an autistic white kid in Chicago was abducted and tortured by 4 black suspects, livestreame...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a43b1426</link>
      <description>In 2017, an autistic white kid in Chicago was abducted and tortured by 4 black suspects, livestreamed online Don Lemon: "I don't think it's evil"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a43b1426</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Buy Ryan Air and restore Ryan as their rightful ruler</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e13e98a8</link>
      <description>Buy Ryan Air and restore Ryan as their rightful ruler</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e13e98a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
