<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-03 15:41 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:41:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I am confident at this point that restoring full body functionality is possible with@neuralink</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7b8712b1</link>
      <description>I am confident at this point that restoring full body functionality is possible with@neuralink</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7b8712b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try it!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fd73ef2f</link>
      <description>Try it!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fd73ef2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Falcon 9 launches the@ASI_SpazioCOSMO-SkyMed Second Generation to orbit from California</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/380f1144</link>
      <description>Falcon 9 launches the@ASI_SpazioCOSMO-SkyMed Second Generation to orbit from California</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_380f1144</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: All these major media outlets falsely claimed Elon Musk’s enthusiastic wave was a Nazi salute: • The...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a693afaf</link>
      <description>All these major media outlets falsely claimed Elon Musk’s enthusiastic wave was a Nazi salute: • The New York Times • BBC • NPR • CNN • Axios • The Washington Post • Reuters • MSNBC • Al Jazeera • USA Today • The Guardian • The Independent They knew it wasn’t true. Yet none of them will dare make the same accusation against Mamdani. This is why the propaganda media is the enemy of the people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a693afaf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: To really be intelligent, AI has to make predictions that are in line with reality. “It's...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/28734b5f</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: To really be intelligent, AI has to make predictions that are in line with reality. “It's incredibly important for an AI model to be grounded in reality. I have a saying, which is physics is the law and everything else is a recommendation. I'm not suggesting people break the laws made by humans, we should generally obey the laws of humans. But I've seen many people break human made laws, but I have not seen anyone break the laws of physics. So, for any given AI, grounding it against reality and reality, for example, as you mentioned with the car, it needs to drive safely and correctly. The humanoid robot Optimus needs to perform the task that it's being asked to perform. These are things that are very helpful for ensuring that the model is truthful and accurate because it has to adhere to the laws of physics. So I think that's actually maybe somewhat overlooked or at least not talked about enough is that to really be intelligent it's got to make predictions that are in line with reality. In other words, physics.” Conversation with Satya Nadella, May 19, 2025</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_28734b5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tesla FSD is life’s time and money glitch. When you’re the driver of a Tesla, you sit down, relax, a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0b544f36</link>
      <description>Tesla FSD is life’s time and money glitch. When you’re the driver of a Tesla, you sit down, relax, and let the car handle 100% of the work. It takes you where you need to go while you get your time back with no stress, when normally, the car would be doing nothing and a human would be doing 100% of the work. Then, while you’re at home with your family, sleeping, working, or just living life being present… that same Tesla will be able to go out on its own, pick people up, drop them off, and earn $ for you. This is what makes this technology feel like a glitch that gives you your time back and makes $ for you, all enabled by this technology that lives in every Tesla. For all of history, making income meant trading hours of your hard effort for $, where you gotta show up or you don’t get paid. FSD flips that on its head. Now the car will work for you, whether you’re in it or not and time stops being the limit. Time is the one thing you NEVER get back. And FSD is about making the most of your limited time and keeping you safe, while it works for you in the background whenever you want. I get it now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0b544f36</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Made with@GrokImagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e92541b3</link>
      <description>Made with@GrokImagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e92541b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Humanity must become multiplanetary and it will. Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/57de496b</link>
      <description>Humanity must become multiplanetary and it will. Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_57de496b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "Making life multiplanetary expands the scope &amp; scale of consciousness. Starship is the o...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/02d796ec</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "Making life multiplanetary expands the scope &amp; scale of consciousness. Starship is the only way for us to become a multiplanet civilization." -@elonmusk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_02d796ec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 𝕏 ♾ 🖤 👻🎶🎭</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/51920aa6</link>
      <description>𝕏 ♾ 🖤 👻🎶🎭</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_51920aa6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We must get to Mars to ensure the long term consciousness of humanity. Made with Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d4a8c074</link>
      <description>We must get to Mars to ensure the long term consciousness of humanity. Made with Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d4a8c074</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: grok imagine: ethereal dark fantasy female figure with long flowing hair, wearing an intricate metal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1868816b</link>
      <description>grok imagine: ethereal dark fantasy female figure with long flowing hair, wearing an intricate metallic crown with sharp antler-like protrusions, eyes closed in serene expression, pale skin glowing softly. Her lower arms and torso are transforming into glossy black liquid metal with reflective chrome details, sharp claw-like fingers emerging from the darkness. Dramatic backlighting creating a halo effect around her head, cool blue-toned misty atmosphere, cinematic lighting, highly detailed, surreal and elegant, dark fantasy aesthetic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1868816b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This picture was taken on Mars last week.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/06cb70bd</link>
      <description>This picture was taken on Mars last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_06cb70bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "The United States of America has successfully carried out a large scale strike against Venezuela an...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bc84703a</link>
      <description>"The United States of America has successfully carried out a large scale strike against Venezuela and its leader, President Nicolas Maduro, who has been, along with his wife, captured and flown out of the Country. This operation was done in conjunction with U.S. Law Enforcement. Details to follow. There will be a News Conference today at 11 A.M., at Mar-a-Lago. Thank you for your attention to this matter! President DONALD J. TRUMP"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bc84703a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Then it is war</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dabf3dd9</link>
      <description>Then it is war</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dabf3dd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
