<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-16 05:54 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:54:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ilhan Omar calls for dismantling the Minneapolis Police Department. All while anti-ICE rioters ransa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3fd271ea</link>
      <description>Ilhan Omar calls for dismantling the Minneapolis Police Department. All while anti-ICE rioters ransack federal vehicles and steal weapons. Democrats are the pro-criminal party. President Trump, invoke the Insurrection Act!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3fd271ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "California’s wealth tax is only on billionaires!" That’s how the income tax started too. Only for t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e3c3dbb7</link>
      <description>"California’s wealth tax is only on billionaires!" That’s how the income tax started too. Only for the ~1%… until it wasn’t. When you allow the government to introduce new taxes, they never shrink, only expand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e3c3dbb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2008. Obama slams the Bush Administration for not doing enough to combat the problem of illegal immi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/37bdad05</link>
      <description>2008. Obama slams the Bush Administration for not doing enough to combat the problem of illegal immigration. 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_37bdad05</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is real-time</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3f1c0057</link>
      <description>Grok is real-time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3f1c0057</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: How can@Yalestudents learn about the world if they are taught by faculty from only one side of the a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/03ba904e</link>
      <description>How can@Yalestudents learn about the world if they are taught by faculty from only one side of the aisle?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_03ba904e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tragic. But it’s not too late for@paramountplusto save the franchise. Step 1: Reconcile with@William...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a1230fac</link>
      <description>Tragic. But it’s not too late for@paramountplusto save the franchise. Step 1: Reconcile with@WilliamShatnerand give him total creative control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a1230fac</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: TryGrokipedia.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa966385</link>
      <description>TryGrokipedia.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa966385</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If ICE backs down now, they’ll be teaching these criminals that their illegal tactics work. Send mor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aa72d988</link>
      <description>If ICE backs down now, they’ll be teaching these criminals that their illegal tactics work. Send more agents. Send the national guard. Arrest them all on federal charges so local juries can’t let them off. Enough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aa72d988</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thank you, Scott Adams. You lost your son to a fentanyl and made it one of your missions to stamp it...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/470d7419</link>
      <description>Thank you, Scott Adams. You lost your son to a fentanyl and made it one of your missions to stamp it out. You did it, Scott, you did it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_470d7419</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Immortality can be yours!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aa0100c1</link>
      <description>Immortality can be yours!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aa0100c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Accurate</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/676e5bbb</link>
      <description>Accurate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_676e5bbb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Creating what we will never see, that is poetry.” - Gerardo Diego Grok Imagine understands poetry a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6e2429b9</link>
      <description>“Creating what we will never see, that is poetry.” - Gerardo Diego Grok Imagine understands poetry and it's beautiful to see how he translates it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6e2429b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Every day, for the prior 4 years under the Biden Administration, our country was mass invaded and fo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7e5bd267</link>
      <description>Every day, for the prior 4 years under the Biden Administration, our country was mass invaded and forcibly occupied by illegal aliens. Innocent American children were raped, mutilated and murdered. Entire towns (Springfield, Columbus, Eu Claire) were resettled. Entire neighborhoods were turned into refugee camps. Entire communities were transformed. Schools and medical systems ravaged. The treasury raided. Walkable communities made unlivable. Family parks made into crime scenes. Communities scarred, besieged. These are incomparable crimes against nation and citizen. Yet, not one day in that long and brutal nightmare did the corrupt press show one tiny microscopic fraction of the outrage they now hurl at the brave HEROES courageously reversing this invasion in the face of unceasing far-left assault. That is because the corrupt press is a key instrument in the Left’s quest for national dissolution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7e5bd267</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: in 2015, bernie was literally maga</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/db51c7d9</link>
      <description>in 2015, bernie was literally maga</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_db51c7d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I just met with the President. I am recommending a full travel ban on every damn country that's been...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/df529d25</link>
      <description>I just met with the President. I am recommending a full travel ban on every damn country that's been flooding our nation with killers, leeches, and entitlement junkies. Our forefathers built this nation on blood, sweat, and the unyielding love of freedom—not for foreign invaders to slaughter our heroes, suck dry our hard-earned tax dollars, or snatch the benefits owed to AMERICANS. WE DON'T WANT THEM. NOT ONE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_df529d25</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Feeling Optimustic about the future!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/627d016d</link>
      <description>Feeling Optimustic about the future!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_627d016d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
