<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-23 01:11 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:11:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Tesla is now offering FSD (Supervised) V14 ride alongs in Spain and Finland. Spain sign up:tes...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/65b93991</link>
      <description>NEWS: Tesla is now offering FSD (Supervised) V14 ride alongs in Spain and Finland. Spain sign up:tesla.com/events/fsd-supervi…Finland sign up:tesla.com/events/fsd-supervi…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_65b93991</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "I've been asked a few times like, do I want to die on Mars? And I'm like, Yes, but just ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/06749465</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "I've been asked a few times like, do I want to die on Mars? And I'm like, Yes, but just not on impact." 🤣</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_06749465</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A driverless Tesla Robotaxi. No one in the car. No safety driver. Fully autonomous. This is actually...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/52d2cc38</link>
      <description>A driverless Tesla Robotaxi. No one in the car. No safety driver. Fully autonomous. This is actually happening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_52d2cc38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Protect the light of consciousness</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/06c55779</link>
      <description>Protect the light of consciousness</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_06c55779</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: VP JD Vance in Minneapolis: “We're not trying to send a political message. We're trying to enforce t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4c0747bc</link>
      <description>VP JD Vance in Minneapolis: “We're not trying to send a political message. We're trying to enforce the law.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4c0747bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "In the future, the robots will make so many robots, that they will actually saturate all...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4b9f8590</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "In the future, the robots will make so many robots, that they will actually saturate all human needs, meaning you won't be able to even think of something to ask the robot for at a certain point, like there will be such an abundance of goods and services. There'll be more robots than people. I think everyone on earth is going to have one humanoid robot because you would want a robot to watch over your kids, take care of your pet, take care of elderly parents. I'm very optimistic about the future. I think we're headed for a future of amazing abundance, which is very cool. Definitely we are in the most interesting time in history."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4b9f8590</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Well done!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5034c9a5</link>
      <description>Well done!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5034c9a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Most people don't understand what Elon is saying about AI and robotics: 1. real GDP is a direct func...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8869e8ed</link>
      <description>Most people don't understand what Elon is saying about AI and robotics: 1. real GDP is a direct function of the volume of goods and services and their cost 2. humanoid hyper-intelligent robots can make every need go asymptotically to $0 3. ubiquitous abundance and high income are a very real possibility Obviously, there's a jagged front in this wave of progress, but it'll accelerate at an insane speed And, as long as the AI can't lie and the robots can't hurt humans, it will be an incredible future</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8869e8ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: True, install a@TeslaPowerwall to have uninterrupted power for your house. When your utility goes do...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ff07411c</link>
      <description>True, install a@TeslaPowerwall to have uninterrupted power for your house. When your utility goes down, you will be one of the few in your neighborhood with working lights, working refrigerator and able to charge all your devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ff07411c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok can watch and summarize videos for you</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/71550add</link>
      <description>Grok can watch and summarize videos for you</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_71550add</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It should be the ONLY priority for the senate, as democracy dies otherwise</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/59aada7b</link>
      <description>It should be the ONLY priority for the senate, as democracy dies otherwise</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_59aada7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This will be lots of fun, and incredibly impactful. Let me know if you're up for it!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/53d3a0ea</link>
      <description>This will be lots of fun, and incredibly impactful. Let me know if you're up for it!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_53d3a0ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Join the@Tesla_Optimusteam either in AI or electromechanical engineering!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c7c973e</link>
      <description>Join the@Tesla_Optimusteam either in AI or electromechanical engineering!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c7c973e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The latest updates to Grok Imagine have improved prompt understanding and dynamic movement. Look at ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0e512ba0</link>
      <description>The latest updates to Grok Imagine have improved prompt understanding and dynamic movement. Look at the camera movements, they're great!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0e512ba0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: LLMs can overfit benchmarks but not the stock market. The future isn’t hackable.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/194b0555</link>
      <description>LLMs can overfit benchmarks but not the stock market. The future isn’t hackable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_194b0555</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Use video mode (turn on camera) and Grok voice will explain everything you’re looking at</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1c459c06</link>
      <description>Use video mode (turn on camera) and Grok voice will explain everything you’re looking at</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1c459c06</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
