<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-14 13:53 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:53:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Governments cannot give freedom. They can only curtail it.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/205b9def</link>
      <description>Governments cannot give freedom. They can only curtail it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_205b9def</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Every single MP quitting X to "protect women" from bikini pics voted against grooming gang inquiries...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1ce2feec</link>
      <description>Every single MP quitting X to "protect women" from bikini pics voted against grooming gang inquiries. Not exaggerating. What does that tell you?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1ce2feec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: .@POTUS: "Our country wasn’t built by people who tried to lie, and cheat, and scam their way to succ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/57f3d747</link>
      <description>.@POTUS: "Our country wasn’t built by people who tried to lie, and cheat, and scam their way to success—it was built by legends like Henry Ford, Henry Dow, Thomas Edison... men who lifted up American workers, and strengthened our nation."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_57f3d747</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 800k voters found to be improperly registered to vote in Oregon</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3b620bc6</link>
      <description>800k voters found to be improperly registered to vote in Oregon</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3b620bc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Defund NED</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7c4b0b4c</link>
      <description>Defund NED</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7c4b0b4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Everything Trump has done was done through Executive Orders. Everything will revert back when a Demo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2179bfd3</link>
      <description>Everything Trump has done was done through Executive Orders. Everything will revert back when a Democrat gets into office. For permanent change, everything must be made into a LAW through Congress. Terminate the filibuster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2179bfd3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Calling it now. This will be the most important book of 2026…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/edef071a</link>
      <description>Calling it now. This will be the most important book of 2026…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_edef071a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇪🇺🇭🇺 EU OFFICIAL CAUGHT PLOTTING “RESISTANCE” AGAINST HUNGARY'S PM ORBAN Short version, without the ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8ab819d5</link>
      <description>🇪🇺🇭🇺 EU OFFICIAL CAUGHT PLOTTING “RESISTANCE” AGAINST HUNGARY'S PM ORBAN Short version, without the Brussels perfume. Leaked files say a senior EU official was quietly working, as far back as 2019, on a plan to organize and coordinate opposition against Viktor Orban. Not metaphorical resistance. Actual structure. NGOs, unions, funding vehicles, election timelines. The whole starter kit. The guy, Marton Benedek, was sitting inside EU institutions while sketching out a roadmap for protests, messaging, fundraising, even something that reads a lot like a shadow government. He talks openly about building a permanent coordination hub to challenge Orban’s rule. This was an EU migration and security official, with deep access and zero plausible deniability, not just some street activist. The early effort flopped. The party he helped build face-planted electorally. But the playbook didn’t disappear. It just waited. Fast forward and suddenly a brand-new figure, Peter Magyar, drops out of nowhere, gets wall-to-wall Western media love, runs a campaign with serious money and polish, keeps his ideology vague, stays aggressively pro-EU, and rockets to the top of the polls. No clear funding trail. No real policy spine. But momentum. The uncomfortable part for Brussels isn’t whether Orban is good or bad. It’s that this confirms what his supporters have said for years: The EU doesn’t just pressure governments. It actively works around them when they won’t comply. Rule of law language on the surface. Regime-management instincts underneath. If this were Russia doing it, headlines would be screaming “foreign interference.” When it’s Brussels, it’s called cooperation. Source:@ZeroHedge</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8ab819d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wow, that means they’re registered to vote</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fc716756</link>
      <description>Wow, that means they’re registered to vote</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fc716756</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Men who have a good sense of humour including self-deprecating humour are ultimately very self-confi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7ee29eff</link>
      <description>Men who have a good sense of humour including self-deprecating humour are ultimately very self-confident. Because it is an honest signal of one's self-assuredness. For example, when I do all of my satirical skits to make fun of the woke imbeciles (including many of my colleagues), I'm doing it knowing full well that it will not be received well amongst the castrati. But my response is: I don't give a f**k because I am authentic to a fault. The Delphic maxim, Know Thyself, is operative here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7ee29eff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Only one side had to build a wall to keep people from escaping. Many people risk their life on a tin...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/291bacd2</link>
      <description>Only one side had to build a wall to keep people from escaping. Many people risk their life on a tiny boat to get from Cuba to America, but none go the other way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_291bacd2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: History will not be kind to Starmer</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/264daa81</link>
      <description>History will not be kind to Starmer</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_264daa81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: REPORT: Australia has just introduced what may be the most extreme hate speech law in Western histor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1105128a</link>
      <description>REPORT: Australia has just introduced what may be the most extreme hate speech law in Western history. The new 2026 “Combating Antisemitism, Hate and Extremism Bill” punishes speech that causes fear—even if no harm occurs—with up to 5 years in prison. It gets worse. The law applies to nearly everything: tweets, blogs, memes, even quoting scripture online. It explicitly states that it doesn’t matter if anyone actually felt hatred or fear. And it allows the government to go back in time and charge people for things they said before the law existed. The bill also gives police power to ban groups without due process—including groups outside Australia—and to imprison citizens for up to 15 years for “supporting” them. And while it claims to offer religious protections, a rep from the Attorney General’s Department confirmed that Catholics and Christians will not receive those protections—even as Jewish, Islamic, and Sikh Australians do. If you post a Bible verse today, what’s stopping them from calling it hate speech tomorrow? Don't miss@zeeemedia's report:👇rumble.com/v74aeto-uk-kids-f…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1105128a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: #Statement| The Foreign Ministry of the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia welcomes the designation by the Unit...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5fb867c2</link>
      <description>#Statement| The Foreign Ministry of the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia welcomes the designation by the United States of America of the Muslim Brotherhood branches in Egypt, Jordan, and Lebanon as terrorist groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5fb867c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In the last 12 years, the number of child care workers has increased by about 33%, while the number ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e71ccdf2</link>
      <description>In the last 12 years, the number of child care workers has increased by about 33%, while the number of children ages 5 and under fell by 8.8%. The isn't just a matter of Somali fraudsters. It’s a much bigger story about special-interest politics boosted by ideology and masquerading as family policy.washingtonexaminer.com/in_fo…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e71ccdf2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: People talk trash about me moving to the right. They say, "B-b-but you've lost your friends." First ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c702f95a</link>
      <description>People talk trash about me moving to the right. They say, "B-b-but you've lost your friends." First they proved they weren't my friends. Second I finally saw eye-to-eye with my parents. Third I became the leader of my family. I gained my soul. Keep talking. It's what you do.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c702f95a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Live at@StarbaseTX!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/238398c3</link>
      <description>Live at@StarbaseTX!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_238398c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
