<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>X (Twitter) - @elonmusk</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Fetched via Nitter (https://xcancel.com)</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDA...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDANCE for all!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-0-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Grok models are incredibly advanced at search and now hold two spots among the t...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Grok models are incredibly advanced at search and now hold two spots among the top five on the Search Arena leaderboard</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-1-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>New polling shows that the public favors a single national AI framework over a 5...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>New polling shows that the public favors a single national AI framework over a 50 state patchwork by 20 points, and moreover, supports executive action until Congress can act. Total vindication for President Trump’s One Rulebook approach.buildingamericasfuture.com/w…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-2-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Elon Musk: There's a weird movement to quell free speech around the world. We sh...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Elon Musk: There's a weird movement to quell free speech around the world. We should be concerned about that.

“Why was the First Amendment a high priority? Number one is because people came from countries where if you spoke freely, you would be imprisoned or killed. And they were like, we would like to not have that here, because that was terrible. 

And actually, there's a lot of places in the world right now, if you're critical of the government, you get imprisoned or killed. We'd like to not have that.”

Source: All-In Summit, September 9, 2024</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-3-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>“There’s no separating Minnesota from our Somali brothers &amp; sisters. There’s no ...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>“There’s no separating Minnesota from our Somali brothers &amp; sisters. There’s no reason that every person has to go to bed hungry at night. We have the ability to feed every person.” - Tim Walz as Somalis stole billions from hungry children under his watch</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-4-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Coming soon: a new series revealing the truth behind some of the most mischaract...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Coming soon: a new series revealing the truth behind some of the most mischaracterized, misunderstood, and misrepresented events in history</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-5-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>This keeps happening to innocent people</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>This keeps happening to innocent people</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-6-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Yes!</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Yes!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-7-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Crazy</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Crazy</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-8-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/ToaqJQbyW…</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/ToaqJQbyW…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-9-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Turn any picture on your phone into a video and then edit it to make a fun viral...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Turn any picture on your phone into a video and then edit it to make a fun viral video!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-10-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Why homelessness is never fixed</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Why homelessness is never fixed</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-11-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Grok's slogan is “To Understand" &amp; "Understand the Universe” and this is the mai...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Grok's slogan is “To Understand" &amp; "Understand the Universe” and this is the main goal of Grok in order to find the whole truth. This is the only way to have AI safety and that's why I only trust Grok.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-12-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj said something at Amfest that was really profound. I'm paraphrasing,...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Nicki Minaj said something at Amfest that was really profound. I'm paraphrasing, but she said, "just because I want little black girls to think they're beautiful doesn't mean I need to put down little girls with blonde hair and blue eyes." 

We all got wrapped up over the last few years in zero sum thinking. This was because the people who think they rule the world pit us against one another.@NICKIMINAJrejects that. We all should.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-13-1766425196</guid></item><item><title>Correct</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Correct</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-14-1766425196</guid></item></channel></rss>