<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-11 22:40 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:40:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Same professional protestor found at 100 different protests</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3b4ccf03</link>
      <description>Same professional protestor found at 100 different protests</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3b4ccf03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: the authoritarian playbook, sound familiar? - control the narrative - label dissent as “misinformati...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ee0d40d8</link>
      <description>the authoritarian playbook, sound familiar? - control the narrative - label dissent as “misinformation” - centralize information channels - use selective enforcement - normalize surveillance - create dependency - exploit crises - encourage self-censorship - moral framing</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ee0d40d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: EditingGrokipedia.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f4f93c2a</link>
      <description>EditingGrokipedia.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f4f93c2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Long list</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/614c87ab</link>
      <description>Long list</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_614c87ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xcancel.com/i/grok/share/iOuwnDfhB…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9a642290</link>
      <description>xcancel.com/i/grok/share/iOuwnDfhB…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9a642290</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Absolutely</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/719315d6</link>
      <description>Absolutely</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_719315d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Hypocrisy for one reason only: voter fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/88cae719</link>
      <description>Hypocrisy for one reason only: voter fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_88cae719</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Once the NGOs start receiving funding from the government, they are almost impossible to stop. You a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fd78823f</link>
      <description>Once the NGOs start receiving funding from the government, they are almost impossible to stop. You are funding your own destruction. It’s an outrage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fd78823f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Does seem low</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/debc1fc4</link>
      <description>Does seem low</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_debc1fc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Why is a non-talking filibuster allowed to happen? This makes it impossible to pass laws. It cannot ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4a79ccfb</link>
      <description>Why is a non-talking filibuster allowed to happen? This makes it impossible to pass laws. It cannot be constitutionally valid, given that it runs so contrary to the will of the people! The point of the filibuster was simply to allow senators to make their argument before legislation was passed. It is NOT there to require 60 votes to pass anything at all.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4a79ccfb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The most ironic outcome is capitalists paying for their own destruction. Fate loves irony.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f4f8b126</link>
      <description>The most ironic outcome is capitalists paying for their own destruction. Fate loves irony.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f4f8b126</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Americans voting overwhelmingly for mass deportation. Congress passed laws requiring it and then pas...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bb8bb995</link>
      <description>Americans voting overwhelmingly for mass deportation. Congress passed laws requiring it and then passed new legislation to fully fund it. The response of the Democrat Party and its activists has been to support and orchestrate violent resistance against federal law enforcement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bb8bb995</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Correct</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a5708bdd</link>
      <description>Correct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a5708bdd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “We should be concerned about anything that undermines the 1st Amendment. There is a reason for the ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d3f980e4</link>
      <description>“We should be concerned about anything that undermines the 1st Amendment. There is a reason for the 1st Amendment. People came from countries where they could not speak freely - where saying certain things would get you thrown in prison.” — Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d3f980e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Medi Hasan talking about prosecuting Elon Musk isn't actually because Elon is breaking any laws. It'...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b213463f</link>
      <description>Medi Hasan talking about prosecuting Elon Musk isn't actually because Elon is breaking any laws. It's because Elon is very powerful and effective. Think about this.. He owns the most free speech platform on the internet. He himself has over 230 million followers. He is on his way to being worth 1 trillion dollars. He owns the likely fastest advancing AI in the world. He is essentially 100% on the side of the republicans And he is only in his mid 50's meaning he has at least a 20 year runway. That is why democrats would want to prosecute him. He is too big of a threat to their political power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b213463f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: No ID, automatic voter registration by states and mail in ballots enable massive fraud. Those factor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3e0a484b</link>
      <description>No ID, automatic voter registration by states and mail in ballots enable massive fraud. Those factors also make it impossible to prove fraud, since there is no ID and no one actually showed up! You can’t conduct exit polls accurately or even count how many people went in to vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3e0a484b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
