<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-30 03:54 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:54:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is from a 2018 Minnesota criminal prosecution against Somali daycare fraudsters. In surveillanc...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/55010d21</link>
      <description>This is from a 2018 Minnesota criminal prosecution against Somali daycare fraudsters. In surveillance video, Somali parents would take their kids to the daycare, check them in, and then leave with them moments later. The owners of the daycare would then bill the state for a full day of childcare-- and give the parents kickback payments for being in on the fraud. Somali fraudsters have been stealing from taxpayers for years and it's clear that the entire Somali community is in on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_55010d21</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I have some bad news. If you are rightfully upset about the daycare fraud in Minnesota, it is only 1...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cfd8810f</link>
      <description>I have some bad news. If you are rightfully upset about the daycare fraud in Minnesota, it is only 1 program. There are 14 programs identified as high risk by federal prosecutors. These are being called the “fraudy 14” 1. Adult Companion Services 2. Adult Day Services 3. Adult Rehabilitative Mental Health Services 4. Assertive Community Treatment 5. Community First Services and Supports (Personal Care Assistance) 6. Early Intensive Developmental and Behavioral Intervention (EIDBI) services for autism 7. Housing Stabilization Services 8. Individualized Home Supports 9. Integrated Community Supports 10. Intensive Residential Treatment Services 11. Night Supervision Services 12. Nonemergency Medical Transportation Services 13. Peer Recovery/Recovery Peer Support Services 14. Recuperative Care</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cfd8810f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The deal was an even playing field, not extremely tilted in the other direction. They broke the deal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/81702fb4</link>
      <description>The deal was an even playing field, not extremely tilted in the other direction. They broke the deal. Therefore, there is no deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_81702fb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Americans' trust in mainstream media hits record lows (28%), as 𝕏 sees all-time highs in u...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ad82fa70</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Americans' trust in mainstream media hits record lows (28%), as 𝕏 sees all-time highs in usage + citizen journalism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ad82fa70</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Standard practice. But when you ask to send pictures of who is being helped or try to talk to the pa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/80caffb9</link>
      <description>Standard practice. But when you ask to send pictures of who is being helped or try to talk to the parents, they ghost you. And the wiring instructions are to wealthy accounting firms …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_80caffb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: JUST IN: It has been revealed Ilhan Omar's net worth grew from negative $45k in 2019 to $30 million ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e069e0bf</link>
      <description>JUST IN: It has been revealed Ilhan Omar's net worth grew from negative $45k in 2019 to $30 million this year — despite her salary being just $174k/year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e069e0bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: As should we all</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0878532f</link>
      <description>As should we all</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0878532f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Oh look: Giving men testosterone induces a red shift in democrats, reduces lying and makes them more...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9dd5ae50</link>
      <description>Oh look: Giving men testosterone induces a red shift in democrats, reduces lying and makes them more likely to do what they believe is right. Who would have thought?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9dd5ae50</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We will bring an end to the Somali fraud network.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ce2ea301</link>
      <description>We will bring an end to the Somali fraud network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ce2ea301</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Democrats hate when this gets shared</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/36fdf125</link>
      <description>Democrats hate when this gets shared</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_36fdf125</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: DHS is on the ground in Minneapolis, going DOOR TO DOOR at suspected fraud sites. The American peopl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/14d0fb6a</link>
      <description>DHS is on the ground in Minneapolis, going DOOR TO DOOR at suspected fraud sites. The American people deserve answers on how their taxpayer money is being used and ARRESTS when abuse is found. Under the leadership of@Sec_Noem, DHS is working to deliver results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_14d0fb6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Not even an address</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2afb992e</link>
      <description>Not even an address</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2afb992e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For years, people attacked Elon Musk over government contracts won by SpaceX....... contracts that s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4cf024c3</link>
      <description>For years, people attacked Elon Musk over government contracts won by SpaceX....... contracts that saved taxpayers billions and literally rescued U.S. spaceflight Yet those same people never ask: • Where did the $13-15B go on California’s invisible high-speed rail? • Why is there silence on $1B+ daycare fraud by Somalis in Minnesota? • Other 100s of Billions in Fraud Let’s be clear..... If not for Elon, the U.S. would’ve been begging Russia or China to reach the ISS NASA gave Boeing $4.2B SpaceX got $2.6B Here are the result: • SpaceX: Years of successful crew &amp; cargo missions • Boeing: Years late, budget overruns, and stranded astronauts..... SpaceX had to step in Today, SpaceX handles ~90% of the world’s payload to orbit For comparison: • Space Shuttle: 135 missions in 30 years • SpaceX: 165+ Falcon 9 missions in 2025 SpaceX earned those contracts because no one else could do the job....... and did it cheaper, faster, and safer And while some people cry about contracts, Elon is pushing US forward in: • Space • EVs • Manufacturing • AI • Energy Without Elon, U.S. would be behind China in all of it Think about that...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4cf024c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Over 4 billion visits per month</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dc5d0bff</link>
      <description>Over 4 billion visits per month</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dc5d0bff</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here is how voter fraud is done</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/81eb9778</link>
      <description>Here is how voter fraud is done</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_81eb9778</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s not just the Somalis in Minnesota. The Dems opened up our nation to anyone who would come here ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1be9f056</link>
      <description>It’s not just the Somalis in Minnesota. The Dems opened up our nation to anyone who would come here and vote for them, in exchange for our tax dollars. They use shell companies to funnel public money to the immigrants, meaning we are slaves that fund the people replacing us. This is why the Dems so desperately don’t want voter ID. Because they are wittingly engaged in a scheme to let the illegals vote, which allows them to stay in power, which allows them to continue to steal our tax dollars. It’s all one giant racket, an We the People are the suckers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1be9f056</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yeah, and the scheme was working too</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/76c5c8ab</link>
      <description>Yeah, and the scheme was working too</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_76c5c8ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We have charged 98 individuals in relation to fraud in Minnesota. More than 60 have pled guilty or b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6ba23cbf</link>
      <description>We have charged 98 individuals in relation to fraud in Minnesota. More than 60 have pled guilty or been convicted. More to come.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6ba23cbf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c32bdaec</link>
      <description>Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. That’s how insanely awful the level of fraud actually is!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c32bdaec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
