<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-27 18:57 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:57:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: SpaceX is building GigaBay to produce 1,000 Starships per year At GigaBay, SpaceX is mass...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0b361ba6</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: SpaceX is building GigaBay to produce 1,000 Starships per year At GigaBay, SpaceX is massively expanding production and integration to reach an annual output of 1,000 Starships The structure itself is enormous, by some measures, it will be the largest building on Earth It’s designed specifically for rapid Starship assembly at unprecedented scale SpaceX is building two GigaBays, one in Texas and another in Florida, bringing Starship production to the Space Coast When you see a human next to these buildings, the scale becomes obvious It’s hard to grasp how massive they are until you do This is industrial capacity built for one purpose: making life multi-planetary....🚀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0b361ba6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Made for fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d9994f3b</link>
      <description>Made for fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d9994f3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yes. We found hundreds of fraud schemes. This is one of many. There was massive fraud in every gover...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/68549dd7</link>
      <description>Yes. We found hundreds of fraud schemes. This is one of many. There was massive fraud in every government program, especially Federal funds sent as block grants to the states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_68549dd7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here’s the inconvenient truth… If@elonmuskdidn’t buy Twitter, the fraud exploding out of Minnesota w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/82e4df7a</link>
      <description>Here’s the inconvenient truth… If@elonmuskdidn’t buy Twitter, the fraud exploding out of Minnesota would still be buried. Tim Walz might even be Vice President right now. Independent platforms broke the Democrat media monopoly. And the truth finally got out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_82e4df7a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 73% of children in Brussels, the capital of Europe, are not European! The Great Replacement has alre...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2ab6d734</link>
      <description>73% of children in Brussels, the capital of Europe, are not European! The Great Replacement has already happened.xcancel.com/i/grok/share/zYKy91usx…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2ab6d734</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: &gt;We’re so glad you’re safe! “I hate white people” &gt;You’ve been our top priority! “I literally want t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/16580db0</link>
      <description>&gt;We’re so glad you’re safe! “I hate white people” &gt;You’ve been our top priority! “I literally want to kill you” &gt;Welcome home! “You British are dogs and monkeys” &gt;Quickly, take this passport!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_16580db0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok just took the #1 spot across all three Open Router LLM Leaderboard rankings and ranke...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dbb7de07</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok just took the #1 spot across all three Open Router LLM Leaderboard rankings and ranked #1 in programming category too, beating Google, OpenAI, and the rest. 🔥</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dbb7de07</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A sign that leftists don't even like their ideology, is that when they have money they choose to liv...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0cfd7ed1</link>
      <description>A sign that leftists don't even like their ideology, is that when they have money they choose to live as far away from the consequences of their policies as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0cfd7ed1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For rides to the same destination, Robotaxi and Waymo had the same 4-minute pickup wait, but vastly ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b357cb56</link>
      <description>For rides to the same destination, Robotaxi and Waymo had the same 4-minute pickup wait, but vastly differed in travel time and fare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b357cb56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Hard work is the way to success!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/82b83062</link>
      <description>Hard work is the way to success!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_82b83062</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Correct</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0d87cf36</link>
      <description>Correct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0d87cf36</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Of course</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/551ebc87</link>
      <description>Of course</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_551ebc87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX rules 1. Make Requirements Less Dumb 2. Delete the Part or Process Step 3. Optimize 4. Accele...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/76244649</link>
      <description>SpaceX rules 1. Make Requirements Less Dumb 2. Delete the Part or Process Step 3. Optimize 4. Accelerate 5. Automate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_76244649</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Mass immigration of people that want to kill White people IS White genocide!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f2325c4d</link>
      <description>Mass immigration of people that want to kill White people IS White genocide!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f2325c4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: wtf else would it be!?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ebeb3c48</link>
      <description>wtf else would it be!?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ebeb3c48</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Next year ALL California public schools must have at least one gender-neutral restroom. Meanwhile al...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/95b903bd</link>
      <description>Next year ALL California public schools must have at least one gender-neutral restroom. Meanwhile also in California schools: 📍63% are below grade level standard in math 📍51% are below grade level standard in English 📍67% are below grade level standard in Science We need to return focus to education NOT gender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_95b903bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7b28166</link>
      <description>The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain vast numbers of illegal (and legal, in some cases) immigrants to win elections and turn America into a single-party state, destroying any real democracy. The more you look at it, the more you will be horrified at what your tax money is doing and the fact that, if this is not reversed, your vote will mean nothing. The most obvious case example is the Somali voting bloc in Minnesota, a state that historically had zero Somalis, electing Ilhan Omar to the US Congress. The same is happening in Europe, UK, Canada, Australia and New Zealand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7b28166</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
