<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-30 18:57 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:57:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: I’m calling for the denaturalization and deportation of every Somali engaged in fraud in M...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c1ee8847</link>
      <description>BREAKING: I’m calling for the denaturalization and deportation of every Somali engaged in fraud in Minnesota. Read my full statement below: “I have three words regarding Somalis who have committed fraud against American taxpayers: Send them home. If they’re here illegally, deport them immediately; if they’re naturalized citizens, revoke their citizenship and deport them quickly thereafter. If we need to change the law to do that, I will. Our nation will not tolerate those who take advantage of our charity and refuse to assimilate into our culture. Additionally, if any naturalized Somalis had undisclosed ties to terrorist organizations like Al-Shabaab, I want to see their citizenship revoked and their asses sent back immediately. Same goes for anyone who is found to have committed marriage fraud during the immigration process.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c1ee8847</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Very big file</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/934c0bd0</link>
      <description>Very big file</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_934c0bd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The wildest thing about the Somali daycare scandal is that apparently the government’s goal was to s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/90bbb428</link>
      <description>The wildest thing about the Somali daycare scandal is that apparently the government’s goal was to subsidize daycares for random immigrants while tax paying American parents have been complaining for years they can barely afford childcare with two incomes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_90bbb428</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xcancel.com/i/grok/share/bXqu2uyL0…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2ae59886</link>
      <description>xcancel.com/i/grok/share/bXqu2uyL0…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2ae59886</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Traitor Tim Walz</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3bdf9c5f</link>
      <description>Traitor Tim Walz</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3bdf9c5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Today's cover: A bombshell video puts Tim Walz under fire over the alleged Somali daycare scheme in ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a63b794c</link>
      <description>Today's cover: A bombshell video puts Tim Walz under fire over the alleged Somali daycare scheme in Minnesota.trib.al/Aci1uFn</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a63b794c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: MORE IN MINNEAPOLIS. Our investigative agents are conducting a massive operation to identify, arrest...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1a1a3580</link>
      <description>MORE IN MINNEAPOLIS. Our investigative agents are conducting a massive operation to identify, arrest, and remove criminals who are defrauding the American people. We will root out this rampant fraud plaguing Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1a1a3580</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: THE AUTOPEN PRESIDENT, RIDDLED WITH FRAUD AND MISMANAGEMENT!@HUDgov</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/78bde78a</link>
      <description>THE AUTOPEN PRESIDENT, RIDDLED WITH FRAUD AND MISMANAGEMENT!@HUDgov</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_78bde78a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fraud will grow infinitely if not stopped</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f44e9e66</link>
      <description>Fraud will grow infinitely if not stopped</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f44e9e66</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tim Walz blames the Somali fraud on 1. white people 2. the Somali community not being educated on ou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/be9da787</link>
      <description>Tim Walz blames the Somali fraud on 1. white people 2. the Somali community not being educated on our laws ANYTHING BUT THE TRUTH!!!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_be9da787</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The latest budget proposal from the European Commission proposes a 600 percent increase in NGO fundi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b53b37e</link>
      <description>The latest budget proposal from the European Commission proposes a 600 percent increase in NGO funding.compactmag.com/article/why-t…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b53b37e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s fraud at scale</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2d2d5b38</link>
      <description>It’s fraud at scale</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2d2d5b38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That is exactly what happens</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4bc8d559</link>
      <description>That is exactly what happens</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4bc8d559</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: No assimilation, just fraud and not contributing via work</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2372e619</link>
      <description>No assimilation, just fraud and not contributing via work</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2372e619</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The problem isn’t the taxes. USSR had no billionaires and had a nearly 100% effective tax rate, and ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7aff563b</link>
      <description>The problem isn’t the taxes. USSR had no billionaires and had a nearly 100% effective tax rate, and it still failed. The problem is the spending. Dollars spent by the state that do not produce a meaningful economic surplus are dollars wasted. If enough of them are wasted and a crisis hits the fan, there is no economic basis to absorb the shock. The stupid high speed rail, $20b spent and nothing that could be sold for anything anywhere near $20b+ was built. Do that over and over and you get Russia in the 90s. All the smart and kind people leave, and you are left with the smart and vicious people ready to take advantage of the crumbling political environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7aff563b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie availab...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d8e32a22</link>
      <description>My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie available to subscribers. I recommend taking this approach for text/image/video content on 𝕏.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d8e32a22</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
