<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-17 19:42 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:42:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sooner or later, people reveal exactly who and what they are. Reform clearly isn’t the solution many...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a6510a38</link>
      <description>Sooner or later, people reveal exactly who and what they are. Reform clearly isn’t the solution many were hoping for, unfortunately many will have to face this and come to terms with it. If you still back Reform, it’s worth asking yourself why.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a6510a38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Madness</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6923474b</link>
      <description>Madness</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6923474b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Reid Hoffman had a profound business and personal relationship with Jeffrey Epstein. It's not just a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/affd58a3</link>
      <description>Reid Hoffman had a profound business and personal relationship with Jeffrey Epstein. It's not just a few connections here and there. They were very close friends in constant contact, all the way up to his 2019 arrest. Yet Hoffman says he rarely talked to him. It is incredible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_affd58a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Demonstrable lies by@reidhoffmanabout his relationship with Epstein</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2d27add4</link>
      <description>Demonstrable lies by@reidhoffmanabout his relationship with Epstein</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2d27add4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If Harvard's defiance of the Supreme Court or their decision to target White students in doing so su...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/77e72ea5</link>
      <description>If Harvard's defiance of the Supreme Court or their decision to target White students in doing so surprises you, you haven't been paying attention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_77e72ea5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: So after 3 days of driving all around Salt Lake area in a Tesla Y, I'm going to give my opinion on i...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/74658df2</link>
      <description>So after 3 days of driving all around Salt Lake area in a Tesla Y, I'm going to give my opinion on it... I love it, and I want one. That's the main takeaway. I've had it in a few anxiety inducing situations, and I restrained myself from grabbing the steering wheel. It performed flawlessly! I love the look of the door handles, but I don't really love the way they function. And I do notice that it is not a timid little car. It's pretty assertive in traffic, and I like that. But sometimes it tends to go over the speed limit. I just let it do it's thing. I had two hands on my coffee cup, and it told me to have my hands ready to drive! It also doesn't put up with me looking at my phone much which is a good thing. The technology is a bit of a learning curve, but my two grandsons ages 12 and 8 just tell me what to do. (It's humiliating.) My husband likes to be in control when he drives, so I don't know that we'll agree to get one anytime soon. But it's my dream to own one now!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_74658df2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Europe extinctionists</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5027f57c</link>
      <description>Europe extinctionists</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5027f57c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just asked the four Grok 4.20 (Beta) agents to build me an artificial life simulator. My mind is blo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e983af6f</link>
      <description>Just asked the four Grok 4.20 (Beta) agents to build me an artificial life simulator. My mind is blown. What should I get him to build next? &gt;&gt;&gt; grok prompt Build an artificial life simulator in one single HTML file. Hundreds of glowing neon particles in different cyberpunk colors. Each pair of colors has its own attraction/repulsion force that you control with sliders. You get emergent “creatures”, swarms, orbiting rings, exploding clusters, chasing packs, it feels alive. Features: - Click/drag to spawn particles of selected color - Real-time force matrix (6×6 sliders) - Randomize rules button (insane results every time) - Pause, speed, particle count, trails/glow toggle - Dark cyberpunk UI with scanlines + glitch effects optional</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e983af6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Grok 4.2 release candidate (public beta) is now available for use. You need to select it specifi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0b25b8ef</link>
      <description>The Grok 4.2 release candidate (public beta) is now available for use. You need to select it specifically. Critical feedback is appreciated. Unlike prior versions of Grok, 4.2 is able to learn rapidly, so there will be improvements every week with release notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0b25b8ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Congratulations to the Tesla team on making the first production Cybercab!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/55a20117</link>
      <description>Congratulations to the Tesla team on making the first production Cybercab!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_55a20117</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is most physically accurate of the four. Opus rear bike frame makes no sense structurally, ther...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3519a85d</link>
      <description>Grok is most physically accurate of the four. Opus rear bike frame makes no sense structurally, there is no connection from pedals to rear wheel, both legs of Pelican are on the right side of the bike and handle bars are disconnected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3519a85d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.2 will be about an order of magnitude smarter and faster than Grok 4 when the public beta con...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b9cb7a52</link>
      <description>Grok 4.2 will be about an order of magnitude smarter and faster than Grok 4 when the public beta concludes next month. Still many bug fixes and improvements landing every day. The public beta gives us more critical feedback to address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b9cb7a52</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Right wing groups used Asian students to challenge race discrimination in college admissions because...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a49772b5</link>
      <description>Right wing groups used Asian students to challenge race discrimination in college admissions because it’s taboo for White people to actually advocate for ourselves openly. This taboo must be destroyed. Anyone trying to weasel around this core issue is part of the problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a49772b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is genuinely fun to use Love that new model smell</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/665e4f5c</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is genuinely fun to use Love that new model smell</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_665e4f5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Predicting the future accurately is the best measure of intelligence</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5dce7d5f</link>
      <description>Predicting the future accurately is the best measure of intelligence</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5dce7d5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is funny, based &amp; smart 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/10d4de8b</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is funny, based &amp; smart 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_10d4de8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OpenAI quietly dropped "safely" and "no financial motive" from its mission</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/65152699</link>
      <description>OpenAI quietly dropped "safely" and "no financial motive" from its mission</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_65152699</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is ridiculously good. Multiple agents push it into another league.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8ce3d384</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is ridiculously good. Multiple agents push it into another league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8ce3d384</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cybercab, which has no pedals or steering wheel, starts production in April</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9425b973</link>
      <description>Cybercab, which has no pedals or steering wheel, starts production in April</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9425b973</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
