<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-19 05:51 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:51:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f8c2319d</link>
      <description>Try Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f8c2319d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX now operates the largest satellite constellation in Earth orbit Starlink today: • ~65–70% of ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3853a977</link>
      <description>SpaceX now operates the largest satellite constellation in Earth orbit Starlink today: • ~65–70% of all active satellites around Earth • ~9,500 active satellites in orbit • ~8,500+ fully operational, delivering real broadband worldwide • Speeds: 200–400 Mbps typical with ~30 ms latency • Tonight: Falcon 9 adds 29 more satellites And this is just the beginning The FCC approved 7,500 additional Gen2 satellites, bringing the total to 15,000 This means better global coverage, higher speeds, and support for direct-to-cell connectivity From remote villages to oceans and skies, Starlink is reshaping global connectivity at a scale never seen before SpaceX is building planet-scale infrastructure that will accelerate human progress on Earth like never before</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3853a977</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just saw this snake in Palo Alto.@Grokwhat kind of snake is this and is it dangerous?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0457a468</link>
      <description>Just saw this snake in Palo Alto.@Grokwhat kind of snake is this and is it dangerous?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0457a468</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 BREAKING: Speaker Johnson &amp; Steve Scalise are DROPPING the HAMMER! They’re about to pass a TURBOCH...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f18913b6</link>
      <description>🚨 BREAKING: Speaker Johnson &amp; Steve Scalise are DROPPING the HAMMER! They’re about to pass a TURBOCHARGED SAVE Act: • Requires PHOTO ID • Proves CITIZENSHIP to vote “The SAVE Act plus—a picture ID requirement.” “There are states PREVENTING voter ID, a recipe for fraud!” This lights a FIRE under the Senate RINOs. Bring it to the floor FULL-STEAM AHEAD! No more stolen elections. GET IT PASSED!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f18913b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The idea grows more appealing every day 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/066e88d9</link>
      <description>The idea grows more appealing every day 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_066e88d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 NICK SHIRLEY CALLS OUT ANDREW CALLAGHAN: "YOU TAMPERED WITH OUR INTERVIEW AND I’VE GOT THE RECEIP...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4f5dc480</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 NICK SHIRLEY CALLS OUT ANDREW CALLAGHAN: "YOU TAMPERED WITH OUR INTERVIEW AND I’VE GOT THE RECEIPTS" Nick Shirley caught Channel 5’s Andrew Callaghan chopping their 2.5-hour convo on Minnesota daycare fraud down to a slick hour. Callaghan cut every part where he fumbled or got called out. Nick dropped the unedited footage to prove it, showing how the final cut twisted the story. One of the big edits? Dodging the stat that 86% of the fraud is tied to Somali networks. Source: YouTube,@nickshirleyy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4f5dc480</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Anyone want a free tunnel?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/31740517</link>
      <description>Anyone want a free tunnel?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_31740517</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here is Grok’s answer to your challenge@CathyYoung63What percentage of people arrested by ICE agents...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6b86859e</link>
      <description>Here is Grok’s answer to your challenge@CathyYoung63What percentage of people arrested by ICE agents are illegal aliens and what percentage are innocent citizens? Grok: According to data from U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) and independent tracking by organizations like the Transactional Records Access Clearinghouse (TRAC) and media outlets, ICE arrests overwhelmingly target non-citizens with immigration violations—commonly referred to as illegal aliens or undocumented immigrants. Reports indicate that over 328,000 people were arrested by ICE from January to mid-December 2025. Wrongful arrests of U.S. citizens (who could be considered "innocent" in this context, as they are not subject to immigration enforcement) are rare but documented. Investigations have identified more than 170 confirmed cases of U.S. citizens being held by ICE agents in 2025, often due to errors in questioning citizenship status. Other sources report up to 674 arrests of individuals claiming or confirmed as U.S. citizens during the same period, though only about 121 were detained beyond initial arrest. Using the higher estimate of 674 wrongful arrests out of approximately 328,000 total ICE arrests in 2025, this represents about 0.2% of arrests. The lower confirmed figure of 170 cases equates to roughly 0.05%. In either case, the percentage of "innocent people" (U.S. citizens wrongly arrested) is under 1%, while approximately 99.8-99.95% are non-citizens with immigration violations (illegal aliens). Note that ICE prioritizes arrests of non-citizens with criminal convictions or charges (about 70% of arrests), but the remaining 30% are typically non-criminal immigration violators—still classified as illegal aliens under U.S. law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6b86859e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Accurate assessment</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/177227d4</link>
      <description>Accurate assessment</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_177227d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Many people don’t realise the only reason ICE agents have to do raids at people’s home or work are b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f05c1267</link>
      <description>Many people don’t realise the only reason ICE agents have to do raids at people’s home or work are because local politicians have refused to consent to information sharing between local &amp; federal law enforcement, which enables efficient, non violent apprehension of illegal aliens</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f05c1267</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2nd Place: Memeable is a browser extension that generates personalized memes of people from X thread...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/29145b87</link>
      <description>2nd Place: Memeable is a browser extension that generates personalized memes of people from X threads. Create personalized ready-to-post memeable content with one click.@thomasthecosmic@gubmee</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_29145b87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 3rd Place: GrokWorld uses Grok Imagine as a world model to generate synthetic training data for robo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7d964280</link>
      <description>3rd Place: GrokWorld uses Grok Imagine as a world model to generate synthetic training data for robots — augmenting or replacing months of manual collection in hours.@apturaai</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7d964280</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Being built as we speak</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d5f48716</link>
      <description>Being built as we speak</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d5f48716</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Travelling to America as an Australian is terrifying. Because living in Australia, we're sheltered. ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e356b5ce</link>
      <description>Travelling to America as an Australian is terrifying. Because living in Australia, we're sheltered. We're far from the rest of the world. Our State Sponsored Media tells you that Australia has the best of everything in the world. That our culture and lifestyle is unmatched. But as soon as you arrive in America it is blindingly obvious how false that is. America feels explosive, alive, chaotic, rich. It's loud, obnoxious, unapologetic. There's no hint of tall poppy syndrome. And no constant nagging of the Nanny State. America is accelerating into an unknown future without fear. There are so many technological innovations here that would never see the light of day in Australia, because they would be strangled by regulation. Australia is beautiful, sure. But it's safe, quiet, controlled. Media and society tell you to conform, comply, be seen and not heard. Take the safe option. Be fearful of new things. Be fearful of the future. The spark of innovation is stifled. The light of creativity is discouraged. The warmth of the collective is more important than the rugged individual. And as time goes on, one of the two countries is going to be left behind. It's pretty clear which country that is. So, it's terrifying. And before I came here, everyone said I should be terrified of America. That I wouldn't be let it the country. That everyone is rioting. That Hitler runs the country. That couldn't be further from the truth. Their brains have been absolutely fried by Australian State Sponsored media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e356b5ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Articles … articles as far as you can see</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/377eb532</link>
      <description>Articles … articles as far as you can see</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_377eb532</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: personalized memes ready-to-post on X sounds fun</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5f53f06a</link>
      <description>personalized memes ready-to-post on X sounds fun</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5f53f06a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a31b6a70</link>
      <description>The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a31b6a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
