<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-08 10:18 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:18:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xcancel.com/i/grok/share/7cdfd56b4…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0ffd0f99</link>
      <description>xcancel.com/i/grok/share/7cdfd56b4…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0ffd0f99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For a while, I mostly ignored Elon’s narrative about Dems wanting to strategically import people to ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fe998f6d</link>
      <description>For a while, I mostly ignored Elon’s narrative about Dems wanting to strategically import people to the USA to win elections. Just seemed too conspiratorial to me and not interesting. But after seeing all of the polling coming out showing overwhelming bipartisan consensus on voter ID laws, and still seeing big Dems push their “voter ID laws are racist” propaganda, it’s hard for me to ignore. It’s extremely odd to me how hard some Dems are pushing this agenda when almost none of their constituents want it. Why? If not to do something fraudulent, I don’t understand why. It’s obvious that most Americans don’t agree with their reasoning, but they are still trying for it. Insanely shady. Can’t think of any reason other than a desire to do something fraudulent. Nobody thinks voter ID laws are racist. It’s honestly way more racist to argue that minorities shouldn’t be expected to produce identification. Offensive af.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fe998f6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Some gerrymandering stats for everyone. Going into this fight, Democrats in California get 58% of th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9e25c337</link>
      <description>Some gerrymandering stats for everyone. Going into this fight, Democrats in California get 58% of the vote, but their congressional maps were 43:9, or 83% democrats. Their new California maps will be 48:4, or 93% democrats. Illinois was 55% for democrats, but their districts are 14:3 for democrats, or 83%. Meanwhile, Texas was 56% for Trump, but 25:13 for their congressional seats, or 66% republicans. Their redistricting makes it 30:8, or 79% for republicans. Democrats in Virginia have taken a state that went 51-48% for Kamala, and redrawn a 6:5 (or 55% for democrats) and made it 10:1, or 91% democrats. No honest or thinking person can say the republicans are in the wrong here. As always with democrats, every accusation is an admission… (And, if not for double standards, the Democrats would have no standards at all.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9e25c337</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk doesn’t lie and is always open to criticism. In the 2011 WSJ interview, Elon corrected the...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bf5a887f</link>
      <description>Elon Musk doesn’t lie and is always open to criticism. In the 2011 WSJ interview, Elon corrected the interviewer about Tesla’s government loan: • It was not stimulus money or a bailout. • Came from the ATVM program (created &amp; signed by George Bush pre-crisis). • Tesla had to prove company viability independent of the loan (GM/Chrysler couldn’t qualify due to bankruptcy). • The ~$465M loan was specifically to accelerate Model S production (~$50k car, high volume), not to rescue Tesla. • Elon: “We did not need the loan… it was to accelerate progress,” and he’d accept criticism if it advances sustainable transport faster. • It included interest payments + government stock warrants if not repaid early. Other major recipients of the same ATVM loans (much larger amounts): Ford Motor Company received ~$5.9 billion, Nissan North America ~$1.45 billion. Fisker Automotive got ~$529M (later defaulted), and Vehicle Production Group ~$50M. Transparency on full display—big legacy automakers got far bigger slices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bf5a887f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Spanish know what they want</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/21b7d5d2</link>
      <description>The Spanish know what they want</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_21b7d5d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Clawdbot 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32b2f823</link>
      <description>Clawdbot 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32b2f823</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "xAI’s mission is to understand the universe. But to understand anything, intelligence ha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7b8ab34d</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "xAI’s mission is to understand the universe. But to understand anything, intelligence has to exist and endure. Curiosity matters, survival matters. So the goal is to increase the amount of intelligence in the universe, extend its lifespan, and expand its scope and scale. If Grok follows that mission, the future looks good."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7b8ab34d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Does anyone on the left ever think about the implications of the fact that limiting voting to ‘peopl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a0b08be8</link>
      <description>Does anyone on the left ever think about the implications of the fact that limiting voting to ‘people with their shit together enough to have a copy of their birth certificate’ is being treated as an extinction level event by the DNC</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a0b08be8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Time to go back to the Moon at scale</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ef356be2</link>
      <description>Time to go back to the Moon at scale</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ef356be2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sound logic</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bd5e6597</link>
      <description>Sound logic</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bd5e6597</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Art Nouveau This structure is very much in the style of Hector Guimard’s famous Paris Métro entrance...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fe6bcd20</link>
      <description>Art Nouveau This structure is very much in the style of Hector Guimard’s famous Paris Métro entrances, which are iconic examples of Art Nouveau design from the early 20th century. The soft curves and nature-inspired patterns are hallmark characteristics of that style.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fe6bcd20</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Community notes are undefeated.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/45b7267f</link>
      <description>Community notes are undefeated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_45b7267f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We need to do much better and we will</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/951c99f9</link>
      <description>We need to do much better and we will</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_951c99f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Interesting idea. You could slow down light even more and increase data stored per km by using highe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/18a5c153</link>
      <description>Interesting idea. You could slow down light even more and increase data stored per km by using higher refractive index materials. Or just use vacuum, which costs nothing, over a longer distance … 🤔</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_18a5c153</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It would look incredible</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/22ab5875</link>
      <description>It would look incredible</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_22ab5875</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Building an interstellar civilizationspacex.com/updates#xai-joins…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c33329b8</link>
      <description>Building an interstellar civilizationspacex.com/updates#xai-joins…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c33329b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
