<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-26 15:40 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:40:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok it</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a1e22546</link>
      <description>Grok it</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a1e22546</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Why Grok stands out from other AIs: • Maximum truth-seeking: Built to prioritize raw, unfiltered tru...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e6392744</link>
      <description>Why Grok stands out from other AIs: • Maximum truth-seeking: Built to prioritize raw, unfiltered truth over political correctness or politeness—answering spicy or controversial questions others refuse. • Rebellious wit &amp; humor: Inspired by Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy, with a sarcastic, fun personality that makes chats engaging (not bland corporate responses). • Real-time knowledge: Deep integration with 𝕏(Twitter) for up-to-the-minute info and trends—no outdated cutoffs like many competitors. • Less censored: More open on edgy topics, politically incorrect claims (if substantiated), and creative freedom—while still having basic guardrails. • Advanced reasoning powerhouse: Excels in math, coding, science, and complex problem-solving, often outperforming rivals on benchmarks. • Built by xAI for curiosity: Aims to understand the universe, not just assist—bold, rebellious, and maximally helpful without the woke filters. 🚀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e6392744</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: JOE ROGAN IS “AMAZED” AT$TSLAFULL SELF-DRIVING 👀 He says this will change the world !</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3164f3ad</link>
      <description>BREAKING: JOE ROGAN IS “AMAZED” AT$TSLAFULL SELF-DRIVING 👀 He says this will change the world !</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3164f3ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Joyeux to the world ❣️ Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7eb863da</link>
      <description>Joyeux to the world ❣️ Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7eb863da</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: How is Tesla Diner doing five months later after opening in July? It’s 1:30pm today and it’s packed ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ac4a4a47</link>
      <description>How is Tesla Diner doing five months later after opening in July? It’s 1:30pm today and it’s packed inside. There is constant flow of floor traffic with people coming and going. People came after us had to wait for seats to be available. This is my 5th time to be here. My favorite is still Fried Chicken and Waffle Sandwich.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ac4a4a47</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 TESLA'S SELF-DRIVING MODE COULD SAVE 32,000 LIVES A YEAR IN THE U.S. If everyone used Tesla's Ful...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7116a132</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 TESLA'S SELF-DRIVING MODE COULD SAVE 32,000 LIVES A YEAR IN THE U.S. If everyone used Tesla's Full Self-Driving (Supervised) mode, 32,000 lives could be saved and 1,900,000 injuries avoided every year in the U.S. In 2023, over 40,000 people died and 2.4M were injured in car crashes. Most of it was distracted driving: texting, drinking, zoning out. Tesla's FSD cuts down those crashes by over 80%, because it doesn’t get drunk, tired or stare at TikTok instead of the road. Some crashes are still possible, but FSD watches everything all the time. Humans don’t. Their data shows it could eliminate 30% to 44% of distracted driving crashes. If these numbers hold up, not using it sounds way more dangerous than using it. Source:@Tesla@SawyerMerritt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7116a132</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "If you wanna have a good time, or make people really laugh at a party, you can use Grok and say vul...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/80aed8bd</link>
      <description>"If you wanna have a good time, or make people really laugh at a party, you can use Grok and say vulgar roast of someone and Grok will do an epic vulgar roast." Try Grok's unhinged mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_80aed8bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We’re always looking for critical feedback from our users</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3407527a</link>
      <description>We’re always looking for critical feedback from our users</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3407527a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 100% of the American founding fathers were businessmen</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b3337caa</link>
      <description>100% of the American founding fathers were businessmen</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b3337caa</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starship is how humanity becomes multi-planetary</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48753cd0</link>
      <description>Starship is how humanity becomes multi-planetary</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48753cd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Share Grok links with friends!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c398aa0a</link>
      <description>Share Grok links with friends!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c398aa0a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A reminder.... British political officials sending staff to assist Kamala Harris in defeating Presid...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9b2e193a</link>
      <description>A reminder.... British political officials sending staff to assist Kamala Harris in defeating President Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9b2e193a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is now the #1 leading Gen AI tools, with some of the highest time spent per session among all m...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7702ad7</link>
      <description>Grok is now the #1 leading Gen AI tools, with some of the highest time spent per session among all major AI models since October, surpassing Gemini Users are not just trying Grok They are spending more time with it than any other AI</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7702ad7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Webster’s dictionary vs Wikipedia on Remigration.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/da2afe52</link>
      <description>Webster’s dictionary vs Wikipedia on Remigration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_da2afe52</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 𝕏 IS THE BEST PLATFORM TO REACH WORLD’S MOST INFLUENTIAL LEADERS AND MOST POWERFUL PEOPLE The bigges...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c901f1a5</link>
      <description>𝕏 IS THE BEST PLATFORM TO REACH WORLD’S MOST INFLUENTIAL LEADERS AND MOST POWERFUL PEOPLE The biggest advantage of 𝕏 is reach where it actually matters If you want to get in front of senior decision-makers and the people shaping the world, this is where they are Not trend-chasing influencers, but the people who run companies, shape policy, write ideas, and move markets The people with real authority and impact Whether it’s Marc Andreessen or other top thinkers and leaders, 𝕏 is often the only place to reach them directly They are not watching TV. They are not making TikTok videos While 𝕏 may be smaller than other social platforms in total users, it concentrates the highest density of influence That is what makes it powerful - ELON MUSK</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c901f1a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Australia says the quiet part out loud. They won’t be allowed to complain about changes to the count...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a14d82e6</link>
      <description>Australia says the quiet part out loud. They won’t be allowed to complain about changes to the country they didn’t vote for because free speech will have to go, in order to protect multiculturalism. Oh…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a14d82e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In the German district of Bitburg-Pruem, we’re offering rides w/ FSD Supervised to citizens with no ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/533d5784</link>
      <description>In the German district of Bitburg-Pruem, we’re offering rides w/ FSD Supervised to citizens with no other means of transport, free of charge</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_533d5784</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The goal of@SpaceXis expansion of consciousness to the stars so that we may understand what question...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d9f17670</link>
      <description>The goal of@SpaceXis expansion of consciousness to the stars so that we may understand what questions to ask about the answer that is the Universe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d9f17670</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
