<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-20 09:28 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:28:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sometimes, I miss the sheer entertaining idiocy of pronouns in bio</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3f4460ac</link>
      <description>Sometimes, I miss the sheer entertaining idiocy of pronouns in bio</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3f4460ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Did you know that Grok Imagine has a video library with free prompts? 1- Click on the video. 2- Use ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/33da256b</link>
      <description>Did you know that Grok Imagine has a video library with free prompts? 1- Click on the video. 2- Use the video as is, or click "Edit" to customize it to your liking. That's what I did with this video. I changed the background a bit and had this young woman speak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_33da256b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: "There will not be any meaningful elections in the future All of America will be 'Califor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/529dea3e</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: "There will not be any meaningful elections in the future All of America will be 'Californicated' and not in a good way It will actually be worse than California The one thing that holds California back from being even worse than it is, is that people can move out of California and still be in America What happens when there’s no place to move? It’ll be way worse than California"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_529dea3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Pretty much (sigh)</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d2dd4002</link>
      <description>Pretty much (sigh)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d2dd4002</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk warned them three years ago. Today the German government is finally admitting he was right...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7d1f7623</link>
      <description>Elon Musk warned them three years ago. Today the German government is finally admitting he was right Chancellor Friedrich Merz has officially labeled the decision to shut down Germany’s nuclear plants a 'huge mistake,' confessing that the move has crippled the economy and left the country with the most expensive energy transition in the world (What Elon warned 3 years ago:) I think it's very important that Germany not shut down its nuclear power stations? I think this is extremely crazy I want to be super clear. My opinion is Germany should not only not shut down the nuclear power plants, it should reopen the ones that shut down. Those are the fastest ones to restart. It's crazy to shut down nuclear power plants Especially if you're in a place where there are no natural disasters. If you're somewhere with severe earthquakes or tsunamis, it's more of a question mark But if there's not a massive natural disaster risk which Germany does not have then there's really no danger with the nuclear power plants</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7d1f7623</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Correct on all points</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0fdf361d</link>
      <description>Correct on all points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0fdf361d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Any elected official who would refuse to vote to pass Voter ID laws is betraying their voters and th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/87b0d1d3</link>
      <description>Any elected official who would refuse to vote to pass Voter ID laws is betraying their voters and their country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_87b0d1d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Join@xAIand build the best AI-based content recommendation engine (on the way to AGI)</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/36cdfefe</link>
      <description>Join@xAIand build the best AI-based content recommendation engine (on the way to AGI)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_36cdfefe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Democrat open borders plan to entrench single party rule, explained in under two minutes 1. Floo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4c5450d3</link>
      <description>The Democrat open borders plan to entrench single party rule, explained in under two minutes 1. Flood the country with untold millions of illegals by land, sea, and air from all over the world. Enough to eclipse the populations of 36 individual US states so far 2. Prioritize the needs of these millions of non-citizens over the needs of the American citizen, with free flights, buses, hotels, meals and phones, ensuring their loyalty to the political party that imported them 3. Keep them in the country at all costs, even when they commit violent crime like murder and rape. Attack the language used to describe the criminals, as opposed to the criminals themselves. Slander critics as racist 4. Ensure their privileges are made irrevocable with city and state sanctuary laws that act as population magnets. Codify permanent status and ensure non-cooperation with ICE 5. Count the non-citizens in the census that will determine congressional apportionment in the House of Representatives. As of now, that would equal 13 extra congressional districts a tremendous amount of electoral power 6. Wage a massive, heavily funded lawfare campaign to change state voting laws that legalize mass mail-in ballots, no signature verification, and no proof of citizenship requirements, making it nearly impossible to prove voter fraud 7. Lock in the permanent voting majority with campaign promises of lavish benefits and permanent privileges, enshrining generational fealty to the Democrat Party 8. Win elections 9. Entrenched single-party rule has been achieved The best part? Your tax dollars are paying for it</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4c5450d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 08:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: incredible. video prompt: Cosmic hums and ethereal whispers. No background music. Ethereal movements...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/704a278d</link>
      <description>incredible. video prompt: Cosmic hums and ethereal whispers. No background music. Ethereal movements for the figure, physically correct for the human. Slow motion. Volumetric lighting. Bokeh glow. Motion blur on flowing elements. The figure's starry tendrils undulate and shimmer in gentle succession, extending outward rhythmically. The human approaches slowly with lantern swinging, casting flickering reflections. Figure tilts head downward gracefully. Dynamic camerawork with smooth tracking and orbit shot circling the encounter at varying angles. She reaches refracting starlight in waves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_704a278d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: She voted against a grooming gang enquiry</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/92c4ef1b</link>
      <description>She voted against a grooming gang enquiry</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_92c4ef1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Troubling</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c30c3541</link>
      <description>Troubling</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c30c3541</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starship is the gateway to Kardashev civilization.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dc6e5714</link>
      <description>Starship is the gateway to Kardashev civilization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dc6e5714</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: To be clear, I think we should only waive the filibuster to pass an election integrity act into law,...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/923f5d69</link>
      <description>To be clear, I think we should only waive the filibuster to pass an election integrity act into law, but not for any other reason. Election integrity must include visual ID that proves citizenship and in-person voting (except in extreme circumstances like troops overseas).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_923f5d69</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the way</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6504aa05</link>
      <description>This is the way</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6504aa05</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
