<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-17 13:36 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:36:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Our AI5 chip design is almost done and AI6 is in early stages, but there will be AI7, AI8, AI9 … aim...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/52014605</link>
      <description>Our AI5 chip design is almost done and AI6 is in early stages, but there will be AI7, AI8, AI9 … aiming for a 9 month design cycle. Join us to work on what I predict will be the highest volume AI chips in the world by far!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_52014605</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It was the best of times, it was the worst of times, it was the age of wisdom, it was the age of foo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0e59c3cb</link>
      <description>It was the best of times, it was the worst of times, it was the age of wisdom, it was the age of foolishness, it was the epoch of belief, it was the epoch of incredulity, it was the season of light, it was the season of darkness, it was the spring of hope, it was the winter of despair. I think it was Charles Dikkens (with two k’s) who wrote that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0e59c3cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Philippines will be the first country in Southeast Asia to deliver Starlink Direct to Cell. In p...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dfa0ce42</link>
      <description>The Philippines will be the first country in Southeast Asia to deliver Starlink Direct to Cell. In partnership with@enjoyglobe, millions of people will stay connected in remote areas that didn't have coverage before.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dfa0ce42</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Once the Dems realized that importing illegals who are dependent on government handouts would be a g...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/84ce2dce</link>
      <description>Once the Dems realized that importing illegals who are dependent on government handouts would be a guaranteed path to power, they opened the floodgates and refused to deport even hardened criminals. Incentives explain outcomes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_84ce2dce</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: As I was just saying, the Dems won’t even deport extreme criminals, because they will lose that prob...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/17e4a622</link>
      <description>As I was just saying, the Dems won’t even deport extreme criminals, because they will lose that probable voter</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_17e4a622</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Colossus 2 supercomputer for@Grokis now operational. First Gigawatt training cluster in the worl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/018f21c7</link>
      <description>The Colossus 2 supercomputer for@Grokis now operational. First Gigawatt training cluster in the world. Upgrades to 1.5GW in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_018f21c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Senate has had this legislation for MONTHS. WTH is@LeaderJohnThunedoing? Pass the S.A.V.E. Act N...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6d0c1530</link>
      <description>The Senate has had this legislation for MONTHS. WTH is@LeaderJohnThunedoing? Pass the S.A.V.E. Act NOW. Save the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6d0c1530</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: London Grokathon kickoff</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bc135dd4</link>
      <description>London Grokathon kickoff</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bc135dd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Building the future</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/05653bdf</link>
      <description>Building the future</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_05653bdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/995ee8f3</link>
      <description>Starlink</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_995ee8f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Most politicians are just the actors on the stage. You don’t see the scriptwriters, directors and pr...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/be8e49e9</link>
      <description>Most politicians are just the actors on the stage. You don’t see the scriptwriters, directors and producers who control them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_be8e49e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Democracy dies in the darkness caused by a lack of photo voter id</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0ca6ba97</link>
      <description>Democracy dies in the darkness caused by a lack of photo voter id</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0ca6ba97</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Indeed, Idiocracy is happening much faster than expected</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7c2e79c7</link>
      <description>Indeed, Idiocracy is happening much faster than expected</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7c2e79c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Democrats take power and immediately disenfranchise their opponents. Red state republicans can eithe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3f4b768f</link>
      <description>Democrats take power and immediately disenfranchise their opponents. Red state republicans can either disenfranchise them first, or end up living in a vassal district of a blue state. There’s no third option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3f4b768f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: One of the most obvious things that maps like this one immediately confirm is that regular people ar...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/572d8fd1</link>
      <description>One of the most obvious things that maps like this one immediately confirm is that regular people are actually very good at intuiting which neighborhoods are dangerous and which ones aren’t. Progressives sometimes get upset at the idea that there’s any such thing as a, “bad neighborhood,” but, in fact, crime is exactly where people think it is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_572d8fd1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: To think that our descendants will find space travel commonplace...it's so wow! Grok Imagine, of cou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/03b372d7</link>
      <description>To think that our descendants will find space travel commonplace...it's so wow! Grok Imagine, of course</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_03b372d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They mean it</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f91f97a5</link>
      <description>They mean it</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f91f97a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s all medical fraud. After my daughter’s pediatrician at Kaiser Permanente tried to put her on pu...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8e9ea690</link>
      <description>It’s all medical fraud. After my daughter’s pediatrician at Kaiser Permanente tried to put her on puberty blockers and wrong-sex hormones when she was only 14, I did an undercover story when I pretended to be “nonbinary.” I was approved by my Kaiser doctors over Zoom for a double mastectomy (top surgery) and a phalloplasty (fake p*nis) made from the skin tissue on my thigh in under 9 months. It was only a $100 co-pay for my elective mastectomy and $200 co-pay for my phalloplasty yet the surgeons would bill $25k for mastectomy and $135k for the phalloplasty.@FTC@SwipeWright@aboutKP</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8e9ea690</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a31b6a70</link>
      <description>The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a31b6a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
