<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-02 05:54 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:54:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This photo was taken in Mogadishu, 1993. The man on the right was my father: John Boswell, Delta For...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/511d77db</link>
      <description>This photo was taken in Mogadishu, 1993. The man on the right was my father: John Boswell, Delta Force C-Squadron. The stories I’ve heard would rattle you at your core. It’s always some 3rd gen ivy league white lib in America talking about how great Somalia is. Fuck Somalia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_511d77db</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: REMINDER: New Yorkers born in America flatly rejected this man. He was elected by foreigners. If we ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/60d2fa72</link>
      <description>REMINDER: New Yorkers born in America flatly rejected this man. He was elected by foreigners. If we do not stop foreigners from flooding this country, they will all choose this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_60d2fa72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Remember… Mamdani won because NYC imported millions of 3rd world voters. This is the blueprint for t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c5aca169</link>
      <description>Remember… Mamdani won because NYC imported millions of 3rd world voters. This is the blueprint for the Democrats to win elections nationally. We can’t allow that to happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c5aca169</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 BREAKING: Elon Musk calls on Senate Republicans to NUKE the 60-vote filibuster so Trump's MAGA pol...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4f8998d5</link>
      <description>🚨 BREAKING: Elon Musk calls on Senate Republicans to NUKE the 60-vote filibuster so Trump's MAGA policies can be passed with only 51 votes This means we can pass ANYTHING we want with 50 Republicans + JD Vance, and zero Dems If we don't, Dems will. GET THIS DONE, NOW!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4f8998d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨🇺🇸 ASMONGOLD ON MINNESOTA FRAUD: DENATURALIZE AND DEPORT ENTIRE SOMALI FAMILIES... TIM WALZ SHOULD ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1cea9f56</link>
      <description>🚨🇺🇸 ASMONGOLD ON MINNESOTA FRAUD: DENATURALIZE AND DEPORT ENTIRE SOMALI FAMILIES... TIM WALZ SHOULD FACE "TREASON WITH CAPITAL PUNISHMENT" Asmongold, one of the most-watched content creators on the internet, unloaded on the Minnesota fraud scandal and said he's done voting unless politicians deliver maximum accountability: "You have to make the punishment infinitely worse than the crime. I'm talking about deporting the entire family, denaturalizing the entire family, sending the entire group of them back to Somalia. That's what needs to happen. If JD Vance does not push for treason with capital punishment against Tim Walz, do not vote for him. If Trump does not deliver that, do not vote for him." His bottom line: "Unless the most extreme, dramatic, brutal, aggressive option is on the table," he's out. Asmongold's audience skews young, male, and politically disengaged, exactly the demographic Republicans need. When someone with his reach tells millions of viewers that half-measures aren't enough, politicians should pay attention. The frustration is real. Billions stolen. Officials who looked the other way. A system that punishes taxpayers while protecting fraudsters. Whether you agree with his prescription or not, he's voicing what a lot of people are thinking: accountability without consequences isn't accountability at all. Source:@Asmongold@Rightanglenews</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1cea9f56</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: When you open 40 daycare centers in a day - that is fraud.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7f3bebdd</link>
      <description>When you open 40 daycare centers in a day - that is fraud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7f3bebdd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cybercab is truly a piece of art.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2c298e90</link>
      <description>Cybercab is truly a piece of art.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2c298e90</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 JUST IN: Elon Musk EVISCERATES San Francisco for rolling out a $5 million-per-person black people ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/019687e6</link>
      <description>🚨 JUST IN: Elon Musk EVISCERATES San Francisco for rolling out a $5 million-per-person black people reparations fund despite a $1 BILLION deficit "This is deeply morally WRONG." "Why is it right for someone who escaped tyranny in other countries and happens to live in SF to pay 'reparations' for something they had nothing to do with?" 💯 "California didn't even have slaves!"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_019687e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸🇸🇴 SOMALI DAYCARES BUSTED FOR FRAUD IN MINNESOTA… NOW ALL THEIR PHONE NUMBERS ARE DEAD A woman tri...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a74c5a4f</link>
      <description>🇺🇸🇸🇴 SOMALI DAYCARES BUSTED FOR FRAUD IN MINNESOTA… NOW ALL THEIR PHONE NUMBERS ARE DEAD A woman tried calling every single daycare tied to the massive Somali daycare fraud in Minnesota. Not one answered. No rings, no callbacks, just disconnected lines like they never existed. And that happened right after they were exposed for not having kids while taking money from the government. That’s not shady at all, right? Millions gone, and suddenly no one’s home. If this was all above board, why are they all vanishing faster than the tax dollars they pocketed? The answer seems quite clear. Source:@WallStreetApes, maggswegner</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a74c5a4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fraud at extreme scale</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5f396be3</link>
      <description>Fraud at extreme scale</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5f396be3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Over the last week, SBA has reviewed thousands of potentially fraudulent pandemic-era PPP and EIDL l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a3b78791</link>
      <description>Over the last week, SBA has reviewed thousands of potentially fraudulent pandemic-era PPP and EIDL loans approved in Minnesota. Today, our agency took action to suspend 6,900 Minnesota borrowers amid suspected fraudulent activity. In total, these borrowers were approved for 7,900 PPP and EIDL loans worth approximately $400M. These individuals will be banned from all SBA loan programs, including disaster loans, going forward. We will also refer every case, where appropriate, to federal law enforcement for prosecution and repayment. After years, the American people will finally begin to see the criminals who stole from law-abiding taxpayers held accountable - and this is just the first state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a3b78791</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Clinton committed a heinous crime against the American people</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e34cdadd</link>
      <description>Clinton committed a heinous crime against the American people</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e34cdadd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A state that never allowed slavery wants to make residents who never owned slaves pay reparations to...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2b3d99f8</link>
      <description>A state that never allowed slavery wants to make residents who never owned slaves pay reparations to people who never were slaves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2b3d99f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Double-standard</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ac5fc07e</link>
      <description>Double-standard</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ac5fc07e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is awesome</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4c502c77</link>
      <description>Grok is awesome</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4c502c77</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Our last chance to stop the ongoing invasion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d4d50a28</link>
      <description>Our last chance to stop the ongoing invasion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d4d50a28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Then it is war</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dabf3dd9</link>
      <description>Then it is war</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dabf3dd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
