<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-31 15:44 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:44:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "I do see a path to 100 gigawatts a year of AI powered space solar satellites. If you do ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a61f5562</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "I do see a path to 100 gigawatts a year of AI powered space solar satellites. If you do a million tons of payload to orbit per year with 100 kilowatts per ton, that's 100 gigawatts of solar powered AI satellites per year. There's a path to get to a terawatt per year, then you want to make those AI satellites on the moon and use a mass driver. We should scale solar substantially in the US. Tesla and SpaceX are scaling solar, and I encourage others to do so as well."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a61f5562</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk is operating on another timeline right now. We are living through perhaps the most pivotal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9c2b7a4e</link>
      <description>Elon Musk is operating on another timeline right now. We are living through perhaps the most pivotal moment in humanity. Optimism is a beautiful thing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9c2b7a4e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX says it aims to deploy up to 1 million orbital satellite data centers in space to provide eno...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7bb59732</link>
      <description>SpaceX says it aims to deploy up to 1 million orbital satellite data centers in space to provide enough compute power for large-scale AI inference and training. • Satellites will get constant power in space. • No batteries are needed. • No glass framing required, which makes the solar panels cheaper to produce. • Passive Radiative cooling Elon says space will be the lowest-cost place to put AI within 3 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7bb59732</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Awesome detail from the SpaceX orbital datacenter filing - heliocentric disposal of satellites at th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9bba0750</link>
      <description>Awesome detail from the SpaceX orbital datacenter filing - heliocentric disposal of satellites at their end of life. This is necessary long term and is something we've been talking about for a while. You can't re-enter that amount of mass without causing problems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9bba0750</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The ones committing the fraud are the ones complaining the loudest</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0278b7dd</link>
      <description>The ones committing the fraud are the ones complaining the loudest</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0278b7dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia is the future</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/51467a70</link>
      <description>Grokipedia is the future</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_51467a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Solar is not A source of energy, it is THE source of energy</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/894d8a85</link>
      <description>Solar is not A source of energy, it is THE source of energy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_894d8a85</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That is the key question. Epstein and Maxwell were sent to prison for running an underage child sex ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/35f4f60c</link>
      <description>That is the key question. Epstein and Maxwell were sent to prison for running an underage child sex ring. Prosecute their clients!!! Until we see at least one client arrest, this partial release of Epstein files means nothing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_35f4f60c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Absolutely</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/719315d6</link>
      <description>Absolutely</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_719315d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Oops, did I say 1 million? I meant to say 1 billion.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/67c5a2bd</link>
      <description>Oops, did I say 1 million? I meant to say 1 billion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_67c5a2bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "AI and humanoid robots will actually eliminate poverty. There is only one way to make everyone weal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/17c513d1</link>
      <description>"AI and humanoid robots will actually eliminate poverty. There is only one way to make everyone wealthy, &amp; that is AI &amp; robotics." 一 Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_17c513d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: MELANIA, the film NOW PLAYING 🎥 in theaters near you</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7db9bab</link>
      <description>MELANIA, the film NOW PLAYING 🎥 in theaters near you</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7db9bab</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: There will be thousands of court cases of children who were mutilated by evil doctors, modern day Me...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/74894156</link>
      <description>There will be thousands of court cases of children who were mutilated by evil doctors, modern day Mengeles. The schools, psychologists/psychiatrists and state officials who facilitated this will pay dearly too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_74894156</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: RINOs call for smaller government, but tonight these 11 Republicans voted to keep the gravy train go...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bed50ac3</link>
      <description>RINOs call for smaller government, but tonight these 11 Republicans voted to keep the gravy train going for the African Development Foundation. How do you explain this to the American people?@LindseyGrahamSC@SenMcConnell@lisamurkowski@JohnBoozman@SenThomTillis@JerryMoran@SenatorWicker@SenJohnHoeven@SenKevinCramer@SenCapito@SenatorCollins</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bed50ac3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Congratulations to the@FLOTUS!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9a3c2769</link>
      <description>Congratulations to the@FLOTUS!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9a3c2769</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia is now referenced in more than 250,000 responses from other AIs, citing over 90...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bc36c2a0</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia is now referenced in more than 250,000 responses from other AIs, citing over 90,000 individual Grokipedia pages. This growth shows how quickly Grokipedia is embedding itself into the internet’s knowledge layer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bc36c2a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 10 TIMES NVIDIA To put 100 GW/per year of AI computers in perspective, Grok estimates Nvidia is pres...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3f804e92</link>
      <description>10 TIMES NVIDIA To put 100 GW/per year of AI computers in perspective, Grok estimates Nvidia is presently at 10GW/per year in AI compute. IE 10X Nvidia. 100 TRILLION COMPANY Now you see why Elon Musk says a 100 Trillion market cap company may be possible within 10 years. SpaceX, xAI and Tesla will all play major roles in AI Space Compute.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3f804e92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok’s video generation limits crush the competition. SuperGrok (Premium+/equivalent) gives you 100–...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/362818ad</link>
      <description>Grok’s video generation limits crush the competition. SuperGrok (Premium+/equivalent) gives you 100–200 videos/day — hundreds more than Google’s plans. SuperGrok Heavy pushes it to 500–1000 videos/day. Google? Severely restricted: •Google AI Pro: ~3 videos/day (Veo 3.1 Fast preview) •Google AI Ultra: ~5 videos/day (Veo 3.1 preview) Grok lets creators go wild without rationing — single digits vs. hundreds/thousands. Night and day difference. 🚀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_362818ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What matters is not release of some subset of the Epstein files, but rather the prosecution of those...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9d3f3c03</link>
      <description>What matters is not release of some subset of the Epstein files, but rather the prosecution of those who committed heinous crimes with Epstein. When there is at least one arrest, some justice will have been done. If not, this is all performative. Nothing but a distraction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9d3f3c03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
