<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-12 07:46 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:46:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Join us to build AGI and understand the universe!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fdf5c22b</link>
      <description>Join us to build AGI and understand the universe!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fdf5c22b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk in new presentation: "I really want to see a mass driver on the Moon that is shooting AI s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/35aed763</link>
      <description>Elon Musk in new presentation: "I really want to see a mass driver on the Moon that is shooting AI satellites into deep space. I can't image anything more epic than a mass driver on the Moon, a self-sustaining city on the Moon, and then going to Mars, throughout our solar system, and ultimately being out there amongst the stars and visiting all these star systems. Maybe we'll meet aliens."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_35aed763</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s clear. Elon has a bunch of super nerds, that are kind hearted, and extremely driven running xAI...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4da9ea13</link>
      <description>It’s clear. Elon has a bunch of super nerds, that are kind hearted, and extremely driven running xAI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4da9ea13</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Only American citizens should decide American elections.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3a6c99ad</link>
      <description>Only American citizens should decide American elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3a6c99ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is great news!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/11fd0832</link>
      <description>This is great news!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_11fd0832</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This should be the 1 congressional priority: &gt; in 15 states, you don't have to show **any** ID to vo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/20582fdb</link>
      <description>This should be the 1 congressional priority: &gt; in 15 states, you don't have to show **any** ID to vote &gt; 69% of liberal voters support photo ID requirements, but only one democratic senator has voted for the Save Act &gt; either voter ID is mandated now, or, whenever the senate next flips, the opposite will happen (mandated no-ID voting across the US) If the bill doesn't pass now, it would be an absolute disaster for electoral security, and would likely essentially create a permanent one-party state Huge bi-partisan support. It's just a common-sense requirement. The bill is stuck due to the zombie filibuster - where the minority can refuse to vote, without even standing and talking End the filibuster and pass the bill!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_20582fdb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨NEW: Elon Musk explains the reason behind the SpaceX and xAI merger. "In order to understand the un...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e4fb315d</link>
      <description>🚨NEW: Elon Musk explains the reason behind the SpaceX and xAI merger. "In order to understand the universe, you must explore the universe. That's the motivation behind the combination of SpaceX and xAI is to accelerate humanity's future in understanding the universe and extending the light of consciousness to the stars. So in the grand scheme of things, when you look at how much energy Earth is actually using for civilization, we're only right now using, call it roughly 1% of the potential energy of Earth. And if we wanted to use even a millionth of the sun's energy, that would be roughly a million times more energy than civilization currently uses. The only way to access that energy, the energy of the sun is to extend beyond Earth. Earth is really a tiny, tiny dust Mote in a vast darkness. The sun is 99.8% of all mass in the solar system, so you have to expand beyond the tiny dust mode that is earth to make any significant dent in using the sun's energy like says, you'd have to expand roughly a million times just to get to 1,000,000th of our sun's energy, and then going beyond that, exploring extending to the Galaxy. So the the next step beyond Earth data centers is our Earth orbital data centers, and we'll be launching with SpaceX orbital data centers at the 100 to 200 gigawatt per year level, not cumulative, I mean, per year. And ultimately, we see a path to maybe launching as much as a terawatt per year of compute from Earth."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e4fb315d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Please call your senator and ask for voter ID to be passed</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/545aecb4</link>
      <description>Please call your senator and ask for voter ID to be passed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_545aecb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Milton Friedman on 4 ways to spend money: 1) Your money on yourself (you’re careful about both cost ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9db7e660</link>
      <description>Milton Friedman on 4 ways to spend money: 1) Your money on yourself (you’re careful about both cost and quality) 2) Your money on others (you care about cost, less about quality) 3) Someone else’s money on yourself (you care about quality, not cost) 4) Someone else’s money on others (you care about neither) The last one is how government spending works</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9db7e660</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tonight, the House passed the SAVE America Act. Now, it’s the Senate’s turn, and we should pass it i...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/50445fee</link>
      <description>Tonight, the House passed the SAVE America Act. Now, it’s the Senate’s turn, and we should pass it immediately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_50445fee</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Dems are calling requiring Voter ID “racist” and “Jim Crow 2.0”. Some Black populations of countries...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2ff847e0</link>
      <description>Dems are calling requiring Voter ID “racist” and “Jim Crow 2.0”. Some Black populations of countries that require Voter ID to vote: Haiti: 95% Jamaica: 92% Kenya: 99% Ghana: 99% Botswana: 90% South Africa: 81% Brazil: 56% I wonder if they know theyre racist towards themselves?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2ff847e0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Connecting remote schools around the world with high-speed internet 🛰️🌎❤️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ad1e9db6</link>
      <description>Connecting remote schools around the world with high-speed internet 🛰️🌎❤️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ad1e9db6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: startup idea: we sell hand made artisanal code</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/441cbde2</link>
      <description>startup idea: we sell hand made artisanal code</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_441cbde2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Some good lists</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/75b22160</link>
      <description>Some good lists</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_75b22160</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI is going for the endgame win SpaceX is building the Dyson swarm factory intelligence ~ energy th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1dadea8d</link>
      <description>xAI is going for the endgame win SpaceX is building the Dyson swarm factory intelligence ~ energy the way to unlock massive free energy is simply to get compute close to the Sun via a kinetic energy bump mass drivers on the Moon are the most effective way to do the latter</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1dadea8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It's amazing that a simple idea, such as the slope of a tangent line could have so many incredible c...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/656275c4</link>
      <description>It's amazing that a simple idea, such as the slope of a tangent line could have so many incredible consequences. Modern calculus was developed ~365 years ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_656275c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 𝕏 is the set of all things</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/408c9710</link>
      <description>𝕏 is the set of all things</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_408c9710</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa93318c</link>
      <description>xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as quickly as xAI, the structure must evolve just like any living organism. This unfortunately required parting ways with some people. We wish them well in future endeavors. We are hiring aggressively. Join xAI if the idea of mass drivers on the Moon appeals to you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa93318c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
