<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-20 21:41 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:41:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Democrat open borders plan to entrench single party rule, explained in under two minutes 1. Floo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/71c78a73</link>
      <description>The Democrat open borders plan to entrench single party rule, explained in under two minutes 1. Flood the country with untold millions of illegals by land, sea, and air from all over the world. Enough to eclipse the populations of 36 individual US states so far 2. Prioritize the needs of these millions of non-citizens over the needs of the American citizen, with free flights, buses, hotels, meals and phones, ensuring their loyalty to the political party that imported them 3. Keep them in the country at all costs, even when they commit violent crime like murder and rape. Attack the language used to describe the criminals, as opposed to the criminals themselves. Slander critics as racist 4. Ensure their privileges are made irrevocable with city and state sanctuary laws that act as population magnets. Codify permanent status and ensure non-cooperation with ICE 5. Count the non-citizens in the census that will determine congressional apportionment in the House of Representatives. As of now, that would equal 13 extra congressional districts a tremendous amount of electoral power 6. Wage a massive, heavily funded lawfare campaign to change state voting laws that legalize mass mail-in ballots, no signature verification, and no proof of citizenship requirements, making it nearly impossible to prove voter fraud 7. Lock in the permanent voting majority with campaign promises of lavish benefits and permanent privileges, enshrining generational fealty to the Democrat Party 8. Win elections 9. Entrenched single-party rule has been achieved The best part? Your tax dollars are paying for it</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_71c78a73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: incredible. video prompt: Cosmic hums and ethereal whispers. No background music. Ethereal movements...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/60228a5f</link>
      <description>incredible. video prompt: Cosmic hums and ethereal whispers. No background music. Ethereal movements for the figure, physically correct for the human. Slow motion. Volumetric lighting. Bokeh glow. Motion blur on flowing elements. The figure's starry tendrils undulate and shimmer in gentle succession, extending outward rhythmically. The human approaches slowly with lantern swinging, casting flickering reflections. Figure tilts head downward gracefully. Dynamic camerawork with smooth tracking and orbit shot circling the encounter at varying angles. She reaches refracting starlight in waves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_60228a5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: She voted against a grooming gang enquiry</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8555d319</link>
      <description>She voted against a grooming gang enquiry</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8555d319</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Troubling</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/519f75b6</link>
      <description>Troubling</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_519f75b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starship is the gateway to Kardashev civilization.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5612a2a7</link>
      <description>Starship is the gateway to Kardashev civilization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5612a2a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: To be clear, I think we should only waive the filibuster to pass an election integrity act into law,...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c5fea597</link>
      <description>To be clear, I think we should only waive the filibuster to pass an election integrity act into law, but not for any other reason. Election integrity must include visual ID that proves citizenship and in-person voting (except in extreme circumstances like troops overseas).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c5fea597</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Go scroll this thread to see the child rapists, thugs and terrorists that the Trump Admin has been t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0426edaf</link>
      <description>Go scroll this thread to see the child rapists, thugs and terrorists that the Trump Admin has been taking down in Minneapolis. THESE MONSTERS are who the Democrats have been out on the streets defending as they try to STOP law enforcement from doing their jobs. Insane.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0426edaf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: How long &amp; complicated can the deportation process be? Remember this Haitian gang member w/ 17 convi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/69142308</link>
      <description>How long &amp; complicated can the deportation process be? Remember this Haitian gang member w/ 17 convictions who went viral for yelling “Fuck Trump, Biden forever” during my embed with ICE Boston 1 year ago? He’s still in ICE custody in the US. Despite having a deportation order, I’m told he continues to use every legal avenue &amp; appeal to try to avoid deportation. He is currently detained by ICE at a facility in Louisiana. We witnessed him get arrested by ICE in Boston on 1/22/25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_69142308</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Nick Shirley interviews a January 6th political prisoner arrested by Democrats for protesting the st...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/718edc79</link>
      <description>Nick Shirley interviews a January 6th political prisoner arrested by Democrats for protesting the stolen 2020 election He says he was put in solitary confinement for 2 year straight 23 hours a day he was locked in his cell. Sometimes for as long as 36 hours straight….</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_718edc79</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: MS-13 Illegals Just Hacked a 14-Year-Old to Death in Maryland: To the activists and politicians chan...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8a6dca7f</link>
      <description>MS-13 Illegals Just Hacked a 14-Year-Old to Death in Maryland: To the activists and politicians chanting “abolish ICE” — do this one thing: Look the 14-year-old’s mother in the face and say it. Say you don’t support the agency that exists to deport violent criminals before innocent lives are taken. Four illegal aliens connected to MS-13 were arrested in Maryland after allegedly hacking a 14-year-old boy to d*ath with a machete. This isn’t political theory. This isn’t rhetoric. This is a child who will never come home and a mother left to bury her son. This is why we stand with ICE. So violent criminals are removed before they destroy families. So tragedies like this don’t happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8a6dca7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Same person</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a55628b5</link>
      <description>Same person</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a55628b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Don’t let your loved ones use ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1d7a820e</link>
      <description>Don’t let your loved ones use ChatGPT</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1d7a820e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Terrible</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b0264780</link>
      <description>Terrible</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b0264780</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Reality is hard to accept sometimes</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dc9bbf42</link>
      <description>Reality is hard to accept sometimes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dc9bbf42</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Anyone who prevents fraud investigations is in on the fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5e91c89b</link>
      <description>Anyone who prevents fraud investigations is in on the fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5e91c89b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the way</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6504aa05</link>
      <description>This is the way</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6504aa05</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
