<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-05 01:21 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:21:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: He makes a good point. Saying this about any other race would be condemned immediately and should be...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a5b41bc6</link>
      <description>He makes a good point. Saying this about any other race would be condemned immediately and should be. So why is it not incredibly racist and wrong to say this about Whites?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a5b41bc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 23:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Major crime scene</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fd3d4608</link>
      <description>Major crime scene</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fd3d4608</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 23:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 BREAKING: Grok just smashed 60 MILLION monthly active users on mobile in January 2026 +44% downloa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/298a5fde</link>
      <description>🚨 BREAKING: Grok just smashed 60 MILLION monthly active users on mobile in January 2026 +44% downloads MoM → fourth straight month of rocket growth The people's AI is accelerating</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_298a5fde</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Senator Lee is correct</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a2028eff</link>
      <description>Senator Lee is correct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a2028eff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Get awesome Internet anywhere! From remote mountain tops to Antarctica, Starlink is the only fast, l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0754b141</link>
      <description>Get awesome Internet anywhere! From remote mountain tops to Antarctica, Starlink is the only fast, low ping global Internet system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0754b141</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Accurate</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/38c7161e</link>
      <description>Accurate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_38c7161e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok v/s ChatGPT Grok pulls real-time info from current events, while ChatGPT has no clue about real...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f542db81</link>
      <description>Grok v/s ChatGPT Grok pulls real-time info from current events, while ChatGPT has no clue about real-time events. When asked about Billie Eilish's recent Grammys speech, ChatGPT had no clue about her recent speech at all &amp; kept talking about her 2020 speech. Grok is real-time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f542db81</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine rank 1</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/570b39de</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine rank 1</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_570b39de</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Our video generation model dominates the arena 🥇, 50 ELO higher than second place. Try@GrokImagine 1...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/68210e1a</link>
      <description>Our video generation model dominates the arena 🥇, 50 ELO higher than second place. Try@GrokImagine 1.0</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_68210e1a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: New season of Cheeky Pint starts tomorrow! First up:@dwarkesh_spand I sit down with@elonmuskto discu...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/50d981e5</link>
      <description>New season of Cheeky Pint starts tomorrow! First up:@dwarkesh_spand I sit down with@elonmuskto discuss space GPUs and much more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_50d981e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: As of today, Starlink is officially available in Venezuela! They launched with a promotional 50% dis...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ef75bda2</link>
      <description>As of today, Starlink is officially available in Venezuela! They launched with a promotional 50% discount on the residential service plan. You can't order online yet, but you can purchase kits from local approved retailers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ef75bda2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink Wi-Fi review on United Airlines: "If I weren't buckled into a seat, I might not have notice...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a50421ab</link>
      <description>Starlink Wi-Fi review on United Airlines: "If I weren't buckled into a seat, I might not have noticed that I was using in-flight Wi-Fi. When it came to working on my laptop and streaming movies on my phone and tablet, I could have been on my broadband at home. The hardware that makes this happen is a pair of low-profile 500Mbps antennas mounted on the top of the fuselage (pic below). This experience was a demonstration flight on United's first mainline Boeing 737-800 aircraft to be outfitted with the new satellite hardware. Two experiences stood out when I was on the Starlink-equipped plane. First, it operates gate-to-gate, so you can connect on your phone or tablet (laptops still need to be put away during takeoff) as soon as you get settled in your seat. After we'd landed and were taxiing back to the gate, I forgot that I was still connected through Starlink. For almost as long as I've owned a cellphone, wheels-down meant it's time to switch off Airplane mode and embrace the familiar connection of local cellular. Second, the few sign-on steps I had to go through weren't any more onerous than getting on a public cafe or hotel Wi-Fi network. After connecting to the United Wi-FI network, a portal window opened with a trio of screens explaining how great the new service is (you can skip them) and a field to enter my United MileagePlus account and password."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a50421ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: FCC has formally accepted and is now seeking public comments on the major application from@SpaceX! T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/80db045a</link>
      <description>FCC has formally accepted and is now seeking public comments on the major application from@SpaceX! This application is seeking approval of launching a massive new constellation of up to 1 million satellites in low Earth orbit, which would function as orbital data centers. The FCC is now welcoming comments on the application, with a comment deadline around early March 2026. LFG!!! 🚀🚀🚀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_80db045a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk on building a Tesla Terafab: “Well, we make a little fab, and see what happens. Make our m...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1f20d615</link>
      <description>Elon Musk on building a Tesla Terafab: “Well, we make a little fab, and see what happens. Make our mistakes at a small scale, then make a big one.” This is the way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1f20d615</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Important to register your Starlink terminal if in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5b76dcf0</link>
      <description>Important to register your Starlink terminal if in Ukraine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5b76dcf0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Whoever said “money can’t buy happiness” really knew what they were talking about 😔</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1123e681</link>
      <description>Whoever said “money can’t buy happiness” really knew what they were talking about 😔</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1123e681</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: UPDATE: The FCC has accepted SpaceX’s filing for a new non-geostationary orbit (NGSO) system of up t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d0433244</link>
      <description>UPDATE: The FCC has accepted SpaceX’s filing for a new non-geostationary orbit (NGSO) system of up to one million satellites, and is now seeking comments. “This satellite system will represent the first step towards becoming a Kardashev II-level civilization - one that can harness the Sun's full power," according to SpaceX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d0433244</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The FCC welcomes and now seeks comment on the SpaceX application for Orbital Data Centers. The propo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9345645b</link>
      <description>The FCC welcomes and now seeks comment on the SpaceX application for Orbital Data Centers. The proposed system would serve as a first step towards becoming a Kardashev II-level civilization and serve other purposes, according to the applicant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9345645b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Building an interstellar civilizationspacex.com/updates#xai-joins…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c33329b8</link>
      <description>Building an interstellar civilizationspacex.com/updates#xai-joins…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c33329b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
