<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-22 07:29 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Solar power is a really big deal.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ca8d746d</link>
      <description>Solar power is a really big deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ca8d746d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine now 10 seconds with improved video &amp; audio</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f7e673e4</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine now 10 seconds with improved video &amp; audio</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f7e673e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: SpaceX says it is aiming to roll out its second-generation cellular@Starlinksystem in 2027, ac...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5cb1ada9</link>
      <description>NEWS: SpaceX says it is aiming to roll out its second-generation cellular@Starlinksystem in 2027, according to new FCC filing. "SpaceX’s first generation service is providing coverage to over 400 million people, with more than 6 million customers accessing the service each month. But this is only the beginning: SpaceX has also invested in spectrum that will enable it to launch a greatly enhanced second generation direct-to-device system in 2027."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5cb1ada9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Over 2,500 airplanes now have@Starlinkinstalled. Airlines/operators that are currently using or are ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6bc1b8a1</link>
      <description>Over 2,500 airplanes now have@Starlinkinstalled. Airlines/operators that are currently using or are in contract to install Starlink internet on their fleet: • United Airlines • British Airways • Lufthansa Airlines • Emirates • Qatar Airlines • Air France • Hawaiian Airlines • Alaska Airlines • Virgin Atlantic • Air Baltic • Air New Zealand • flydubai • Scandinavian Airlines • WestJet • JSX • ZipAir The 2,500 number includes private planes, business jets and commercial aircraft. SpaceX has a long backlog for aviation installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6bc1b8a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: STARLINK: Today, Prabhakar Jayakumar (@prabhakarpj), SpaceX's Head of Starlink India, and the Govern...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/68ac2d7c</link>
      <description>STARLINK: Today, Prabhakar Jayakumar (@prabhakarpj), SpaceX's Head of Starlink India, and the Government of Goa signed a non-commercial Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to explore Starlink for digital inclusion, smart governance, disaster response, coastal safety, tourism, and public services in remote areas. The agreement, witnessed by Chief Minister Dr Pramod Sawant and IT Minister Rohan Khaunte, includes piloting the service to schools, healthcare facilities, and disaster centers. More news in the EC below!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_68ac2d7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Correct</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c8f33e9d</link>
      <description>Correct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c8f33e9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨🇺🇸 73% OF AMERICANS THINK VOTER ID IS TOTALLY REASONABLE It turns out most people across the board ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b6c11336</link>
      <description>🚨🇺🇸 73% OF AMERICANS THINK VOTER ID IS TOTALLY REASONABLE It turns out most people across the board are totally fine with showing ID to vote. And who said yes? - 73% of all voters, as well as - 70% of Black voters - 69% of Hispanic voters - And even 64% of Democrats are cool with it It proves that this isn’t some fringe idea, as pretty much everyone agrees it’s common sense. At this point, fighting voter ID feels more like arguing just to argue, as most folks already made up their minds, clearly. Source:@Rasmussen_Poll</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b6c11336</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Why are the EU politicians so insistent on Europe committing suicide?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2fd3a7fa</link>
      <description>Why are the EU politicians so insistent on Europe committing suicide?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2fd3a7fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 THE CENSUS LOOPHOLE LETTING POLITICIANS IMPORT CONGRESSIONAL SEATS Here's a math problem that sho...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5b1259ea</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 THE CENSUS LOOPHOLE LETTING POLITICIANS IMPORT CONGRESSIONAL SEATS Here's a math problem that should terrify every American: California gets extra House seats because of people who can't legally vote, while Ohio loses representation because it follows immigration law. The Census counts 11-15 million undocumented immigrants for congressional apportionment, giving sanctuary states bonus political power at everyone else's expense. The mechanics are devastating. States with large undocumented populations get congressional seats and electoral votes, while law-abiding states lose influence. Current estimates show this affects 3-5 House seats, potentially reaching 17 by 2030. Politicians can literally import political power by encouraging illegal immigration. Think about the perverse incentives. Why should a citizen in Indiana have their voice diminished because California ignores federal immigration law? Every undocumented immigrant counted for apportionment dilutes legal citizens' votes everywhere else. We're rewarding lawbreaking with increased political power while punishing law-abiding states with reduced representation. The Founders never imagined cities openly defying federal law to pad census numbers. The solution is simple: count only citizens for congressional apportionment. This is about ensuring representation reflects actual voters, not whoever happens to be physically present. Fix this loophole before the next census makes the distortion permanent. Source:@ArthurMacwaters/ Census Bureau</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5b1259ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The census loophole is a sovereignty issue, not just a math problem. Sanctuary states gaming the sys...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8a68d2e7</link>
      <description>The census loophole is a sovereignty issue, not just a math problem. Sanctuary states gaming the system by counting non-citizens for apportionment undermines the principle of "one person, one vote" for actual taxpayers. H.R.7109 - the Equal Representation Act - fixes this by mandating citizenship verification, ensuring congressional seats reflect legal voters rather than illegal entries. While some studies claim minimal impact, they ignore the compounding effect: every seat gained through demographic manipulation lets politicians redirect billions in federal funds to maintain their power base. California's 2.1 million undocumented residents didn't just "happen" to be there - they're the result of decades of deliberate non-enforcement. The real cost? Law-abiding states lose infrastructure grants, healthcare resources, and political clout. This isn't about partisanship - it's about preventing foreign nationals from dictating America's legislative agenda through proxy representation. Fix the census, restore weight to citizens' votes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8a68d2e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "We wouldn't survive without migrant doctors and nurses!" This list of doctors guilty of professiona...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cb283347</link>
      <description>"We wouldn't survive without migrant doctors and nurses!" This list of doctors guilty of professional misconduct disagrees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cb283347</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Voter ID and in-person voting would save America. Both are essential to stop fraud.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6da5ac4c</link>
      <description>Voter ID and in-person voting would save America. Both are essential to stop fraud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6da5ac4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I’m able to make a whole video with Grok Imagine for 46 seconds</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c40831df</link>
      <description>I’m able to make a whole video with Grok Imagine for 46 seconds</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c40831df</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The reason that all liberal insults fail to land is because everybody can see clearly that they won’...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aa86f5d9</link>
      <description>The reason that all liberal insults fail to land is because everybody can see clearly that they won’t follow those insults to their logical conclusion. So, for example, a liberal will call somebody who very clearly has, like, an 85th percentile IQ a complete fucking moron, but they would never say that about dumb kids in failing schools, who they imagine to be just a few more dollars away from careers as astronauts The liberal will call some morally average working guy a “bad person” but on the other hand the violent degenerate on his 50th arrest just needs our help. In this you can see that it is for them merely a status game and they’re only concerned about status with respect to people who they see as status rivals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aa86f5d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 𝕏 ads have improved significantly and it shows Ads are now more relevant and really useful in day-to...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/09919a65</link>
      <description>𝕏 ads have improved significantly and it shows Ads are now more relevant and really useful in day-to-day life Visual quality is higher, and spammy ads are almost entirely gone Higher-quality, better-designed ads are prioritized, while low-effort, cluttered ads are pushed down Advertisers also have more control where ads appear, how they look, and how they’re presented This is the best time to advertise on 𝕏 for your products if you still haven’t started yet</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_09919a65</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Insurance is half price when Tesla self-driving is activated, because it increases safety so much</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3c80061d</link>
      <description>Insurance is half price when Tesla self-driving is activated, because it increases safety so much</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3c80061d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
