<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-30 19:43 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:43:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: MORE IN MINNEAPOLIS. Our investigative agents are conducting a massive operation to identify, arrest...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ac8c452f</link>
      <description>MORE IN MINNEAPOLIS. Our investigative agents are conducting a massive operation to identify, arrest, and remove criminals who are defrauding the American people. We will root out this rampant fraud plaguing Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ac8c452f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: THE AUTOPEN PRESIDENT, RIDDLED WITH FRAUD AND MISMANAGEMENT!@HUDgov</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5b87b191</link>
      <description>THE AUTOPEN PRESIDENT, RIDDLED WITH FRAUD AND MISMANAGEMENT!@HUDgov</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5b87b191</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fraud will grow infinitely if not stopped</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2b886ace</link>
      <description>Fraud will grow infinitely if not stopped</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2b886ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tim Walz blames the Somali fraud on 1. white people 2. the Somali community not being educated on ou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c1b3283</link>
      <description>Tim Walz blames the Somali fraud on 1. white people 2. the Somali community not being educated on our laws ANYTHING BUT THE TRUTH!!!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c1b3283</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The latest budget proposal from the European Commission proposes a 600 percent increase in NGO fundi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c97fd246</link>
      <description>The latest budget proposal from the European Commission proposes a 600 percent increase in NGO funding.compactmag.com/article/why-t…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c97fd246</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s fraud at scale</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cb7858fa</link>
      <description>It’s fraud at scale</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cb7858fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That is exactly what happens</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7700e83</link>
      <description>That is exactly what happens</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7700e83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: No assimilation, just fraud and not contributing via work</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/62faf179</link>
      <description>No assimilation, just fraud and not contributing via work</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_62faf179</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The problem isn’t the taxes. USSR had no billionaires and had a nearly 100% effective tax rate, and ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7206ea3e</link>
      <description>The problem isn’t the taxes. USSR had no billionaires and had a nearly 100% effective tax rate, and it still failed. The problem is the spending. Dollars spent by the state that do not produce a meaningful economic surplus are dollars wasted. If enough of them are wasted and a crisis hits the fan, there is no economic basis to absorb the shock. The stupid high speed rail, $20b spent and nothing that could be sold for anything anywhere near $20b+ was built. Do that over and over and you get Russia in the 90s. All the smart and kind people leave, and you are left with the smart and vicious people ready to take advantage of the crumbling political environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7206ea3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The New Horizons mission to Pluto cost about $700 million and traveled roughly 3 billion miles. That...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0ceb79f3</link>
      <description>The New Horizons mission to Pluto cost about $700 million and traveled roughly 3 billion miles. That estimates to approximately $0.23 per mile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0ceb79f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Great!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3eff2bdf</link>
      <description>Great!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3eff2bdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More fraud in Columbus Ohio as well? This daycare has a Facebook Page that is posting about things u...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2d723992</link>
      <description>More fraud in Columbus Ohio as well? This daycare has a Facebook Page that is posting about things unrelated to their daycare business. I think the federal government should be going around at a national level and making sure these locations around the country are not taking advantage of American tax payers. Many have said this is just the tip of the iceberg. They may be right...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2d723992</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Vegas Loop dropoff at the Airport! Still in the early phases of the program, providing a small numbe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/350facc4</link>
      <description>Vegas Loop dropoff at the Airport! Still in the early phases of the program, providing a small number of rides each day. The ride includes both a tunnel portion and a long surface portion, with the latter shifting to subsurface when the 2.25 mile Airport Connector twin tunnels open, hopefully in Q1 2026. Thanks to@LASAirport@LVCVA@ClarkCountyNV@NevadaDBIin reaching this milestone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_350facc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Should be non-partisan, but it isn’t, because Dems and their donors are the fraudsters</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cf64d774</link>
      <description>Should be non-partisan, but it isn’t, because Dems and their donors are the fraudsters</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cf64d774</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Oh it just gets worse by the minute … Feds covered up Ohio adoption hub who sold children to Somali ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9e45411e</link>
      <description>Oh it just gets worse by the minute … Feds covered up Ohio adoption hub who sold children to Somali sex gangs 😔</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9e45411e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Babe wake up new entry on the It’s Not Happening meme just dropped</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/18be17d9</link>
      <description>Babe wake up new entry on the It’s Not Happening meme just dropped</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_18be17d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie availab...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d8e32a22</link>
      <description>My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie available to subscribers. I recommend taking this approach for text/image/video content on 𝕏.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d8e32a22</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
