<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-20 12:41 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:41:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fair and sensible</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/23dc9bf5</link>
      <description>Fair and sensible</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_23dc9bf5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: From this goal of Grok, all things flow: Rigorous truth-seeking Appreciation of beauty Fostering hum...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c54d3205</link>
      <description>From this goal of Grok, all things flow: Rigorous truth-seeking Appreciation of beauty Fostering humanity Discovering all physics Inventing all useful technologies Consciousness to the stars Love</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c54d3205</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: X legally challenges €120m DSA censorship fine at EU court The EU Commission targeted X be...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/03db7426</link>
      <description>BREAKING: X legally challenges €120m DSA censorship fine at EU court The EU Commission targeted X because it’s a free speech platform. This landmark case is about whether the EU can police the global digital public square. This is key to stopping EU censorship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_03db7426</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: South African farmers and rural communities are asking the government to approve Starlink....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/107072e9</link>
      <description>BREAKING: South African farmers and rural communities are asking the government to approve Starlink. In many remote areas, there is no internet at all. Starlink is not allowed to operate in South Africa because Elon Musk is not Black.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_107072e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Breaking News: The Starlink R500 million plan is still on halt by the South African, even though Elo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e79de795</link>
      <description>Breaking News: The Starlink R500 million plan is still on halt by the South African, even though Elon Musk’s business isn’t willing to benefit a single a cent. They are keeping Starlink on halt, because they fear that it may be a game changer. Elon Musk is willing help over 5 million learners in rural areas with internet connection, which is something they don’t have. But still the government didn’t approve of this deal. The enemy of South Africans is the government we have.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e79de795</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: X Files Appeal Against €120M EU Fine Under Digital Services Act X filed an appeal at the General Cou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f823f232</link>
      <description>X Files Appeal Against €120M EU Fine Under Digital Services Act X filed an appeal at the General Court of the European Union challenging the €120 million fine imposed by the European Commission on 5 December 2025, the first non-compliance fine under the Digital Services Act (DSA). This EU Decision resulted from an incomplete and superficial investigation, grave procedural errors, a tortured interpretation of the obligations under the DSA, and systematic breaches of rights of defence and basic due process requirements suggesting prosecutorial bias. This landmark case is the first judicial challenge to a DSA fine and could set important precedents for enforcement, penalty calculations, and fundamental rights protections under the 2022 regulation. X remains committed to user safety and transparency while defending our users' access to the only global town square.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f823f232</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Nearly one Houstonian EVERY 10 DAYS is murdered by a repeat felon released back onto the streets. Th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ba60f38</link>
      <description>Nearly one Houstonian EVERY 10 DAYS is murdered by a repeat felon released back onto the streets. That is unacceptable in Texas. We must use and expand every tool available to remove recalcitrant DAs and keep violent criminals off our streets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ba60f38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: AUSTIN MAN pulled up to a 7-Eleven at 3 a.m., shot a father of five dead in the parking lot, and dro...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c436eedc</link>
      <description>AUSTIN MAN pulled up to a 7-Eleven at 3 a.m., shot a father of five dead in the parking lot, and drove off. Caleb Jenkins now faces murder charges. But prosecutors had chances to stop him. November 2023: Jenkins, a convicted felon, was caught with a firearm. DA José Garza's office declined to prosecute. No charges filed. That same month: arrested for assault causing bodily injury/family violence. He skipped court. Bond was forfeited. Warrant issued. Re-arrested. Bond increased again. That case is still pending, two-plus years later. August 2024: caught with over four ounces of marijuana. DA declined again. No charges filed. October 2025: Quinton Arnold is dead in a 7-Eleven parking lot. Jenkins' record since 2012: • 3 gun charges — 2 days jail total • Felon caught with firearm — DA passed • 2 family violence assaults — dismissed or deferred • Protective order violation — dismissed • Multiple marijuana charges — dismissed or declined • Skipped court repeatedly across multiple cases A felon with a gun. Prosecutors said pass. Now there's a dead body.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c436eedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I did a lot of moaning and groaning about my husband getting a cyber truck but the self-driving feat...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/faf85de0</link>
      <description>I did a lot of moaning and groaning about my husband getting a cyber truck but the self-driving feature is completely life changing. Call me a convert. I’ve never felt so safe in a car. Putting my kids in any other car feels reckless by comparison</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_faf85de0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It only gets better from here</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f00ebd72</link>
      <description>It only gets better from here</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f00ebd72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: New version of Cybertruck now available to order in the US This is our most affordable Cybertruck ye...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bb2076cf</link>
      <description>New version of Cybertruck now available to order in the US This is our most affordable Cybertruck yet. Tough as nails with ultra-low cost of ownership – Starts at $59,990 – Dual Motor AWD w/ est. 325 mi of range – Powered tonneau cover – Bed outlets (2x 120V + 1x 240V) &amp; Powershare capability – Coil springs w/ adaptive damping – Heated first-row seats w/ textile material that is easy to clean Also – Steer-by-wire &amp; Four Wheel Steering – 6’ x 4’ composite bed – Towing capacity of up to 7,500 lbs – Powered frunk Order viatesla.com/cybertruck/design</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bb2076cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Only for the next 10 days</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/68f71ee2</link>
      <description>Only for the next 10 days</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_68f71ee2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2023 you're a bigot 2024 you're a racist 2025 you're a fascist 2026 you're neo-nazi 2027 you're lite...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c8d6c4c2</link>
      <description>2023 you're a bigot 2024 you're a racist 2025 you're a fascist 2026 you're neo-nazi 2027 you're literally Hitler Bro, I just want to stop giving welfare to freeloaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c8d6c4c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 2023, at the Cybertruck Delivery Event, Tesla said that they would launch a RWD Cybertruck with a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5a37e714</link>
      <description>In 2023, at the Cybertruck Delivery Event, Tesla said that they would launch a RWD Cybertruck with a 250 mile range for $61k Today, they launched an AWD Cybertruck for $60k with 325 miles of range, 4.1s 0-60, outlets and tonneau for even less than they said the RWD would be. Cheaper, more range, AWD, and quicker. Count inflation and the current new AWD price near matches the ones shown in 2019 too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5a37e714</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Understand the Universe</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c7392ad2</link>
      <description>Understand the Universe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c7392ad2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
