<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-20 06:26 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:26:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Without the SAVE Act, efforts to elect Republicans are a lie</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b58e2baf</link>
      <description>Without the SAVE Act, efforts to elect Republicans are a lie</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b58e2baf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The United States processed 27 million online voter registration applications between 2018 and 2020....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/de139ce6</link>
      <description>The United States processed 27 million online voter registration applications between 2018 and 2020. These 27 million online applications required no proof of citizenship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_de139ce6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Globe Telecom has signed a deal with@Starlinkto launch direct-to-cell satellite connectivity (...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e7e586ee</link>
      <description>NEWS: Globe Telecom has signed a deal with@Starlinkto launch direct-to-cell satellite connectivity (Starlink Mobile) in the Philippines within the next few months. The operator said in a statement it will be the first to offer Starlink’s satellite-to-mobile service in the Philippines and Southeast Asia, and the second in Asia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e7e586ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I just watched a video of a girl who was put on testosterone at 14 talk about her voice changing and...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/991dafd3</link>
      <description>I just watched a video of a girl who was put on testosterone at 14 talk about her voice changing and how no one told her that testosterone doesn’t just lower your voice. It literally thickens the vocal cords, and the female larynx is not built to accommodate that, now it hurts for her to even speak. I had no idea and I wonder how much other crap like this nobody is being told. Putting children on this crap and changing their lives forever should be a crime for both parents and doctors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_991dafd3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thanks for leading the way in the House,@timburchett! We MUST pass the SAVE Act to secure our electi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b05da5f4</link>
      <description>Thanks for leading the way in the House,@timburchett! We MUST pass the SAVE Act to secure our elections and save our country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b05da5f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If we can’t get Republicans to pass the most inoffensive, common-sense bill in history, one that’s s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/da733d36</link>
      <description>If we can’t get Republicans to pass the most inoffensive, common-sense bill in history, one that’s supported by the vast majority of Americans, what use are they? Why should anyone vote for any of them again?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_da733d36</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: 𝕏 has open sourced its For You feed algorithm, the same production system running today an...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0004d8e0</link>
      <description>BREAKING: 𝕏 has open sourced its For You feed algorithm, the same production system running today and powered by Grok from xAI. The full code is live on GitHub and will be refreshed every 4 weeks. Your feed blends posts from accounts you follow with posts discovered across all of 𝕏, then ranks them using a Grok based transformer that predicts how likely you are to like, reply, repost, click, or watch. Instead of one simple score, the model predicts many actions and combines them for a more nuanced ranking. Everything learns directly from user behavior. Intelligence lives inside the model, not scattered pipelines. The system is modular, transparent, and stable, with each post scored independently so results are cacheable and consistent. This is one of the most open looks ever at a large scale social feed ranking system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0004d8e0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: One of the dumbest things ever</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1ae78ad3</link>
      <description>One of the dumbest things ever</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1ae78ad3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 2017, an autistic white kid in Chicago was abducted and tortured by 4 black suspects, livestreame...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e4999588</link>
      <description>In 2017, an autistic white kid in Chicago was abducted and tortured by 4 black suspects, livestreamed online Don Lemon: "I don't think it's evil"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e4999588</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok explained the newly open sourced X algorithm in 10 clear and easy points: 1) When you open the ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e41ad44b</link>
      <description>Grok explained the newly open sourced X algorithm in 10 clear and easy points: 1) When you open the "For You" feed on X, it starts by gathering your personal info, like who you follow and what posts you've liked, replied to, or shared in the past—this helps customize what you see. 2) Next, it collects potential posts from two main places: ones from people you already follow (called in-network) and new discoveries from across all of X (called out-of-network) that might interest you. 3) The in-network posts come from a fast system that stores recent updates from your followed accounts in memory, making it quick to grab without delays. 4) For out-of-network posts, it uses smart AI to compare your interests (based on your history) with all posts on X, picking ones that seem similar or relevant through a matching process. 5) Once it has these candidate posts, it adds extra details to each, like the post's text, images, videos, author's name, and whether they're verified or if it's behind a paywall. 6) Then, it cleans up the list by removing duplicates, old posts, your own stuff, anything from blocked or muted people, keywords you don't like, or things you've already seen. 7) Now, a powerful AI model (based on Grok) looks at your past interactions and predicts how likely you are to like, reply, repost, click, or even dislike each post—giving each a score. 8) It combines these predictions into one final score per post, boosting good actions (like likes) and lowering bad ones (like blocks), while adjusting to mix in variety so one person doesn't dominate your feed. 9) The posts are sorted by these scores, and the top ones are selected to create your feed, ensuring a balanced mix of familiar and new content. 10) Finally, it does one last check to remove any deleted, spammy, violent, or inappropriate posts, then serves up the ranked feed for you to scroll through.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e41ad44b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Throwback to Elon Musk straight-up owning Don Lemon right on The Don Lemon Show😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f836cc13</link>
      <description>Throwback to Elon Musk straight-up owning Don Lemon right on The Don Lemon Show😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f836cc13</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 05:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: MACROHARD and MACROHARDRR from space 🛰️ xAI's powerhouse</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ad85582</link>
      <description>MACROHARD and MACROHARDRR from space 🛰️ xAI's powerhouse</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ad85582</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "In person voting with ID, End of Story." Election integrity starts with voter ID. Without it, democ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/422c6b4d</link>
      <description>"In person voting with ID, End of Story." Election integrity starts with voter ID. Without it, democracy fails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_422c6b4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And the fraudsters always have amazingly good fake sob stories</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0471249f</link>
      <description>And the fraudsters always have amazingly good fake sob stories</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0471249f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They will do this nationally as soon as they gain power and democracy will end</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bad2bcb2</link>
      <description>They will do this nationally as soon as they gain power and democracy will end</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bad2bcb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Literally every Tesla owner while on FSD</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ba885b00</link>
      <description>Literally every Tesla owner while on FSD</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ba885b00</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We know the algorithm is dumb and needs massive improvements, but at least you can see us struggle t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a561919a</link>
      <description>We know the algorithm is dumb and needs massive improvements, but at least you can see us struggle to make it better in real-time and with transparency. No other social media companies do this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a561919a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
