<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-31 23:33 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:33:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2026 is going to be a banger of a year.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c0845268</link>
      <description>2026 is going to be a banger of a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c0845268</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok solves tough problem</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f21aa1f0</link>
      <description>Grok solves tough problem</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f21aa1f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: x.com/i/article/200636226814…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/025849ad</link>
      <description>x.com/i/article/200636226814…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_025849ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Seriously 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ca11d9df</link>
      <description>Seriously 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ca11d9df</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: To meet surging global demand for reliable, high-speed internet, the@SpaceXteam achieved an unpreced...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bd20fdc0</link>
      <description>To meet surging global demand for reliable, high-speed internet, the@SpaceXteam achieved an unprecedented launch cadence in 2025, conducting more than 120 Falcon 9 missions dedicated to expanding the Starlink constellation, adding over 270 Tbps of capacity to the network</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bd20fdc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48bdd30a</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48bdd30a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That would be amazing 🤩</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f01395a2</link>
      <description>That would be amazing 🤩</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f01395a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wait until you learn about the CA homeless industrial complex. It's taxpayer funded money laundering...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6dcb837a</link>
      <description>Wait until you learn about the CA homeless industrial complex. It's taxpayer funded money laundering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6dcb837a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I can't get over this clip. The best writers on SNL could never top this.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9e9a0d50</link>
      <description>I can't get over this clip. The best writers on SNL could never top this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9e9a0d50</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: tbh while i obviously don’t enjoy paying taxes, i wouldn’t mind as much if i could see the value ret...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/693218f1</link>
      <description>tbh while i obviously don’t enjoy paying taxes, i wouldn’t mind as much if i could see the value returned when the value is cities full of homelessness and crime, and widespread fraud, it hits me at a deep, disgusted level</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_693218f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 2023, a transgender terrorist killed three children and three adults at a Christian school in Nas...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/672273e3</link>
      <description>In 2023, a transgender terrorist killed three children and three adults at a Christian school in Nashville. She did it because she hated Christians, hated white people, and was radicalized by gender ideology. Joe Biden’s FBI knew this and deliberately hid it from the public because they wanted to push a false narrative that white people are the biggest terrorist threat to the country. I don’t say this with hyperbole: The Biden admin was a crime perpetrated against the American people. The people who decided to hide this information from us should be in jail— starting with Chris Wray.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_672273e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Outside China, Superchargers delivered more energy than all other fast chargers combined</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/73f27c52</link>
      <description>Outside China, Superchargers delivered more energy than all other fast chargers combined</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_73f27c52</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Nurse 'attacked by Afghan migrant in crowbar rampage' reveals she was 'beaten nearly to death' as sh...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cf3050a0</link>
      <description>Nurse 'attacked by Afghan migrant in crowbar rampage' reveals she was 'beaten nearly to death' as she reveals gruesome injuries inflicted on hertrib.al/RzF2UQK</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cf3050a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Starlink direct to cell now has 6 million monthly customers. Over 400 million people now have ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/309978e9</link>
      <description>NEWS: Starlink direct to cell now has 6 million monthly customers. Over 400 million people now have access to Starlink direct to cell across 22 countries and 6 continents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_309978e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Whether by design or not, replacement is an objective reality. The demographics make that clear.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b696c883</link>
      <description>Whether by design or not, replacement is an objective reality. The demographics make that clear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b696c883</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sweden: 25 year old woman (left) was (allegedly) murdered and dismembered by the (trans) woman (righ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/374ca1b3</link>
      <description>Sweden: 25 year old woman (left) was (allegedly) murdered and dismembered by the (trans) woman (right) last Saturday. His chosen trans name is "Vilma Andersson" (the name of a Swedish 17-year old girl who was also murdered and dismembered). Previously he attempted to kidnap, rape and murder a 10 year old girl. He was given 28 month sentence for this crime.aftonbladet.se/nyheter/a/3pJ…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_374ca1b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine prompt: A highly detailed close-up digital anime-style illustration of a fierce young w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/51b6a8ef</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine prompt: A highly detailed close-up digital anime-style illustration of a fierce young woman with pale skin, sharp golden-yellow eyes gazing intensely to the side, long straight black hair with blunt bangs partially covering one eye, a small black kanji tattoo on her cheek, and a silver lip piercing. She grips a gleaming black katana sword vertically in front of her face with her right hand, black-painted nails visible, the blade engraved with intricate golden Japanese kanji and reflecting dramatic highlights. Her exposed arm and shoulder feature elaborate traditional irezumi tattoos in black ink with yellow and red accents, including demon faces, patterns, and floral elements. She wears a black jacket with yellow abstract designs. The background is a vibrant bright yellow with chaotic black ink splatters, strokes, and abstract lines. High-contrast dramatic lighting with strong metallic sheen on the sword, glossy textures on hair and skin, cyberpunk atmosphere blended with yakuza aesthetics, sharp focus, intricate linework, and vivid color saturation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_51b6a8ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/723dfe9f</link>
      <description>xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try@Grok. Download latest app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_723dfe9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
