<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-26 16:25 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:25:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨💵 BREAKING: SIGNALGATE DONORS LIST AVAILABLE FOR DOWNLOAD; POLITICIANS + FOREIGN LEADERSHIP CONFIRM...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1a85cc24</link>
      <description>🚨💵 BREAKING: SIGNALGATE DONORS LIST AVAILABLE FOR DOWNLOAD; POLITICIANS + FOREIGN LEADERSHIP CONFIRMED? In one of the files revealed by@camhigby, a resources file directs people with money to a website, Stand with Minnesota, which in turns directs donors to a campaign ran by Tending the Soil on Chuffed. More about Tending the Soil later. What to know: the campaign is hosted by Chuffed and the first donation came from Jonny Soppotiuk, a Canada-based community organizer who is part of Chuffed leadership and specializes in fundraising. He is most likely a central figure in raising money. So, yeah. Starting to look like foreigners are playing a key role in all of this. That's not all. I've put together a spreadsheet of 4000+ donors and their possible identities. 👇 Download in the next link below 👇</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1a85cc24</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: People often ask me why I speak publicly about grooming gangs and child sexual exploitation, and why...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/03552710</link>
      <description>People often ask me why I speak publicly about grooming gangs and child sexual exploitation, and why I hold MPs to account regardless of party. This is why. In 1998, my teenage sister was abducted and subjected to hours of rapes and sodomy, he left her for dead. What was done to her changed the course of her life. She lives with severe mental illness and addiction, which are recognised consequences of prolonged childhood sexual trauma. She has received no meaningful, consistent support since the offence occurred. Because of that trauma, her children were removed from her care. I know this intimately, because I fostered two of them. They are my niece and nephews. Our family has lived with the impact of this crime for more than 27 years. The man responsible was convicted of multiple offences involving underage girls. At the time of sentencing, in open court, he shouted that he would come back and sexually assault every woman and child in our family. That threat was made while judgment was being passed. He was given a lengthy prison sentence. Since then, I have been repeatedly drawn back into the justice system through parole reviews. During the pandemic, Humberside Police’s serious crime unit contacted me to inform me he was again being considered for release. I provided a victim impact statement on my sister’s behalf, because she is not well enough to do so herself. What is less often understood is that the harm did not end with my sister. Because of the threats made in court, and further conduct over time, I required legal protection. A non-molestation order and an exclusion zone were put in place to protect me, my children, and other women in our family. I am now also formally recognised as a victim of his actions. After serving over two decades in custody, he was released and then recalled to prison within months for breaching his licence conditions. He is currently back in custody. I am never told the full details. I am simply summoned again, year after year, to repeat the same process. This is not a political position I have adopted. This is not something I have joined late. This is my family’s lived reality. This is why I speak. This is why I refuse silence. This is why safeguarding and accountability matter to me. When I talk about child sexual exploitation, I am not speculating. I am describing a life my family has lived for more than two decades. My position is clear. Life should mean life, I will continue to fight for life without parole for child rapists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_03552710</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: An inside look at what's happening at Starbase</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/87b4e40f</link>
      <description>An inside look at what's happening at Starbase</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_87b4e40f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The grokipedia team is growing here - if you’re excited about truth, come join us</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/686fae9d</link>
      <description>The grokipedia team is growing here - if you’re excited about truth, come join us</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_686fae9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Grok</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fbf95c26</link>
      <description>Try Grok</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fbf95c26</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I mean, the "mom" - who had apparently lost custody of 2/3 of her kids due to neglect or abuse - got...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cfa812f1</link>
      <description>I mean, the "mom" - who had apparently lost custody of 2/3 of her kids due to neglect or abuse - got shot because she was illegally impeding an active arrest, tried to flee the scene, and drove her SUV at a federal agent as part of that. The agent briefly went to the hospital with internal bleeding. The "nurse" got shot because he was "directing traffic" around an active ICE situation, moved over to illegally interfere with it, and grabbed and scuffled with agents - all while armed and with two spare magazines on him. Both of these people were apparently part of a large, illicit underground network that is apparently doing things like illegally recording license plates and addresses and connected with ICE - and flat out dispatching raiders to screw with government arrests. You can view these two shoots as good or not, but the state is not killing people for being "too good, too noble." These were VERY predictable, avoidable situations of violence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cfa812f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/2c72b7759…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bd6de5d2</link>
      <description>Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/2c72b7759…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bd6de5d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 36,500 killed in two days? They're massacring their own civilians. Where are the protesters in the w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c44a765</link>
      <description>36,500 killed in two days? They're massacring their own civilians. Where are the protesters in the west -- the university encampments, the street protests, the UN, Hollywood?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c44a765</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Question for Americans from a dumb Aussie about the Minnesota thing. Obama used ICE to deport approx...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1dd9e849</link>
      <description>Question for Americans from a dumb Aussie about the Minnesota thing. Obama used ICE to deport approx 3M illegals, and got the nickname "Deporter in Chief". And he wasn't even voted in on doing that. There were some protests, but nothing even remotely violet or crazy. Why is now everyone so violet and crazy? Is there any other explanation apart from Orange Man Bad?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1dd9e849</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Enrique Bautista Vasquez is a 20-year-old illegal accused of sexually assaulting a 14-year-old autis...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5f3a0bd5</link>
      <description>Enrique Bautista Vasquez is a 20-year-old illegal accused of sexually assaulting a 14-year-old autistic girl. He allegedly lured her to his Cathedral City apartment on New Year's Eve. Julio Cesar Xocop-Vicente, a criminal illegal alien from Guatemala, killed Amber Paris, a 15-year-old girl and American citizen, after running a stop sign while speeding and striking her with his vehicle. He fled the scene and was arrested the next day, but was released by local authorities, allowing him to walk free on bond before ICE could file an immigration detainer. Worse, local authorities then dismissed his driving-without-a-license charge on December 2, 2025, while Paris was still fighting for her life. This isn't the first time he has been arrested and set free under sanctuary policies. This is who the Democrats are protecting. Who you vote for matters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5f3a0bd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You probably didn't hear about what an illegal did to an 11-year-old little girl in her own bedroom ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/776f563d</link>
      <description>You probably didn't hear about what an illegal did to an 11-year-old little girl in her own bedroom because the media was too busy lying to you about ICE detaining a 5 year old</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_776f563d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The White “liberal” standard for behavior is extremely strict, but is only applied to Whites</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/204f26db</link>
      <description>The White “liberal” standard for behavior is extremely strict, but is only applied to Whites</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_204f26db</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Where are the protests about this?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d5f74661</link>
      <description>Where are the protests about this?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d5f74661</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I remember</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/af261b10</link>
      <description>I remember</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_af261b10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A man was walking his dog in Washington. Some lunatic walked up to him and asked what religion he wa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8cdf1859</link>
      <description>A man was walking his dog in Washington. Some lunatic walked up to him and asked what religion he was. He said Christian and the lunatic stabbed him &amp; his dog who are now both in the hospital. The suspect was kiIIed by police violently resisting arrest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8cdf1859</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “He was unarmed and they killed him anyway!” We said the same thing and you guys laughed.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/247c8a71</link>
      <description>“He was unarmed and they killed him anyway!” We said the same thing and you guys laughed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_247c8a71</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Davos discussion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea7c03ad</link>
      <description>Davos discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea7c03ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
