<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-28 15:35 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:35:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Significant net negative</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/00ee3708</link>
      <description>Significant net negative</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_00ee3708</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Someone should write an alternate historical novel where Americans are the first to master the autom...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7490fd83</link>
      <description>Someone should write an alternate historical novel where Americans are the first to master the automobile, the first in flight, the first to harness the atom, the first to land on the moon — but just keep going and never open our borders to the entire third world for sixty years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7490fd83</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 SOMALI BALLOT HARVESTING EXPOSÉ IN MINNESOTA WAS SUPPRESSED... THEN THE FRAUD EXPLODED In Septemb...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f08b7377</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 SOMALI BALLOT HARVESTING EXPOSÉ IN MINNESOTA WAS SUPPRESSED... THEN THE FRAUD EXPLODED In September 2020, James O'Keefe's Project Veritas dropped undercover footage alleging a massive ballot-harvesting racket in Ilhan Omar's Minneapolis district. Paid operatives illegally scooped absentee ballots from elderly Somali immigrants, stuffing envelopes and even bragging on Snapchat about hauling 300 for City Council hopeful Jamal Osman. Whistleblower Omar Jamal spilled that it was an "open secret," with Omar's crew like staffer Ali Gainey coordinating the cash-fueled scheme, exploiting vulnerable folks for DFL power plays. But media "fact-checkers" swarmed, branding it racist kryptonite without debunking evidence, cops claimed no proof, and the story vanished like the Hunter laptop weeks later. NY Post's Miranda Devine got hammered for covering it, yet fraud festered: Fast-forward to 2025, and Minnesota's drowning in $9B+ Somali-linked scams from Feeding Our Future to Medicaid ghost services, same MO of milking taxpayer programs for riches and votes. Why does it keep happening? Incentives galore, lax election laws, unchecked welfare flows, and bloc voting power keep the cycle spinning for crooks and pols. Govt needs to gut 'em: Enforce strict voter ID, audit programs ruthlessly, tie aid to citizenship/residency checks, and deport fraudsters. Slash the rewards, kill the motivation, or watch the "3rd world" playbook swallow more states. Source: NY Post (2020), CBS News, FOX9,@mirandadevine,@JamesOKeefeIII</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f08b7377</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The prospect of a state income tax on millionaires has already got some of the state's richer reside...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dc4d1078</link>
      <description>The prospect of a state income tax on millionaires has already got some of the state's richer residents talking about leaving. History says it's mostly just talk.st.news/49a3A39</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dc4d1078</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Mass migration from the third world is a pro-rape policy.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/465155f3</link>
      <description>Mass migration from the third world is a pro-rape policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_465155f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Any elected official that puts foreigners before their citizens is committing treason against their ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9a1d2cf8</link>
      <description>Any elected official that puts foreigners before their citizens is committing treason against their country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9a1d2cf8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Racist” is just a magic spell to make you stop objecting to the surrender of your nations. Luckily ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dcd3eb80</link>
      <description>“Racist” is just a magic spell to make you stop objecting to the surrender of your nations. Luckily some of its wielders, like this guy, are clumsy enough to make this obvious, even to normies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dcd3eb80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cool@Starlink</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a1fe3fd7</link>
      <description>Cool@Starlink</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a1fe3fd7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: As I was saying …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/11ac5e37</link>
      <description>As I was saying …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_11ac5e37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Awesome</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/feda012d</link>
      <description>Awesome</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_feda012d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Worth reading this bombshell report from@CBSNewsabout the Somali fraud rings in Minnesota.👇 “The doc...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4293152c</link>
      <description>Worth reading this bombshell report from@CBSNewsabout the Somali fraud rings in Minnesota.👇 “The documents feature exhibits from a recent federal trial, many of which are being made public by CBS News for the first time. The exhibits include: -A confirmation email for a stay in an overwater villa with a private pool at Radisson Blu Resort Maldives -Lakefront property in Minnesota -Receipts showing wire transfers to China and East Africa -First class tickets to Istanbul and Amsterdam -A 2021 Porsche Macan -Stacks of cash, texted between defendants”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4293152c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "You are gonna be the richest 25 year old InshaAllah."@CBSNewsobtained dozens of documents that reve...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1a026999</link>
      <description>"You are gonna be the richest 25 year old InshaAllah."@CBSNewsobtained dozens of documents that reveal how Minnesota fraudsters spent hundreds of millions in taxpayer dollars on luxury cars, villas and overseas wire transfers . . . including to China.cbsnews.com/news/minnesota-f…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1a026999</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Don't worry guys. I'm certain there's no childcare fraud at all in Utah.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c75022a</link>
      <description>Don't worry guys. I'm certain there's no childcare fraud at all in Utah.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c75022a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Industrial scale fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b94856dd</link>
      <description>Industrial scale fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b94856dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What they actually want is to imprison and bankrupt those they disagree with</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d3bef752</link>
      <description>What they actually want is to imprison and bankrupt those they disagree with</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d3bef752</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Traitor” Tim Walz</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/df17ba24</link>
      <description>“Traitor” Tim Walz</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_df17ba24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7b28166</link>
      <description>The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain vast numbers of illegal (and legal, in some cases) immigrants to win elections and turn America into a single-party state, destroying any real democracy. The more you look at it, the more you will be horrified at what your tax money is doing and the fact that, if this is not reversed, your vote will mean nothing. The most obvious case example is the Somali voting bloc in Minnesota, a state that historically had zero Somalis, electing Ilhan Omar to the US Congress. The same is happening in Europe, UK, Canada, Australia and New Zealand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7b28166</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
