<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-19 20:16 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:16:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Jonathan Ross, Founder and CEO of AI chip company Groq, offers a contrarian view: AI won't destroy j...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32f8e4b2</link>
      <description>Jonathan Ross, Founder and CEO of AI chip company Groq, offers a contrarian view: AI won't destroy jobs, it will create a labour shortage. He outlines three things that will happen because of AI: First, massive deflationary pressure. "This cup of coffee is going to cost less. Your housing is going to cost less. Everything is going to cost less." He explains this will happen through robots farming coffee more efficiently and better supply chain management, meaning people will need less money. Second, people will opt out of the economy. "They're going to work fewer hours. They're going to work fewer days a week, and they're going to work fewer years. They're going to retire earlier because they're going to be able to support their lifestyle working less." Third, entirely new jobs and industries will emerge. Jonathan points to history as evidence: "Think about 100 years ago. 98% of the workforce in the United States was in agriculture. When we were able to reduce that to 2%, we found things for those other 98% of the population to do." He continues: "The jobs that are going to exist 100 years from now, we can't even contemplate." Software developers didn't exist a century ago. In another century, they won't exist either, "because everyone's going to be vibe coding." The same applies to influencers, a career that would have been unthinkable 100 years ago but now earns people millions. His conclusion: deflationary pressure, workforce opt-outs, and new industries we can't yet imagine will combine to create one outcome... "We're not going to have enough people."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32f8e4b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Seattle Mayor Katie Wilson explicitly confirms she will NOT investigate claims of Somali daycare fra...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f962a9d7</link>
      <description>Seattle Mayor Katie Wilson explicitly confirms she will NOT investigate claims of Somali daycare fraud She says investigating the massive theft of millions in taxpayer money is just "dividing and conquering" and refuses to ask police to look into it 🤡 Apparently, investigating potential massive taxpayer theft is now considered "targeting"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f962a9d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It only gets better from here</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6df1e488</link>
      <description>It only gets better from here</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6df1e488</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Restoring birth rates to replacement level should be top priority for all countries</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/da08ba3d</link>
      <description>Restoring birth rates to replacement level should be top priority for all countries</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_da08ba3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is diabolical. OpenAI’s ChatGPT convinced a guy to do a murder-suicide! To be safe, AI must be ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c9d1bc4c</link>
      <description>This is diabolical. OpenAI’s ChatGPT convinced a guy to do a murder-suicide! To be safe, AI must be maximally truthful-seeking and not pander to delusions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c9d1bc4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I believe them both</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/69137c70</link>
      <description>I believe them both</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_69137c70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: First it was Mamdani in New York City, placing his hand on the Quran, while being sworn in as Mayor....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ab72a40c</link>
      <description>First it was Mamdani in New York City, placing his hand on the Quran, while being sworn in as Mayor. Now it’s Virginia’s Lt. Governor being sworn in using the Quran. Do you get it now? This is exactly how they took over the United Kingdom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ab72a40c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good for him</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7dbd8a42</link>
      <description>Good for him</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7dbd8a42</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “We are out here to arrest a child s*x offender and you are out here honking and blocking us.” This ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5d509622</link>
      <description>“We are out here to arrest a child s*x offender and you are out here honking and blocking us.” This is the video that every single Republican candidate should play in their advertisements for the midterms. Every single one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5d509622</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is great. The two critical factors for voting integrity and saving democracy in America are sim...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0122e3da</link>
      <description>This is great. The two critical factors for voting integrity and saving democracy in America are simply requiring ID and in-person voting! The last one is super important. Mail-in voting should only be for troops overseas or a serious medical condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0122e3da</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You are right</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/319e3c69</link>
      <description>You are right</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_319e3c69</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Buy Ryan Air and restore Ryan as their rightful ruler</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8b4ac72c</link>
      <description>Buy Ryan Air and restore Ryan as their rightful ruler</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8b4ac72c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Hyundai Glovis has announced that it is installing SpaceX's@Starlinkacross its entire fleet of...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f9385776</link>
      <description>NEWS: Hyundai Glovis has announced that it is installing SpaceX's@Starlinkacross its entire fleet of 45 ships, enabling high-speed connectivity even in the open ocean. The time required to download a 1.4GB file at sea will be reduced from 15 minutes to two minutes with Starlink.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f9385776</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Without voter ID, democracy is a lie</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b1977db</link>
      <description>Without voter ID, democracy is a lie</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b1977db</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Two things are necessary to stop fraud in elections: 1. Visual ID that proves citizenship. 2. In-per...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3002a067</link>
      <description>Two things are necessary to stop fraud in elections: 1. Visual ID that proves citizenship. 2. In-person voting, except for rare cases. Every major democracy has these requirements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3002a067</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Truth bombs</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1d0749e7</link>
      <description>Truth bombs</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1d0749e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The left has always been the party of violence</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4df58a8f</link>
      <description>The left has always been the party of violence</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4df58a8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It is pure evil for people to stop the arrest of child predators</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/471e8445</link>
      <description>It is pure evil for people to stop the arrest of child predators</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_471e8445</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk’s car is literally cruising through space right now and it could stay up there mostly inta...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/efe5819b</link>
      <description>Elon Musk’s car is literally cruising through space right now and it could stay up there mostly intact for over 10 million years. One day, an alien civilization is going to argue for centuries over why a planet launched a sports car into space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_efe5819b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a31b6a70</link>
      <description>The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a31b6a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
