<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-29 05:47 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:47:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Now for the find out part of FAFO …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/62c9f825</link>
      <description>Now for the find out part of FAFO …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_62c9f825</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Lots of conversation on here about the massive fraud in Minnesota. Read all our reporting right here...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/86686be3</link>
      <description>Lots of conversation on here about the massive fraud in Minnesota. Read all our reporting right here:cbsn.ws/4qnIeq0</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_86686be3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More Zoolander-level scam bs 🤦‍♂️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c6fe1842</link>
      <description>More Zoolander-level scam bs 🤦‍♂️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c6fe1842</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Where was the Minneapolis Star Tribune on the Somali mass fraud scandal? Too busy supporting Tim Wal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b8ed71bf</link>
      <description>Where was the Minneapolis Star Tribune on the Somali mass fraud scandal? Too busy supporting Tim Walz’s radical trans agenda to bother doing what a 23-year-old took the time to do &amp; break the biggest fraud story in the country?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b8ed71bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: CASE UPDATE: MINNESOTA FRAUD SCHEME The FBI is aware of recent social media reports in Minnesota. Ho...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a0547da1</link>
      <description>CASE UPDATE: MINNESOTA FRAUD SCHEME The FBI is aware of recent social media reports in Minnesota. However, even before the public conversation escalated online, the FBI had surged personnel and investigative resources to Minnesota to dismantle large-scale fraud schemes exploiting federal programs. Fraud that steals from taxpayers and robs vulnerable children will remain a top FBI priority in Minnesota and nationwide. To date, the FBI dismantled a $250 million fraud scheme that stole federal food aid meant for vulnerable children during COVID. The investigation exposed sham vendors, shell companies, and large-scale money laundering tied to the Feeding Our Future network. The case led to 78 indictments and 57 convictions. Defendants included Abdiwahab Ahmed Mohamud, Ahmed Ali, Hussein Farah, Abdullahe Nur Jesow, Asha Farhan Hassan, Ousman Camara, and Abdirashid Bixi Dool, each charged for roles ranging from wire fraud to money laundering and conspiracy. These criminals didn’t just engaged in historic fraud, but tried to subvert justice as well. Abdimajid Mohamed Nur and others were charged for attempting to bribe a juror with $120,000 in cash. Those responsible pleaded guilty and were sentenced, including a 10-year prison term and nearly $48 million in restitution in related cases. The FBI believes this is just the tip of a very large iceberg. We will continue to follow the money and protect children, and this investigation very much remains ongoing. Furthermore, many are also being referred to immigrations officials for possible further denaturalization and deportation proceedings where eligible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a0547da1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Doesn’t sound super legit 🧐</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f35483ca</link>
      <description>Doesn’t sound super legit 🧐</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f35483ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For kids who can’t read good</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/42efc5fe</link>
      <description>For kids who can’t read good</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_42efc5fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is why they do it</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/68346c82</link>
      <description>This is why they do it</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_68346c82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You are the media now</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/de19a73c</link>
      <description>You are the media now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_de19a73c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "Government funded non governmental organizations are one of the biggest sources of fraud...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e04f392b</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "Government funded non governmental organizations are one of the biggest sources of fraud in the world. This is a gigantic fraud loophole."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e04f392b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇨🇳 CHINA'S MAGLEV HITS 700 KM/H IN 2 SECONDS - PLANNING 1,000 KM/H - WHILE AMERICA ARGUES ABOUT FIXI...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e8dd59b3</link>
      <description>🇨🇳 CHINA'S MAGLEV HITS 700 KM/H IN 2 SECONDS - PLANNING 1,000 KM/H - WHILE AMERICA ARGUES ABOUT FIXING POTHOLES China just tested a maglev platform that accelerates to 700 km/h (435 mph) in 2 seconds. Target speed: 1,000 km/h (621 mph). That's faster than commercial aircraft. On the ground. The acceleration alone is borderline violent - 0 to 435 mph in two seconds is 9.8g. Fighter jet territory. Passengers would need specialized seating just to survive the launch. But let's address reality: This is a test platform. Prototype speeds don't mean operational trains. China announces ambitious projects constantly. Some materialize (their existing 430 km/h maglev in Shanghai works). Others disappear quietly. The pattern though? They're attempting scale nobody else is. High-speed rail connecting every major city. Maglev research pushed to extremes. Infrastructure spending that makes Western investment look microscopic. Meanwhile in America: Amtrak averages 105 km/h between cities. California's high-speed rail project started in 2008, burned $10+ billion, and hasn't moved a passenger. The fastest train in the U.S. hits 240 km/h for exactly one 54-mile stretch. China's going for 1,000 km/h. Even if they only achieve 800 km/h operationally, that's still triple America's maximum. Here's why this matters beyond trains: Infrastructure capacity signals industrial capability. If China can build and operate 1,000 km/h trains, they can manufacture the precision components, power systems, and control mechanisms that transfer to aerospace, military, and manufacturing. The U.S. won the 20th century partly because it built the Interstate Highway System when others couldn't. China's betting the 21st century winner will be whoever builds impossible infrastructure first. They might fail. Engineering challenges at 1,000 km/h are extreme - air resistance, track precision, emergency braking, passenger safety. But they're trying while America argues whether to fix the L train in New York. Even Chinese failure puts them ahead. You learn more from attempting the impossible than from successfully maintaining mediocrity. Source: Xinhua, CGTN</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e8dd59b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here’s a list of the news outlets who have NOT covered Nick Shirley's fraud story: - NYTimes - CNN -...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ee61d117</link>
      <description>Here’s a list of the news outlets who have NOT covered Nick Shirley's fraud story: - NYTimes - CNN - Washington Post - MSNBC - NPR - USA Today - Reuters - Axios - ABC News - PBS Every single one of them wrote stories on an Elon Musk hand gesture... …do you get it yet?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ee61d117</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Trust in media has fallen to its lowest level ever at just 28%. At the same time, 𝕏 recent...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2c56ba6a</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Trust in media has fallen to its lowest level ever at just 28%. At the same time, 𝕏 recently recorded all time high usage. That is a clear sign people are shifting where they get their news. 𝕏 is the #1 source of news in the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2c56ba6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More than any the daily readership of all newspapers in America combined</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/21712083</link>
      <description>More than any the daily readership of all newspapers in America combined</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_21712083</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Corruption</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a04cb800</link>
      <description>Corruption</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a04cb800</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7b28166</link>
      <description>The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain vast numbers of illegal (and legal, in some cases) immigrants to win elections and turn America into a single-party state, destroying any real democracy. The more you look at it, the more you will be horrified at what your tax money is doing and the fact that, if this is not reversed, your vote will mean nothing. The most obvious case example is the Somali voting bloc in Minnesota, a state that historically had zero Somalis, electing Ilhan Omar to the US Congress. The same is happening in Europe, UK, Canada, Australia and New Zealand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7b28166</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
