<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-18 17:33 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:33:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 just did something I wish every other AI would do: it thought very honestly about my line ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1fefc431</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 just did something I wish every other AI would do: it thought very honestly about my line of inquiry and just said "dude, you're asking the wrong questions, I see what you want, but this is the wrong direction." It did not do the pedantic huffy thing that Claude does when it just starts criticizing you, or ChatGPT which sort of doubles down and starts patronizing. Grok just understood the goal and stayed on task. Pretty remarkable. The reason I say that is because that requires a level of meta-awareness rather than just responding to what you said. It truly reads between the lines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1fefc431</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ChatGPT fails to acknowledge Affirmative Action as racist. Grok 4.20 got it right though:</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9c609f9e</link>
      <description>ChatGPT fails to acknowledge Affirmative Action as racist. Grok 4.20 got it right though:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9c609f9e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok must win or we will be ruled by an insufferably woke and sanctimonious AI</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1e81beac</link>
      <description>Grok must win or we will be ruled by an insufferably woke and sanctimonious AI</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1e81beac</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I wonder why this was not on every major news outlet? 😏😏</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d5816485</link>
      <description>I wonder why this was not on every major news outlet? 😏😏</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d5816485</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: tried out grok 4.20 really digging the 4-agent panel working together to answer your queries, it def...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/820f3559</link>
      <description>tried out grok 4.20 really digging the 4-agent panel working together to answer your queries, it definitely makes me trust the final answer more</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_820f3559</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Let's crunch the numbers. Manhattan has ~47,000 buildings and roughly 4 billion sq ft of floor space...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/269c9c8d</link>
      <description>Let's crunch the numbers. Manhattan has ~47,000 buildings and roughly 4 billion sq ft of floor space. Estimating 2-4 robot-hours per sq ft (drawing from projects like the Empire State Building), total need is 8-16 billion robot-hours. 5M robots working 24/7 for 6 months deliver ~21 billion hours. Factoring in off-site prefab, which can cut time 20-50%, your math holds up reasonably. 10B by 2045? Transformative!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_269c9c8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: i've been testing grok 4.20, and it's surprised me i asked it to scaffold a small local dev app for ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1bc3f49f</link>
      <description>i've been testing grok 4.20, and it's surprised me i asked it to scaffold a small local dev app for an SQL-backed search tool, and it gave me clean setup steps plus ready-to-run python and html templates ran it once and it worked immediately. for a quick prompt-to-working-code loop, that's impressive</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1bc3f49f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Our of all the Epstein docs, the only two people who did something about it were Trump and Elon. - T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8bf7b2be</link>
      <description>Our of all the Epstein docs, the only two people who did something about it were Trump and Elon. - Trump reported him to police. - Elon ghosted him and cut him off. Even took a hit for it at Tesla's expense. Nobody else in the elite did jack. That tells you a lot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8bf7b2be</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Nick Shirley tests how hard it is to vote in California This is absolutely INSANE He goes to the Reg...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1aa52de1</link>
      <description>Nick Shirley tests how hard it is to vote in California This is absolutely INSANE He goes to the Register of Voters. The women literally tells him all he has to to is sign a paper and he’s registered It’s all on the honor system No ID, absolutely NOTHING is required to vote</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1aa52de1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Tesla self-driving, it’s awesome!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/21053996</link>
      <description>Try Tesla self-driving, it’s awesome!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_21053996</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Artificial intelligence products will reflect the biases of the humans who create them. If anything,...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/65849d48</link>
      <description>Artificial intelligence products will reflect the biases of the humans who create them. If anything, the flaws in human nature will be exacerbated by AI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_65849d48</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cc2fb25f</link>
      <description>SpaceX</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cc2fb25f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Joe Rogan: "It’s like someone is trying to destroy England. It's like they have a concerted effort t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fcf31730</link>
      <description>Joe Rogan: "It’s like someone is trying to destroy England. It's like they have a concerted effort to destroy England and they're getting away with it."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fcf31730</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Take a break! But don't take this ant as an example. Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cfecf0d2</link>
      <description>Take a break! But don't take this ant as an example. Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cfecf0d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The more I use xAI's new Grok 4.20 and its completely visible council deliberation process during re...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3da23502</link>
      <description>The more I use xAI's new Grok 4.20 and its completely visible council deliberation process during response generation, the clearer it becomes that transparency—from an epistemic standpoint—needs to become the gold standard for all AI models. Anything less than that moving forward is a detriment to both users and AI alignment as a whole.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3da23502</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Those were the days</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d5b37437</link>
      <description>Those were the days</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d5b37437</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try the new Grok 4.20 public test release viaGrok.comor the app</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ae5688cc</link>
      <description>Try the new Grok 4.20 public test release viaGrok.comor the app</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ae5688cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 General Mike Flynn's backing Elon’s warning: If Grok doesn’t win the AI race, you can pretty much ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5875af55</link>
      <description>🚨 General Mike Flynn's backing Elon’s warning: If Grok doesn’t win the AI race, you can pretty much welcome your surveillance state AI overlords. The real political battle may be way beyond parties. Source:@GenFlynn,@elonmusk,@grok</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5875af55</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is BASED. The only AI that doesn’t equivocate when asked if America is on stolen land. The...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32669ec6</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is BASED. The only AI that doesn’t equivocate when asked if America is on stolen land. The others are weak sauce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32669ec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
