<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-30 07:57 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:57:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Grok ✨</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8bda1968</link>
      <description>Try Grok ✨</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8bda1968</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine✨️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa08edd9</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine✨️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa08edd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good morning my friends. I want to take a moment to tell you how much I appreciate each one of you. ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1a5f4bcd</link>
      <description>Good morning my friends. I want to take a moment to tell you how much I appreciate each one of you. Hope you enjoy my first 10 sec Grok video. 💕#Tuesday_Vibes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1a5f4bcd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And rapid improvements coming every week</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ba2add75</link>
      <description>And rapid improvements coming every week</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ba2add75</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: X announces partnership with Warner Bros Discovery for the 2026 Winter Olympics in Milano Cort...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d8ba5831</link>
      <description>NEWS: X announces partnership with Warner Bros Discovery for the 2026 Winter Olympics in Milano Cortina. The deal brings exclusive Olympics content to X users in Europe and the UK, with brands getting access to in-game clips via X's Amplify offering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d8ba5831</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Amazing and typical chart. The entire argument for mass migration, of course, rests on the assumptio...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ae48e138</link>
      <description>Amazing and typical chart. The entire argument for mass migration, of course, rests on the assumption that all or most migrants WILL positively contribute to society. But, this....isn't true.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ae48e138</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sebastian Gomez-Pena, who is paralysed from the neck down, is one of the first people in the UK to r...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7c20b297</link>
      <description>Sebastian Gomez-Pena, who is paralysed from the neck down, is one of the first people in the UK to receive Elon Musk’s brain chip. "It's magical," he tells Sky's@t0mclark3, "it's cool to see that when I think about moving my hand something actually happens."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7c20b297</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Elon Musk has just confirmed that Grok Imagine is now generating more images &amp; videos than...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a2c4c8f2</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Elon Musk has just confirmed that Grok Imagine is now generating more images &amp; videos than everyone else combined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a2c4c8f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: House Republicans just introduced the “Make Elections Great Again” Act. The MEGA Act would...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e93d9203</link>
      <description>BREAKING: House Republicans just introduced the “Make Elections Great Again” Act. The MEGA Act would: - Require photo ID to vote - Require citizenship verification to register to vote - Require states use paper ballots for federal elections - Voter roll maintenance requirements - Requires mail in ballots be received on election day - Bans ballot harvesting - Bans ranked choice voting - Bans Universal vote by mail - Bans partisan voter initiatives</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e93d9203</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX is now providing precise positional awareness of objects in Earth orbit to all satellite oper...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fcf3ea03</link>
      <description>SpaceX is now providing precise positional awareness of objects in Earth orbit to all satellite operators for free. This will greatly reduce the probability of collisions that create orbital debris (space junk) hazards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fcf3ea03</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Reminds me of this classic meme 😂 Use 𝕏 Chat instead of WhatsApp! There will never be “hooks for adv...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ea0f0a6</link>
      <description>Reminds me of this classic meme 😂 Use 𝕏 Chat instead of WhatsApp! There will never be “hooks for advertising” in 𝕏 Chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ea0f0a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Proud of the groundbreaking work the@starlinkteam is doing to advance space safety. With Stargaze, w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/da7dd451</link>
      <description>Proud of the groundbreaking work the@starlinkteam is doing to advance space safety. With Stargaze, we have the beginnings of the space traffic system needed to ensure safe satellite operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_da7dd451</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thanks to our 1M subscribers in Brazil,@Starlink’s second largest customer base! Starlink now accept...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ac868a8</link>
      <description>Thanks to our 1M subscribers in Brazil,@Starlink’s second largest customer base! Starlink now accepts Pix instant payments and has unlocked sold out regions in all of Brazil.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ac868a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You can now see all the trending news of 𝕏 right on your homescreen. Add the 𝕏 News widget to your p...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ab22b268</link>
      <description>You can now see all the trending news of 𝕏 right on your homescreen. Add the 𝕏 News widget to your phone. Stay up to date with breaking news, big conversations, and viral moments as they happen around the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ab22b268</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just a reminder that Reid Hoffman really did say in a public forum that he wished President Trump ha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8bfdca28</link>
      <description>Just a reminder that Reid Hoffman really did say in a public forum that he wished President Trump had been killed in the assassination attempt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8bfdca28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Man Outed As Nazi For Saying We Should Have Laws And Bordersbuff.ly/Zk3XLoC</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8b9319d9</link>
      <description>Man Outed As Nazi For Saying We Should Have Laws And Bordersbuff.ly/Zk3XLoC</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8b9319d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: New Tesla Solar Panel &amp; Tesla Panel Mount now available Solar Panel – 420W – Uses same cascading cel...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f0a8fa0f</link>
      <description>New Tesla Solar Panel &amp; Tesla Panel Mount now available Solar Panel – 420W – Uses same cascading cell technology as our Solar Roof cells to create 18 power zones (3x more than conventional panels). This reduces energy loss in shaded conditions &amp; produces more energy Panel Mount – 33% faster installation by using a groove-based frame system for streamlined assembly (eliminating traditional rails &amp; clamps) – Up to 15% fewer roof penetrations while preserving structural integrity &amp; lowering costs – Low-profile finish that is universally compatible with shingle, tile, metal &amp; flat roofs</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f0a8fa0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: Starlink is going to do a tremendous amount of good “Starlink is good in and of itself. T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c25fbc6b</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: Starlink is going to do a tremendous amount of good “Starlink is good in and of itself. The Starlink system provides low-cost, high-bandwidth connectivity anywhere in the world. It's the first truly global Internet system. And I think it's helping a lot of people around the world who either don't have access to connectivity, or it's too expensive. You know, once you have access to the Internet, you can learn anything. You can sell your products and services to the rest of the world. So, I think Starlink actually is going to do a tremendous amount of good in lifting people out of poverty and helping them.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c25fbc6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: With the release of version 1.0, Grok Imagine is now generating more images &amp; videos than everyone e...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/459eb0c6</link>
      <description>With the release of version 1.0, Grok Imagine is now generating more images &amp; videos than everyone else combined!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_459eb0c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 07:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
