<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-11 17:55 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:55:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Despite 30 knot winds at the Allan Hills, Antarctica, where ice cores up to 2,700,000 years old have...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2a1a7745</link>
      <description>Despite 30 knot winds at the Allan Hills, Antarctica, where ice cores up to 2,700,000 years old have been found,@SpaceXStarlink continues to give the@NSF-supported COLDEX team unprecedented connectivity!@blueicehiggins@icy_pete</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2a1a7745</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 Epstein’s associate Al Seckel hacking Wikipedia to replace his mug shot, scrub the "sex offender"...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4ffac9a9</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 Epstein’s associate Al Seckel hacking Wikipedia to replace his mug shot, scrub the "sex offender" label, and rebrand him as "businessman, philanthropist." They even recorded the IPs of anyone who tried to edit it back and blocked them out. And people still trust Wikipedia as a source. File number: EFTA02416819</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4ffac9a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is why European nations just hanged these criminals: getting rid of them works Over the course ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e14556ea</link>
      <description>This is why European nations just hanged these criminals: getting rid of them works Over the course of roughly the 15th to mid-18th centuries, about 1% of each generation in Europe was executed, with states getting serious about solving violent crime and using the gallows to solve it Over 200 crimes, most of them theft-related, were capital crimes. Year after year, the criminal class faced the gallows, and year after year those sentences were carried out It worked. After a few centuries of work, the crime genes had essentially been plucked out of the gene pool, and there just wasn't that much serious crime anymore; by the end of the 18th century, the homicide rate had fallen from over 40 per 100,000--higher than even most of America's notoriously violent cities--to less than 1 per 100k population, far safer than most modern nations. Doing something similar, even if just life imprisonment, would work similarly well now. Just taking the lawbreakers off the streets for good and preventing them from propagating their genes, however that's done, fixes the crime problem We ought learn from our ancestors, and do as they would do</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e14556ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨🇬🇧 UK government accused of having plans to delete records about grooming gangs. Solving problems? ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/35d9daaf</link>
      <description>🚨🇬🇧 UK government accused of having plans to delete records about grooming gangs. Solving problems? Better erase the records! Source:@Katie_Lam_MP</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_35d9daaf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The worst Epstein document I've seen. A little girl said Jesus makes her feel safe so they dressed u...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c2b79130</link>
      <description>The worst Epstein document I've seen. A little girl said Jesus makes her feel safe so they dressed up as Jesus as they raped &amp; murdered her. The level of evil we're dealing with here is incomprehensible. Every single name must be revealed and justice must be served.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c2b79130</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Irish will become a minority in Ireland because Irish men are afraid of being called racist and ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5b02db6d</link>
      <description>The Irish will become a minority in Ireland because Irish men are afraid of being called racist and upsetting people from the 3rd world. What a pathetic way for an ancient civilization like Ireland to disappear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5b02db6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: There will be a reckoning</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bd05eaf9</link>
      <description>There will be a reckoning</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bd05eaf9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI opened a new engineering office in Bellevue, Washington at Lincoln Square South</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5ece16c6</link>
      <description>xAI opened a new engineering office in Bellevue, Washington at Lincoln Square South</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5ece16c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We are literally paying foreigners to rape British women. Abolish asylum. Blanket reject all applica...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/02c2ce03</link>
      <description>We are literally paying foreigners to rape British women. Abolish asylum. Blanket reject all applications. Deport every single last one of them. I don't care about the Refugee Convention. What are they going to do, send an UN army to rape more women?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_02c2ce03</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For those fools/liars who say it is racist to require ID to vote (it obviously is not), why do major...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7e9659c2</link>
      <description>For those fools/liars who say it is racist to require ID to vote (it obviously is not), why do majority Black countries require ID to vote?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7e9659c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "I have the distinct honor to say that we lost white population"- former NY Rep. Charles Barron (D) ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c7126b2b</link>
      <description>"I have the distinct honor to say that we lost white population"- former NY Rep. Charles Barron (D) Listen to the crowd's reaction</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c7126b2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: Nothing any of my companies have done has been to stifle competition In fact, we’ve done ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a5c890b6</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: Nothing any of my companies have done has been to stifle competition In fact, we’ve done the opposite So at Tesla, we have open-sourced our patents. Anyone can use our patents for free How many companies do you know who’ve done that? Can you name one? I can’t At SpaceX, we don’t use patents. Once in a while, we’ll file a patent just so some patent troll doesn’t cause trouble, but we’re not stopping anyone We’ve done nothing anti-competitive We’ve done nothing to stop our competitors. I just want to clarify for the audience, because some companies have done anti-competitive things. I think the unusual thing about SpaceX and Tesla is that we’ve done things that have helped our competition So at Tesla, we have made our Supercharger system open access. We’ve made our charger technology available for free to other manufacturers</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a5c890b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the trans kiIIer who gunned down 35 kids in Canada</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8443be36</link>
      <description>This is the trans kiIIer who gunned down 35 kids in Canada</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8443be36</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cybertruck on the Moon</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/eaf8c0e6</link>
      <description>Cybertruck on the Moon</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_eaf8c0e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And they’re better cars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/154c139f</link>
      <description>And they’re better cars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_154c139f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starship will be able to do both the Moon and Mars. The destination, as I wrote in Rocket Dreams, do...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/016e9293</link>
      <description>Starship will be able to do both the Moon and Mars. The destination, as I wrote in Rocket Dreams, doesn't matter as much as the means of ascent. The good news is: we're GOING.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_016e9293</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I don’t need to conduct a research study to identify that there is an undeniable pattern of violence...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0305d58b</link>
      <description>I don’t need to conduct a research study to identify that there is an undeniable pattern of violence here. Another Trans person just shot 35 people, killing 10 in Canada. Giving mentally ill people cross sex hormones to affirm a delusion is DANGEROUS. Knowing this is COMMON SENSE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0305d58b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Between 2020 and 2023 California added over 24,000 regulatory restrictions. At the federal level gro...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/80cb3c7b</link>
      <description>Between 2020 and 2023 California added over 24,000 regulatory restrictions. At the federal level growth in regulatory restrictions has been pretty consistent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_80cb3c7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Preserve the official court documents!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3eb2dc49</link>
      <description>Preserve the official court documents!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3eb2dc49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
