<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-30 14:46 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:46:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wikipedia has been completely weaponized It’s essential you understand this</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8d1540bf</link>
      <description>Wikipedia has been completely weaponized It’s essential you understand this</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8d1540bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Humans are hardware. Cultures are software. We have fundamentally the same hardware, but adopt very ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f3da351c</link>
      <description>Humans are hardware. Cultures are software. We have fundamentally the same hardware, but adopt very different software. Not all software is compatible. America's software is built on universal principles and respect for law. Developing countries often run software that prioritizes tribe, custom, and heritage. That's okay. But it's incompatible. When an immigrant comes to America, they need to choose America's software over the software of the place they're leaving. Otherwise, America gets buggy and dysfunctional. Some countries have software more similar to America - and immigrants from those places will likely have an easier time integrating. That's pattern recognition, not prejudice. But the promise of America is that anyone who adopts our software and adds value to the lives of people already here gets to be here. You don't get to be here just because you want to be here. You need to bring something to the table. Millions of people want to come. We can have empathy for all of them, but we can't accommodate all of them. That's why merit-based immigration is the only rational path forward. Don't let people scare you into silence by calling you racist for recognizing this. This is how citizens of other countries approach their country. Why should America be any different?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f3da351c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here’s how vouching works for Minnesota residential facilities: Shukran: “I work for a residential f...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b16a927d</link>
      <description>Here’s how vouching works for Minnesota residential facilities: Shukran: “I work for a residential facility. My 300 residents want to vote.” Election Day Worker: “Show me you’re an employee.” Shukran: “Here you go.” *Shows badge* Election Day Worker: “All 300 can vote.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b16a927d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Starlink’s Direct to Cell service helped One NZ users send over 7 million texts via satell...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bb78ab71</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Starlink’s Direct to Cell service helped One NZ users send over 7 million texts via satellites across New Zealand this year even in remote spots without regular coverage. More than 700,000 customers are covered and usage spiked during extreme weather and outages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bb78ab71</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia.comis growing</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0856e79f</link>
      <description>Grokipedia.comis growing</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0856e79f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Democrats want to legalize all illegals, which would turn all swing state blue immediately and ensu...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5517d648</link>
      <description>"Democrats want to legalize all illegals, which would turn all swing state blue immediately and ensure permanent one-party rule in America!" 一 Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5517d648</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: "The Democrats… [are] paying [illegals] to come here and then turning them into voters… T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/752f7355</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: "The Democrats… [are] paying [illegals] to come here and then turning them into voters… This is why the Democrats are so upset… if we turn off this gigantic money magnet for illegal immigrants, then they will leave and they'll lose voters."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_752f7355</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok (xAI) is no longer chasing the market — it’s defining it. 📊 40.3% OpenRouter LLM market share 🔥...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b3df17c2</link>
      <description>Grok (xAI) is no longer chasing the market — it’s defining it. 📊 40.3% OpenRouter LLM market share 🔥 2.85 TRILLION tokens processed 🏆 Clear #1 by a massive margin This isn’t incremental growth. This is dominance powered by real usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b3df17c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I've been noting scams like what the Somalis in Minnesota are doing as a major source of fraudulent ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e4042ac2</link>
      <description>I've been noting scams like what the Somalis in Minnesota are doing as a major source of fraudulent autism diagnoses for a while now. So much of the apparent 'autism epidemic' is this style of grift.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e4042ac2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Asmongold goes off on the Minnesota Somali Daycare fraud and how wealthy Americans (and Hasan) defen...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/89917490</link>
      <description>Asmongold goes off on the Minnesota Somali Daycare fraud and how wealthy Americans (and Hasan) defend it: "Average Americans are tired of having their country rotted out, looted, pillaged by a bunch of random f-ing 3rd worlders and then asked to apologize for it because of something that happened before we were born." "It's outrageous. These insulated, generally white liberals who live in gate communities...they never have to see it."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_89917490</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: When Elon made a hand gesture in passion, they wrote hundreds of articles calling him racist When So...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f3f811f1</link>
      <description>When Elon made a hand gesture in passion, they wrote hundreds of articles calling him racist When Somalis steal billions of dollars, they call the people who are upset racist It appears that the best way to loot the country is to call everyone racist</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f3f811f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: HOLY COW MINNESOTA VOTER FRAUD This is the form used to vouch up to 8 voters on Election Day (for pe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2957f714</link>
      <description>HOLY COW MINNESOTA VOTER FRAUD This is the form used to vouch up to 8 voters on Election Day (for people that don’t have IDs). If you read closely it says, “Employees of residential facilities may vouch for an 👉UNLIMITED👈 number of facility residents.” This is legal. This is Minnesota law. Which means that there *should* be a paper trail of every single one of these vouching forms. How many persons serve as vouchers each election? What is the number of persons for each voucher? Do these vouchers show up every single election? We need to begin submitting Data Practices Requests to the Minnesota Secretary of State. This is a huge story.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2957f714</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 CROWDFUNDED DOGE: THE PLAN TO UNLEASH DOZENS OF NICK SHIRLEYS ACROSS AMERICA Nick Shirley's Minne...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f1e7426d</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 CROWDFUNDED DOGE: THE PLAN TO UNLEASH DOZENS OF NICK SHIRLEYS ACROSS AMERICA Nick Shirley's Minnesota daycare investigation hit 124 million views in less than 4 days and exposed millions in alleged welfare fraud. Now Silicon Valley wants to scale the model nationwide. Chamath Palihapitiya just backed the idea of a crowdfunded grant program to unleash "tens of investigative journalists" on fraud across blue states, starting with California. The concept: create a decentralized DOGE-like network of citizen journalists funded by tech investors, supported by private investigators, and aimed at systematically documenting fraud across blue states. Think of it as Elon's DOGE operation, but crowdsourced and hyper-focused on state-level corruption instead of federal waste. The strategy is simple: flood the news cycle with so many documented fraud cases that traditional media can't ignore them and Democrats can't counter the narrative fast enough. One hoodie-wearing journalist with a camera just reached more people than every major news network combined. Now imagine dozens doing the same thing simultaneously across multiple states. This is launching with the midterms in mind, designed to overwhelm whatever narrative control corporate media still has. Shirley proved the model works. Now the question is whether Silicon Valley backing can turn one viral investigation into a coordinated nationwide blitz. Source:@chamath, ZeroHedge</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f1e7426d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨🇺🇸 MINNESOTA CONFIRMS NONE OF THE DAYCARES IN VIRAL FRAUD VIDEO HAD PAYMENTS PAUSED, STATE DOING SI...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ce48f0a7</link>
      <description>🚨🇺🇸 MINNESOTA CONFIRMS NONE OF THE DAYCARES IN VIRAL FRAUD VIDEO HAD PAYMENTS PAUSED, STATE DOING SITE VISITS TODAY It took a YouTuber to get the state to do its job. Minnesota Department of Children, Youth and Families Commissioner Tikki Brown confirmed that none of the 10 child care centers Nick Shirley visited in his viral video have had their payments paused. She added that state workers are doing site visits to the remaining centers... today. After the video went viral. After national outrage. The now-infamous "Quality Learing Center" that couldn't spell its own name and received $4 million? Closed just over a week ago. Mako Childcare, the first one in Shirley's video? Closed several years ago. So let's get this straight: Centers that closed years ago were apparently still in the system. The misspelled daycare with no children only closed after it became a national embarrassment. None of the 10 have had payments paused. The state is only now showing up to check. A YouTuber with a camera did more oversight in one afternoon than Minnesota did with billions in taxpayer funds over years. They weren't even doing site visits before. They're doing them now because America is watching. Source: Minnesota DCYF</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ce48f0a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xcancel.com/i/grok/share/J66acSGx3…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/44d7431e</link>
      <description>xcancel.com/i/grok/share/J66acSGx3…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_44d7431e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Obviously</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/00deb5e4</link>
      <description>Obviously</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_00deb5e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The reason is that the Democratic Party is buying their vote</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/42a64aa6</link>
      <description>The reason is that the Democratic Party is buying their vote</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_42a64aa6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie availab...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d8e32a22</link>
      <description>My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie available to subscribers. I recommend taking this approach for text/image/video content on 𝕏.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d8e32a22</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
