<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-19 14:57 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:57:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here is Grok’s answer to your challenge@CathyYoung63What percentage of people arrested by ICE agents...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/10f0ebc6</link>
      <description>Here is Grok’s answer to your challenge@CathyYoung63What percentage of people arrested by ICE agents are illegal aliens and what percentage are innocent citizens? Grok: According to data from U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) and independent tracking by organizations like the Transactional Records Access Clearinghouse (TRAC) and media outlets, ICE arrests overwhelmingly target non-citizens with immigration violations—commonly referred to as illegal aliens or undocumented immigrants. Reports indicate that over 328,000 people were arrested by ICE from January to mid-December 2025. Wrongful arrests of U.S. citizens (who could be considered "innocent" in this context, as they are not subject to immigration enforcement) are rare but documented. Investigations have identified more than 170 confirmed cases of U.S. citizens being held by ICE agents in 2025, often due to errors in questioning citizenship status. Other sources report up to 674 arrests of individuals claiming or confirmed as U.S. citizens during the same period, though only about 121 were detained beyond initial arrest. Using the higher estimate of 674 wrongful arrests out of approximately 328,000 total ICE arrests in 2025, this represents about 0.2% of arrests. The lower confirmed figure of 170 cases equates to roughly 0.05%. In either case, the percentage of "innocent people" (U.S. citizens wrongly arrested) is under 1%, while approximately 99.8-99.95% are non-citizens with immigration violations (illegal aliens). Note that ICE prioritizes arrests of non-citizens with criminal convictions or charges (about 70% of arrests), but the remaining 30% are typically non-criminal immigration violators—still classified as illegal aliens under U.S. law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_10f0ebc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Accurate assessment</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5609de70</link>
      <description>Accurate assessment</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5609de70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Many people don’t realise the only reason ICE agents have to do raids at people’s home or work are b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bcf06a8f</link>
      <description>Many people don’t realise the only reason ICE agents have to do raids at people’s home or work are because local politicians have refused to consent to information sharing between local &amp; federal law enforcement, which enables efficient, non violent apprehension of illegal aliens</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bcf06a8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2nd Place: Memeable is a browser extension that generates personalized memes of people from X thread...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e2c4aab2</link>
      <description>2nd Place: Memeable is a browser extension that generates personalized memes of people from X threads. Create personalized ready-to-post memeable content with one click.@thomasthecosmic@gubmee</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e2c4aab2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 3rd Place: GrokWorld uses Grok Imagine as a world model to generate synthetic training data for robo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/05cf7a70</link>
      <description>3rd Place: GrokWorld uses Grok Imagine as a world model to generate synthetic training data for robots — augmenting or replacing months of manual collection in hours.@apturaai</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_05cf7a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Being built as we speak</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/517b825f</link>
      <description>Being built as we speak</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_517b825f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Travelling to America as an Australian is terrifying. Because living in Australia, we're sheltered. ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a7c923cc</link>
      <description>Travelling to America as an Australian is terrifying. Because living in Australia, we're sheltered. We're far from the rest of the world. Our State Sponsored Media tells you that Australia has the best of everything in the world. That our culture and lifestyle is unmatched. But as soon as you arrive in America it is blindingly obvious how false that is. America feels explosive, alive, chaotic, rich. It's loud, obnoxious, unapologetic. There's no hint of tall poppy syndrome. And no constant nagging of the Nanny State. America is accelerating into an unknown future without fear. There are so many technological innovations here that would never see the light of day in Australia, because they would be strangled by regulation. Australia is beautiful, sure. But it's safe, quiet, controlled. Media and society tell you to conform, comply, be seen and not heard. Take the safe option. Be fearful of new things. Be fearful of the future. The spark of innovation is stifled. The light of creativity is discouraged. The warmth of the collective is more important than the rugged individual. And as time goes on, one of the two countries is going to be left behind. It's pretty clear which country that is. So, it's terrifying. And before I came here, everyone said I should be terrified of America. That I wouldn't be let it the country. That everyone is rioting. That Hitler runs the country. That couldn't be further from the truth. Their brains have been absolutely fried by Australian State Sponsored media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a7c923cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Articles … articles as far as you can see</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a4b8d55e</link>
      <description>Articles … articles as far as you can see</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a4b8d55e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: personalized memes ready-to-post on X sounds fun</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c5684e56</link>
      <description>personalized memes ready-to-post on X sounds fun</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c5684e56</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: EVERY SINGLE BLM/anti-ICE story is like this. So, there are two separate components here. (1) Good f...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bf3899fd</link>
      <description>EVERY SINGLE BLM/anti-ICE story is like this. So, there are two separate components here. (1) Good faith people CAN actually disagree on the division of fault in all such cases. We have courts to decide that, and we'll see at least civil matters in every case here. (2) It is Very Very Very Very easy not to get shot by the police. The Renee Good situation is accurately broken down below. Similarly, Jacob Blake, the most famous BLM case after Floyd and Brown, was a rapist who fought cops with a hunting knife on him while trying to steal a car full of kids. Hard to feel anything close to full sympathy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bf3899fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Great points</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fb467e12</link>
      <description>Great points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fb467e12</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "We are trying to arrest a child s*x offender" ICE agents say as activists honk to alert to their pr...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b755c231</link>
      <description>"We are trying to arrest a child s*x offender" ICE agents say as activists honk to alert to their presence in St Paul Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b755c231</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This video is hilarious, sorry!!😂 (I don't know the author)</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/19fb37e6</link>
      <description>This video is hilarious, sorry!!😂 (I don't know the author)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_19fb37e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Jonathan Ross, Founder and CEO of AI chip company Groq, offers a contrarian view: AI won't destroy j...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a645c6b8</link>
      <description>Jonathan Ross, Founder and CEO of AI chip company Groq, offers a contrarian view: AI won't destroy jobs, it will create a labour shortage. He outlines three things that will happen because of AI: First, massive deflationary pressure. "This cup of coffee is going to cost less. Your housing is going to cost less. Everything is going to cost less." He explains this will happen through robots farming coffee more efficiently and better supply chain management, meaning people will need less money. Second, people will opt out of the economy. "They're going to work fewer hours. They're going to work fewer days a week, and they're going to work fewer years. They're going to retire earlier because they're going to be able to support their lifestyle working less." Third, entirely new jobs and industries will emerge. Jonathan points to history as evidence: "Think about 100 years ago. 98% of the workforce in the United States was in agriculture. When we were able to reduce that to 2%, we found things for those other 98% of the population to do." He continues: "The jobs that are going to exist 100 years from now, we can't even contemplate." Software developers didn't exist a century ago. In another century, they won't exist either, "because everyone's going to be vibe coding." The same applies to influencers, a career that would have been unthinkable 100 years ago but now earns people millions. His conclusion: deflationary pressure, workforce opt-outs, and new industries we can't yet imagine will combine to create one outcome... "We're not going to have enough people."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a645c6b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Seattle Mayor Katie Wilson explicitly confirms she will NOT investigate claims of Somali daycare fra...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/26e8fc86</link>
      <description>Seattle Mayor Katie Wilson explicitly confirms she will NOT investigate claims of Somali daycare fraud She says investigating the massive theft of millions in taxpayer money is just "dividing and conquering" and refuses to ask police to look into it 🤡 Apparently, investigating potential massive taxpayer theft is now considered "targeting"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_26e8fc86</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It only gets better from here</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/be0b885e</link>
      <description>It only gets better from here</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_be0b885e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Restoring birth rates to replacement level should be top priority for all countries</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ba004b0</link>
      <description>Restoring birth rates to replacement level should be top priority for all countries</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ba004b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a31b6a70</link>
      <description>The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a31b6a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
