<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>X (Twitter) - @elonmusk</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Fetched via Nitter (https://xcancel.com)</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDA...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDANCE for all!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-0-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Yes!</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Yes!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-1-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Crazy</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Crazy</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-2-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/ToaqJQbyW…</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/ToaqJQbyW…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-3-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Turn any picture on your phone into a video and then edit it to make a fun viral...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Turn any picture on your phone into a video and then edit it to make a fun viral video!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-4-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Why homelessness is never fixed</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Why homelessness is never fixed</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-5-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Grok's slogan is “To Understand" &amp; "Understand the Universe” and this is the mai...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Grok's slogan is “To Understand" &amp; "Understand the Universe” and this is the main goal of Grok in order to find the whole truth. This is the only way to have AI safety and that's why I only trust Grok.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-6-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj said something at Amfest that was really profound. I'm paraphrasing,...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Nicki Minaj said something at Amfest that was really profound. I'm paraphrasing, but she said, "just because I want little black girls to think they're beautiful doesn't mean I need to put down little girls with blonde hair and blue eyes." 

We all got wrapped up over the last few years in zero sum thinking. This was because the people who think they rule the world pit us against one another.@NICKIMINAJrejects that. We all should.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-7-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Correct</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Correct</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-8-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Grok</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Grok</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-9-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj is right.

We need to stand up for Christians that are being persecu...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Nicki Minaj is right.

We need to stand up for Christians that are being persecuted.

Christians are the most persecuted religious group in the world.

385 million Christians worldwide face severe persecution for their faith.

You never hear about this in the media.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-10-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>"We want to make Starfleet Academy real. Let's go out there and visit other star...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>"We want to make Starfleet Academy real. Let's go out there and visit other star systems and see if there are alien civilizations.

The universe is 13.8 billion years old and earth is about 4 1/2 billion years old. We are a mere 5500 year old civilization."

一 Elon Musk</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-11-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>“Physics teaches you to reason from first principles rather than by analogy.”

E...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>“Physics teaches you to reason from first principles rather than by analogy.”

Elon Musk</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-12-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Elon Musk: A lot of the negativity stems from the axiomatic flaw that the econom...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Elon Musk: A lot of the negativity stems from the axiomatic flaw that the economic pie is static, that it's a zero-sum game.

“At my first company I didn't have any money, I just had $100,000 in student debt. That was a company in the very early days, of the Internet, called Zip2. But for all companies subsequently, I basically doubled down. I took the money from Zip2, invested it in X.com-PayPal, and then took the PayPal money, invested that in creating Tesla and SpaceX. It didn't feel right that I should ask investors to invest if I was not prepared to invest my own money. I think the whole other people's money thing is not right. You want to have skin in the game. As a result of that, I own a lot of shares in the company. And the better the company does, the more valuable the shares are. But that's because the pie has grown. And so you have to say what's at the root of a lot of the negativity is an axiomatic flaw. That the pie is static, that it's a zero-sum game, that if someone else succeeds, it's because they took more than their fair share of this fixed pie. But it's not a fixed pie. Obviously, the economic pie has grown considerably from what it was in the past. The output of goods and services, the productivity per person is dramatically greater than it has been in the past. So when you create a new company and you create new products and services, you're growing the amount of goods and services available to people. So you've not taken anything away from anyone. You've created something new and you've given people new products and services they didn't have before. We didn't use to have an iPhone, we didn't use to have computers. We didn't use to have cars or be able to fly in airplanes. We didn't use to have many of the life-saving medicines that we have today. These are all new things. The pie has grown tremendously.”

From: Interview with Ben Shapiro, January 24, 2024</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-13-1766418086</guid></item><item><title>Did you know that Grok saves time? Grok does web searches, creates documents, vi...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Did you know that Grok saves time? Grok does web searches, creates documents, videos or games for you. And it does all this in a matter of minutes, which would take hours, days, or weeks to do manually.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-14-1766418086</guid></item></channel></rss>