<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>X (Twitter) - @elonmusk</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Fetched via Nitter (https://xcancel.com)</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDA...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDANCE for all!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-0-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>“Physics teaches you to reason from first principles rather than by analogy.”

E...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>“Physics teaches you to reason from first principles rather than by analogy.”

Elon Musk</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-1-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>Elon Musk: A lot of the negativity stems from the axiomatic flaw that the econom...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Elon Musk: A lot of the negativity stems from the axiomatic flaw that the economic pie is static, that it's a zero-sum game.

“At my first company I didn't have any money, I just had $100,000 in student debt. That was a company in the very early days, of the Internet, called Zip2. But for all companies subsequently, I basically doubled down. I took the money from Zip2, invested it in X.com-PayPal, and then took the PayPal money, invested that in creating Tesla and SpaceX. It didn't feel right that I should ask investors to invest if I was not prepared to invest my own money. I think the whole other people's money thing is not right. You want to have skin in the game. As a result of that, I own a lot of shares in the company. And the better the company does, the more valuable the shares are. But that's because the pie has grown. And so you have to say what's at the root of a lot of the negativity is an axiomatic flaw. That the pie is static, that it's a zero-sum game, that if someone else succeeds, it's because they took more than their fair share of this fixed pie. But it's not a fixed pie. Obviously, the economic pie has grown considerably from what it was in the past. The output of goods and services, the productivity per person is dramatically greater than it has been in the past. So when you create a new company and you create new products and services, you're growing the amount of goods and services available to people. So you've not taken anything away from anyone. You've created something new and you've given people new products and services they didn't have before. We didn't use to have an iPhone, we didn't use to have computers. We didn't use to have cars or be able to fly in airplanes. We didn't use to have many of the life-saving medicines that we have today. These are all new things. The pie has grown tremendously.”

From: Interview with Ben Shapiro, January 24, 2024</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-2-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>Did you know that Grok saves time? Grok does web searches, creates documents, vi...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Did you know that Grok saves time? Grok does web searches, creates documents, videos or games for you. And it does all this in a matter of minutes, which would take hours, days, or weeks to do manually.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-3-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>Rapid evolution</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Rapid evolution</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-4-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>BREAKING: Beloved school bus driver in PA fired over sign asking kids to speak E...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>BREAKING: Beloved school bus driver in PA fired over sign asking kids to speak English</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-5-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>New Tesla Supercharger: San Francisco, CA - Lombard Street (16 stalls)tesla.com/...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>New Tesla Supercharger: San Francisco, CA - Lombard Street (16 stalls)tesla.com/findus?location=40…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-6-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>BREAKING: Google is now accusing the British government of attacking free speech...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>BREAKING: Google is now accusing the British government of attacking free speech and "undermining" people's right to free expression with the Online Safety Act.

Over 12.000 people are now arrested every year in Britain for social media posts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-7-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>HH Sheikh Khalid &amp; Elon Musk in Abu Dhabi ❤️</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>HH Sheikh Khalid &amp; Elon Musk in Abu Dhabi ❤️</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-8-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>Every European country is now below replacement fertility. Civilizations disappe...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Every European country is now below replacement fertility. Civilizations disappear when they stop having children. Wake up, Europe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-9-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>True facts!</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>True facts!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-10-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>Messed up</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>Messed up</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-11-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>New Tesla Supercharger now open in Mount Sheridan, QLD (6 stalls) - the most nor...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>New Tesla Supercharger now open in Mount Sheridan, QLD (6 stalls) - the most northern Supercharger site in AU

Built in partnership with the Queensland Governmenttesla.com/findus?bounds=-16.……</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-12-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>At first look, it’s baffling: how could Gavin possibly run for President, with a...</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>At first look, it’s baffling: how could Gavin possibly run for President, with all this CA fraud and waste on his watch?

Simple. Who profits from all this nonsense? He’s proven his worth to a bevy of D interests, and they’re excited for him to control even larger purse strings!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-13-1766403089</guid></item><item><title>MACROHARDER coming soon</title><link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link><description>MACROHARDER coming soon</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>elonmusk-14-1766403089</guid></item></channel></rss>