<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-01 21:43 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:43:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Well said</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ed7f1c65</link>
      <description>Well said</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ed7f1c65</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Electricity is proxy for industrial might. It is the foundation of the economy.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1d9a650f</link>
      <description>Electricity is proxy for industrial might. It is the foundation of the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1d9a650f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Legacy media lies relentlessly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/55c30570</link>
      <description>Legacy media lies relentlessly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_55c30570</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon would not have repeatedly called for all the Epstein files to be released if he had anything to...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/64007381</link>
      <description>Elon would not have repeatedly called for all the Epstein files to be released if he had anything to hide</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_64007381</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Democrats are using this as an opportunity to smear Elon. No one has done more to fight child exploi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4e5635ac</link>
      <description>Democrats are using this as an opportunity to smear Elon. No one has done more to fight child exploitation and trafficking than Elon. He risked his life and fortune to get the Epstein files released. X routinely suspends millions of accounts for CP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4e5635ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Epstein wasn’t just trafficking girls; he was in talks about pushing radical gender ideology. Emails...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/05d1f37a</link>
      <description>Epstein wasn’t just trafficking girls; he was in talks about pushing radical gender ideology. Emails show they were pitching him on “trans children” and how to normalize it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_05d1f37a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The irony is unreal U.S. Department of Justice just dropped ~3 million pages of Jeffrey Epstein file...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/05fdf83b</link>
      <description>The irony is unreal U.S. Department of Justice just dropped ~3 million pages of Jeffrey Epstein files, thousands of images, hundreds of videos A big reason this even happened is Elon Musk, who’s been relentlessly calling for actual prosecutions of everyone who committed these crimes Yet the woke media spent the whole day obsessing over emails where Epstein was pestering Elon Musk to attend his party, with Elon clearly brushing him off, and then they spin the story the other way around Where are the questions for the people actually in the videos? Where are the prosecutions? Where are the arrests? Literally zero arrests. Three million files and not a single handcuff for the real predators The media is using Elon as a distraction, keeping the spotlight on a billionaire they love to hate instead of demanding justice for the powerful figures who were actually on that island and are named throughout these files They’re now literally targeting Elon to taint his reputation, while the real predators walk free Never trust the legacy media. They’ve become one of the most corrupt forces on the planet</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_05fdf83b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The major takeaways from the Epstein files: Jeffrey Epstein loved Democratic politicians Jeffrey Eps...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e04bd9ec</link>
      <description>The major takeaways from the Epstein files: Jeffrey Epstein loved Democratic politicians Jeffrey Epstein loved liberal Hollywood actors and Musicians Jeffrey Epstein loved liberal billionaire misfits The only celebrity/billionaire Jeffrey Epstein hated was Donald Trump!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e04bd9ec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is how I knew so long ago that Reid Hoffman went to Epstein’s island. Epstein used Reid being t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/773c70cc</link>
      <description>This is how I knew so long ago that Reid Hoffman went to Epstein’s island. Epstein used Reid being there to try to get me to go, not realizing that it would have the opposite effect 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_773c70cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Booster 19 rolled out of production last night and made a midnight voyage down to Massey's for cryog...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fe730a9d</link>
      <description>Booster 19 rolled out of production last night and made a midnight voyage down to Massey's for cryogenic testing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fe730a9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk has consistently raised the issue of holding Epstein's clients accountable. He's one of th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ca65e795</link>
      <description>Elon Musk has consistently raised the issue of holding Epstein's clients accountable. He's one of the voices that has kept the noise around this matter alive, preventing those with access to the evidence from concealing it: “I think the public will be rightly frustrated if no one is prosecuted for the Epstein client list. No one at all. Some number should at least be an attempted prosecution of the worst offenders. [If Ghislaine Maxwell is in jail for sex trafficking], that means sex trafficking occurred. So, who were the clients? So the proof is there. I mean, there's lots of videos. Whenever they raided Epstein's place, there would have been like a mountain of evidence. Where is that mountain? Like, who took possession of the evidence? Specifically.” Video:@MarioNawfal</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ca65e795</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Because they are guilty</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/865fd4b5</link>
      <description>Because they are guilty</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_865fd4b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink enables reliable connectivity on Earth's oceans and waterways 🛰️🛥️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/358f137a</link>
      <description>Starlink enables reliable connectivity on Earth's oceans and waterways 🛰️🛥️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_358f137a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I am grateful to SpaceX President@Gwynne_Shotwelland personally to@elonmuskfor their swift response ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3661d836</link>
      <description>I am grateful to SpaceX President@Gwynne_Shotwelland personally to@elonmuskfor their swift response and for immediately beginning work on a solution. Elon Musk’s decision to urgently activate Starlink and send the first batch of terminals to Ukraine at the outset of the full-scale invasion was critical to the resilience of our state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3661d836</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here’s the part nobody talks about: Elon is a big reason Ukraine can still defend itself In modern w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c186a709</link>
      <description>Here’s the part nobody talks about: Elon is a big reason Ukraine can still defend itself In modern war, communication is the ultimate advantage When Russia invaded Ukraine, Elon sent the first batch of Starlink terminals and gave them vital connectivity when it mattered most That remains the key advantage Ukraine still has today</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c186a709</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try it out if you are in Austin.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea8b85c7</link>
      <description>Try it out if you are in Austin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea8b85c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Nobody has fought harder for full release of the Epstein files and prosecutions of those who abused ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c5d099dd</link>
      <description>Nobody has fought harder for full release of the Epstein files and prosecutions of those who abused children more than I did, knowing full well that the legacy media, far-left propagandists and those who are actually guilty would: 1. Admit nothing 2. Deny everything 3. Make counter-accusations against me I knew that I would be smeared relentlessly, despite never having attended his parties or been on his “Lolita Express” plane or set foot on his creepy island or done anything wrong at all. Nonetheless, the extreme pain of being accused of being the opposite of who I am was worth it. The strong must protect those cannot protect themselves, especially vulnerable children. I will gladly accept any amount of future pain to do more to protect kids and give them a chance to grow up and have happy lives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c5d099dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
