<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-16 23:37 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Tesla spotted testing the redesigned Tesla Semi for the first time in Fremont, CA. • Model Y s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/affe70d7</link>
      <description>NEWS: Tesla spotted testing the redesigned Tesla Semi for the first time in Fremont, CA. • Model Y style light bar • More efficient • Increased payload capability • 1.7kWh/mile (15% improvement vs old Semi) • Designed for autonomy • 500 mile range • 1.2MW (1,200kW) peak charging speed • 800kW drive power • Side windows don't go as far back • Heavy duty metal anti-slip traction strips on side steps • A lot more under the skin improvements Volume production starts soon. Drone footage via MetGod:youtu.be/watch?v=HNJ2_25k…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_affe70d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OPENAI FOUNDERS PLOTTED TO OUST ELON IN 2017 New court docs reveal the plot was never about "safety"...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5d9fe0ab</link>
      <description>OPENAI FOUNDERS PLOTTED TO OUST ELON IN 2017 New court docs reveal the plot was never about "safety" it was about getting rich Greg Brockman’s private diary from Sept 2017 exposes the scheme to kick Elon out: "This is the only chance we have to get out from Elon... Financially, what will take me to $1B?" He admitted that keeping Elon involved would "nuke the economics" for the founders They were already plotting to ditch the non-profit mission and sideline Musk- while publicly preaching "benefit humanity" They were privately calculating how to become billionaires The mask slips 🤡</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5d9fe0ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: STARLINK NEWS: Globe Telecom has partnered with SpaceX to introduce Starlink Direct-to-Cell (DTC) in...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a97fd541</link>
      <description>STARLINK NEWS: Globe Telecom has partnered with SpaceX to introduce Starlink Direct-to-Cell (DTC) in the Philippines, marking the first deployment of this technology in Southeast Asia and the second in Asia. The service enables standard LTE smartphones to connect directly to Starlink's constellation to provide text messaging, voice, data, and internet-of-things services in remote, underserved, or no-coverage areas without requiring additional hardware or apps. A ceremonial Memorandum of Agreement signing was witnessed by Philippines President Ferdinand Marcos Jr., the initiative supports digital inclusion under the theme "Every Filipino Connected" and aims for commercial availability starting in March 2026. SpaceX's Starlink Sr Partnership Manager, Damien Innes, represented the company and signed the agreement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a97fd541</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Stephen Miller just CALLED OUT what's happening across America between Democrats and DHS a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c0de11a</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Stephen Miller just CALLED OUT what's happening across America between Democrats and DHS and he didn't HOLD BACK! "This is clearly an INSURGENCY against the federal government. They are describing the federal government as an occupying force." "If you were to permit individual cities and states to ratify their own immigration laws for themselves, then you wouldn't have a republic and you wouldn't have a country, and that's the proposition that Fry and Ellison and Walsh are trying to test." "They are asserting that they have the unfettered right to harbor aliens who have no right to be in this country, and to incite a violent insurrection from organized agitators against federal forces to prevent those federal forces from effectuating duly enacted immigration law." It's time to INVOKE THE INSURRECTION ACT NOW!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c0de11a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Can’t wait to start the trial. The discovery and testimony will blow your mind.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/25f82754</link>
      <description>Can’t wait to start the trial. The discovery and testimony will blow your mind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_25f82754</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sword of truth, by Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/93d58198</link>
      <description>Sword of truth, by Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_93d58198</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sam Altman had indirect stake in OpenAI through YC fund Board later learned he also secretly owned O...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e7783a17</link>
      <description>Sam Altman had indirect stake in OpenAI through YC fund Board later learned he also secretly owned OpenAI Startup Fund All while serving as “independent director” of the non-profit he ran as CEO</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e7783a17</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Unjust and evil plea deal outcomexcancel.com/i/grok/share/0e5f81e3c…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cfa62b5c</link>
      <description>Unjust and evil plea deal outcomexcancel.com/i/grok/share/0e5f81e3c…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cfa62b5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OpenAI team from 2017-2023: "hey - let's do some shady stuff" Greg Brockman: "perfect, I'll write it...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f5fed9b2</link>
      <description>OpenAI team from 2017-2023: "hey - let's do some shady stuff" Greg Brockman: "perfect, I'll write it all down as we go"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f5fed9b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Elon's odds of winning his lawsuit against Sam Altman soar, as he reveals "the discovery a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1f31f88b</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Elon's odds of winning his lawsuit against Sam Altman soar, as he reveals "the discovery and testimony will blow your mind"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1f31f88b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Sam Altman had an indirect stake in OpenAI through a YC fund. Court testimony later reveal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/83b4ae73</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Sam Altman had an indirect stake in OpenAI through a YC fund. Court testimony later revealed he also secretly owned the OpenAI Startup Fund. Scam Altman is cooked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_83b4ae73</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They will eventually apply the “wealth tax” to everyone, just like the income tax, which was suppose...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cb372db3</link>
      <description>They will eventually apply the “wealth tax” to everyone, just like the income tax, which was supposed to be just a temporary tax of a few percent of the top 1% to pay for WW1 …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cb372db3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: My son had documents against OpenAI. They attacked him and killed him. 一 Mother of Suchir Balaji, Op...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ef74055e</link>
      <description>My son had documents against OpenAI. They attacked him and killed him. 一 Mother of Suchir Balaji, OpenAI Whistleblower. A proper investigation must take place, and justice must prevail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ef74055e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: California wealth tax insanity: Tony Xu, DoorDash's co-founder, would owe over $4B in tax on his $2....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0403a71e</link>
      <description>California wealth tax insanity: Tony Xu, DoorDash's co-founder, would owe over $4B in tax on his $2.5B stake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0403a71e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 84% of Americans support requiring photo ID to vote, yet the U.S. is one of the few countries tha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/42af144d</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 84% of Americans support requiring photo ID to vote, yet the U.S. is one of the few countries that doesn’t require it. In fact, the majority of countries worldwide, including big democracies like the UK, Canada, and Germany, have voter ID laws. And somehow, the people against it keep acting like basic verification is extreme. Source:@america</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_42af144d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is needed to save democracy in America</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/40260d95</link>
      <description>This is needed to save democracy in America</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_40260d95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Goodnight, 𝕏..·˚ ༘ ☾ ⋆｡˚ ☄︎</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8ed46e44</link>
      <description>Goodnight, 𝕏..·˚ ༘ ☾ ⋆｡˚ ☄︎</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8ed46e44</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Model Y Performance now available in the Middle East</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d6e6719c</link>
      <description>Model Y Performance now available in the Middle East</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d6e6719c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cybertruck is the best vehicle Tesla has ever made so far</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a0b94665</link>
      <description>Cybertruck is the best vehicle Tesla has ever made so far</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a0b94665</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
