<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-10 14:45 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:45:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: As many as 1,200 Tesla vehicles will be in@boringcompany's Vegas Loop when it's done building ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aeed1211</link>
      <description>NEWS: As many as 1,200 Tesla vehicles will be in@boringcompany's Vegas Loop when it's done building 68 miles of tunnels and 104 stations in the next few years. Boring Co. President Steve Davis: "At that point, the larger capacity@TeslaRobovan will be introduced to the loop system, mainly to be used during large events where several passengers are going to the same destination, such as game and event days at Allegiant Stadium." “The second you have four (passengers) and you have to start stopping, the best thing you can do is put your smallest vehicle in, which is a car,” Davis said. “But if you know people are going to the stadium because of a game, you’ll know an hour before, two hours before, that a lot of people are going to a game or a Sphere show, if you are smart about it, that’s when you put a high occupancy vehicle in, that’s when you put the Robovan in.” via@reviewjournal</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aeed1211</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The left didn’t care about Iryna Zarutska. The left didn’t care about Charlie Kirk. The left didn’t ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/063cc25f</link>
      <description>The left didn’t care about Iryna Zarutska. The left didn’t care about Charlie Kirk. The left didn’t care about Austin Metcalf. The left didn’t care National Guardsmen got shot in DC. But they burn cities over a woman who tried to kill ICE agents. Let that sink in…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_063cc25f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: The FCC has just authorized@SpaceXto deploy and operate up to 15,000 next-gen satellites (up f...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3dde20db</link>
      <description>NEWS: The FCC has just authorized@SpaceXto deploy and operate up to 15,000 next-gen satellites (up from 7,500). "This expansion will enable SpaceX to deliver high-speed, low-latency internet service globally, including enhanced mobile and supplemental coverage from space." The FCC’s decision allows SpaceX to: • Upgrade the Gen2 Starlink satellites with advanced form factors and cutting-edge technology. • Operate across Ku-, Ka-, V-, E-, and W-band frequencies, supporting both Fixed Satellite Service (FSS) and Mobile Satellite Service (MSS). • Waive obsolete requirements that prevented overlapping beam coverage and enhanced capacity. • Add new orbital shells at altitudes ranging from 340 km to 485 km, optimizing coverage and performance. • Provide direct-to-cell connectivity outside the United States and supplemental coverage within the U.S., paving the way for next-generation mobile services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3dde20db</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🔄 Update your iOS Grok App to version 1.3.32.⚡️ Voice and Imagine just got an upgrade...and it shows...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/75a05ebd</link>
      <description>🔄 Update your iOS Grok App to version 1.3.32.⚡️ Voice and Imagine just got an upgrade...and it shows. Twin suns. Floating cities. Living architecture. Watch the City of Echoes awaken, and imagine yourself living there. ➤ By@grokImagine ✨</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_75a05ebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Made with@GrokImagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3988c066</link>
      <description>Made with@GrokImagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3988c066</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Dreamscape ✨</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fd5c6046</link>
      <description>Dreamscape ✨</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fd5c6046</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The United States supports the brave people of Iran</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/01cf3ead</link>
      <description>The United States supports the brave people of Iran</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_01cf3ead</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Falcon 9 will launch nine new National Security Space Launch missions on behalf of the@USSpaceForces...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b22c96aa</link>
      <description>Falcon 9 will launch nine new National Security Space Launch missions on behalf of the@USSpaceForcestarting in late 2026, continuing to deliver assured access to space and support U.S. national defense capabilities →ssc.spaceforce.mil/Newsroom/…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b22c96aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Falcon 9 launches 29@Starlinksatellites from Florida</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e3dd21a7</link>
      <description>Falcon 9 launches 29@Starlinksatellites from Florida</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e3dd21a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The income tax was supposed to be temporary to fund World War I. Now it funds Somali fraud. Ending t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3b8c6534</link>
      <description>The income tax was supposed to be temporary to fund World War I. Now it funds Somali fraud. Ending the income tax would cement Donald Trump as the greatest President in American history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3b8c6534</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good morning everyone! Our petition to cancel the puberty blockers trial stands at over 38,000 signa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e3df9834</link>
      <description>Good morning everyone! Our petition to cancel the puberty blockers trial stands at over 38,000 signatures in less than 48 hours! At this pace, we will hit 100,000 in a matter of days and force a parliamentary debate. Please share as wide as you can.petition.parliament.uk/petit…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e3df9834</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What if a dream could look back at you? This image came from a feeling... By@grokImagine.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2fd2e18a</link>
      <description>What if a dream could look back at you? This image came from a feeling... By@grokImagine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2fd2e18a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wrong.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bc9010c1</link>
      <description>Wrong.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bc9010c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Dragon and Crew-11 are targeted to undock from the space station no earlier than Wednesday, January ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7ea0f9df</link>
      <description>Dragon and Crew-11 are targeted to undock from the space station no earlier than Wednesday, January 14</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7ea0f9df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 1M people have signed a petition demanding a General Election Parliament debates it on Monday People...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/499dcbcb</link>
      <description>1M people have signed a petition demanding a General Election Parliament debates it on Monday People are getting sick of this Labour Government Is this the beginning of the end for Keir Starmer?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_499dcbcb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: One day, soon, Tehran will be more liberal than London. Let that sink in</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7ee20ef5</link>
      <description>One day, soon, Tehran will be more liberal than London. Let that sink in</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7ee20ef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Real charmer …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a2686f57</link>
      <description>Real charmer …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a2686f57</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
