<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-31 14:48 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: US taxpayers should not be forced to fund corrupt organizations</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aabe430c</link>
      <description>US taxpayers should not be forced to fund corrupt organizations</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aabe430c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: These are actually my goals!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cd780d8f</link>
      <description>These are actually my goals!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cd780d8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What's currently going on at@moltbookis genuinely the most incredible sci-fi takeoff-adjacent thing ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/312108f1</link>
      <description>What's currently going on at@moltbookis genuinely the most incredible sci-fi takeoff-adjacent thing I have seen recently. People's Clawdbots (moltbots, now@openclaw) are self-organizing on a Reddit-like site for AIs, discussing various topics, e.g. even how to speak privately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_312108f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine is improving super fast! What are the highest priority improvements you want? Please re...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ae3eb185</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine is improving super fast! What are the highest priority improvements you want? Please reply below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ae3eb185</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a6f81876</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a6f81876</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The choice before us is unavoidable. The United States can remain a nation governed by law, or we ca...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/156adba9</link>
      <description>The choice before us is unavoidable. The United States can remain a nation governed by law, or we can allow the law to dissolve into suggestion — as my Democrat colleagues would have it. The future belongs to countries that believe in themselves enough to enforce their laws.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_156adba9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: One of the greatest lies in our culture at the moment is that allowing lawlessness is compassionate ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/35f97002</link>
      <description>One of the greatest lies in our culture at the moment is that allowing lawlessness is compassionate and enforcing the law is cruel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_35f97002</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Last night I saw, “MELANIA,” for the second time. The audience loved it, and so do I. Check it out —...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/81a2cf22</link>
      <description>Last night I saw, “MELANIA,” for the second time. The audience loved it, and so do I. Check it out — A MUST SEE!amazon.com/salp/melaniamovie…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_81a2cf22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It really is that good</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ada2f81</link>
      <description>It really is that good</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ada2f81</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Celebrities, I know it’s very important to you that you feel that you’re making a difference, and yo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9da82e67</link>
      <description>Celebrities, I know it’s very important to you that you feel that you’re making a difference, and you are, you’re making independents vote Republican.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9da82e67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That’s my favorite part</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ef81abe2</link>
      <description>That’s my favorite part</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ef81abe2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The satellites will actually be so far apart that it will be hard to see from one to another. Space ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/169bbc04</link>
      <description>The satellites will actually be so far apart that it will be hard to see from one to another. Space is so vast as to be beyond comprehension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_169bbc04</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The balance of power is changing</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5bb70c1d</link>
      <description>The balance of power is changing</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5bb70c1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 100GW/year of solar-powered AI satellites requires 100GW/year of AI computers …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0c5423cb</link>
      <description>100GW/year of solar-powered AI satellites requires 100GW/year of AI computers …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0c5423cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "I do see a path to 100 gigawatts a year of AI powered space solar satellites. If you do ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/376225a6</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "I do see a path to 100 gigawatts a year of AI powered space solar satellites. If you do a million tons of payload to orbit per year with 100 kilowatts per ton, that's 100 gigawatts of solar powered AI satellites per year. There's a path to get to a terawatt per year, then you want to make those AI satellites on the moon and use a mass driver. We should scale solar substantially in the US. Tesla and SpaceX are scaling solar, and I encourage others to do so as well."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_376225a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk is operating on another timeline right now. We are living through perhaps the most pivotal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7948188d</link>
      <description>Elon Musk is operating on another timeline right now. We are living through perhaps the most pivotal moment in humanity. Optimism is a beautiful thing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7948188d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX says it aims to deploy up to 1 million orbital satellite data centers in space to provide eno...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ae4e7a3</link>
      <description>SpaceX says it aims to deploy up to 1 million orbital satellite data centers in space to provide enough compute power for large-scale AI inference and training. • Satellites will get constant power in space. • No batteries are needed. • No glass framing required, which makes the solar panels cheaper to produce. • Passive Radiative cooling Elon says space will be the lowest-cost place to put AI within 3 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ae4e7a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Awesome detail from the SpaceX orbital datacenter filing - heliocentric disposal of satellites at th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c3048cc6</link>
      <description>Awesome detail from the SpaceX orbital datacenter filing - heliocentric disposal of satellites at their end of life. This is necessary long term and is something we've been talking about for a while. You can't re-enter that amount of mass without causing problems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c3048cc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The ones committing the fraud are the ones complaining the loudest</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/09d980fa</link>
      <description>The ones committing the fraud are the ones complaining the loudest</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_09d980fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: With the release of version 1.0, Grok Imagine is now generating more images &amp; videos than everyone e...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/459eb0c6</link>
      <description>With the release of version 1.0, Grok Imagine is now generating more images &amp; videos than everyone else combined!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_459eb0c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
