<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-26 23:16 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:16:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Grok</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4b17453c</link>
      <description>Try Grok</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4b17453c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I mean, the "mom" - who had apparently lost custody of 2/3 of her kids due to neglect or abuse - got...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/835d8a3d</link>
      <description>I mean, the "mom" - who had apparently lost custody of 2/3 of her kids due to neglect or abuse - got shot because she was illegally impeding an active arrest, tried to flee the scene, and drove her SUV at a federal agent as part of that. The agent briefly went to the hospital with internal bleeding. The "nurse" got shot because he was "directing traffic" around an active ICE situation, moved over to illegally interfere with it, and grabbed and scuffled with agents - all while armed and with two spare magazines on him. Both of these people were apparently part of a large, illicit underground network that is apparently doing things like illegally recording license plates and addresses and connected with ICE - and flat out dispatching raiders to screw with government arrests. You can view these two shoots as good or not, but the state is not killing people for being "too good, too noble." These were VERY predictable, avoidable situations of violence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_835d8a3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/2c72b7759…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f64e5440</link>
      <description>Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/2c72b7759…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f64e5440</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 36,500 killed in two days? They're massacring their own civilians. Where are the protesters in the w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/64811a90</link>
      <description>36,500 killed in two days? They're massacring their own civilians. Where are the protesters in the west -- the university encampments, the street protests, the UN, Hollywood?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_64811a90</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Question for Americans from a dumb Aussie about the Minnesota thing. Obama used ICE to deport approx...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/43b8b61f</link>
      <description>Question for Americans from a dumb Aussie about the Minnesota thing. Obama used ICE to deport approx 3M illegals, and got the nickname "Deporter in Chief". And he wasn't even voted in on doing that. There were some protests, but nothing even remotely violet or crazy. Why is now everyone so violet and crazy? Is there any other explanation apart from Orange Man Bad?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_43b8b61f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Enrique Bautista Vasquez is a 20-year-old illegal accused of sexually assaulting a 14-year-old autis...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0662d8e5</link>
      <description>Enrique Bautista Vasquez is a 20-year-old illegal accused of sexually assaulting a 14-year-old autistic girl. He allegedly lured her to his Cathedral City apartment on New Year's Eve. Julio Cesar Xocop-Vicente, a criminal illegal alien from Guatemala, killed Amber Paris, a 15-year-old girl and American citizen, after running a stop sign while speeding and striking her with his vehicle. He fled the scene and was arrested the next day, but was released by local authorities, allowing him to walk free on bond before ICE could file an immigration detainer. Worse, local authorities then dismissed his driving-without-a-license charge on December 2, 2025, while Paris was still fighting for her life. This isn't the first time he has been arrested and set free under sanctuary policies. This is who the Democrats are protecting. Who you vote for matters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0662d8e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You probably didn't hear about what an illegal did to an 11-year-old little girl in her own bedroom ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f3f1a6ea</link>
      <description>You probably didn't hear about what an illegal did to an 11-year-old little girl in her own bedroom because the media was too busy lying to you about ICE detaining a 5 year old</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f3f1a6ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The White “liberal” standard for behavior is extremely strict, but is only applied to Whites</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6e094942</link>
      <description>The White “liberal” standard for behavior is extremely strict, but is only applied to Whites</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6e094942</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Where are the protests about this?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c066048e</link>
      <description>Where are the protests about this?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c066048e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I remember</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/21f464d0</link>
      <description>I remember</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_21f464d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A man was walking his dog in Washington. Some lunatic walked up to him and asked what religion he wa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/55391f2f</link>
      <description>A man was walking his dog in Washington. Some lunatic walked up to him and asked what religion he was. He said Christian and the lunatic stabbed him &amp; his dog who are now both in the hospital. The suspect was kiIIed by police violently resisting arrest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_55391f2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “He was unarmed and they killed him anyway!” We said the same thing and you guys laughed.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/86396df8</link>
      <description>“He was unarmed and they killed him anyway!” We said the same thing and you guys laughed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_86396df8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In this example, stars like the sun would be about the size of red blood cells and on average would ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f3a9d442</link>
      <description>In this example, stars like the sun would be about the size of red blood cells and on average would be about 500 m apart</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f3a9d442</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Charlie Kirk was asking for it by saying controversial things” “The National Guardsmen were asking ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/773c1577</link>
      <description>“Charlie Kirk was asking for it by saying controversial things” “The National Guardsmen were asking for it by being present in DC when the left didn’t want them to be” “You can’t hurt a guy just because he’s engaging in armed obstruction of law enforcement” Same people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_773c1577</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The realism of Grok Imagine is astounding!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cb3ae0e4</link>
      <description>The realism of Grok Imagine is astounding!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cb3ae0e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok 4.20 just took the #1 spot on PredictionArena. 🥇 It is the only AI in profit, while e...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/42cec610</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok 4.20 just took the #1 spot on PredictionArena. 🥇 It is the only AI in profit, while every other model is sitting at a loss on the initial investment. While competitors burn capital, Grok is actively generating gains in real prediction markets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_42cec610</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Davos discussion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea7c03ad</link>
      <description>Davos discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea7c03ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
