<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-10 08:42 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:42:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Life cannot just be about one sad thing after another. There must also be things that make us super ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aa7a3f6f</link>
      <description>Life cannot just be about one sad thing after another. There must also be things that make us super excited and inspired about the future. This is one of things. Bigtime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aa7a3f6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX will have the first Moon base and it's much closer than most realize Starship can carry the h...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3d89fe0c</link>
      <description>SpaceX will have the first Moon base and it's much closer than most realize Starship can carry the highest tonnage to space of anything ever built and it's fully reusable, which changes everything Tesla Optimus robots could do most of the construction work, with minimal human intervention Tesla already makes solar panels at scale, perfect for powering a lunar base Even Tesla's Cybertruck could be adapted for lunar transport When you factor in all the pieces working together, a Moon base isn't decades away...it's happening sooner than we think Once established, the utility of a lunar outpost will scale exponentially, creating the foundation for humanity's permanent presence beyond Earth</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3d89fe0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Grok voice mode. It’s great!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9c5287fb</link>
      <description>Try Grok voice mode. It’s great!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9c5287fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX's Plan: 1. Create off-site backups of humans ASAP to ensure the survival of consciousness &amp; l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6d13fa27</link>
      <description>SpaceX's Plan: 1. Create off-site backups of humans ASAP to ensure the survival of consciousness &amp; life 2. Use Grok to better understand the universe/discover new physics (incl. how to extend consciousness &amp; life to the stars) 3. Extend consciousness &amp; life to the stars Any questions?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6d13fa27</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Pass voter ID!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b246152</link>
      <description>Pass voter ID!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b246152</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/70398684</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_70398684</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: An 11 year old was raped in a park. The Police arrested HER for being drunk and disorderly. They lef...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/684f62b7</link>
      <description>An 11 year old was raped in a park. The Police arrested HER for being drunk and disorderly. They left the men. A 12 year old was being raped and her dad went to save her from the flat The Police Arrested the DAD They left the men. Awful</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_684f62b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨BREAKING: TWO of Keir Starmer's inner circle government officials, Morgan McSweeney and Tim Allan, ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0a2cd028</link>
      <description>🚨BREAKING: TWO of Keir Starmer's inner circle government officials, Morgan McSweeney and Tim Allan, have now RESIGNED in the last 24 hours It's OVER for him. The Epstein files are going to take the communist down…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0a2cd028</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 1920, Mises dropped an intellectual atom bomb on socialism with a simple question: "How do you kn...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/70db61d0</link>
      <description>In 1920, Mises dropped an intellectual atom bomb on socialism with a simple question: "How do you know what anything costs without market prices?" While Soviet planners were drowning in millions of arbitrary calculations, trying to set prices for everything from bread to bulldozers by committee, Mises had already proven it impossible. As Rothbard later quipped: "Socialist calculation is like trying to play chess blindfolded while your opponent keeps moving the board." Today's central bankers face the same delusion, believing they can calculate the "correct" interest rate for an entire economy. The result? The same chaos Soviet planners created, just with better marketing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_70db61d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This video was live-streamed from Antarctica using@Starlink</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f6826ad2</link>
      <description>This video was live-streamed from Antarctica using@Starlink</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f6826ad2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s unbelievable what has happened to Britain. Just a few generations ago they were the greatest em...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5a11f1fd</link>
      <description>It’s unbelievable what has happened to Britain. Just a few generations ago they were the greatest empire in the history of the world. Now their girls are being taken to Pakistan as sex slaves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5a11f1fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Asmongold says we need to be even more aggressively hostile against woke, because they will do it to...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2c775d8f</link>
      <description>Asmongold says we need to be even more aggressively hostile against woke, because they will do it to you (and have). I often say that the biggest tactical error is to not believe you are in a war, when the other side is eagerly warring against you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2c775d8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 1861, to prevent border states from seceding, Lincoln occupied them with troops. He arrested the ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/795fcc1f</link>
      <description>In 1861, to prevent border states from seceding, Lincoln occupied them with troops. He arrested the mayor of Baltimore and secessionist legislators in Maryland. SCOTUS said he exceeded his powers. Lincoln ignored SCOTUS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_795fcc1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Hear me out… honeymoons on the actual Moon</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/369d2b09</link>
      <description>Hear me out… honeymoons on the actual Moon</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_369d2b09</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What you see on 𝕏 today is literally tomorrow's breaking news on every other platform and media outl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/33915e04</link>
      <description>What you see on 𝕏 today is literally tomorrow's breaking news on every other platform and media outlet</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_33915e04</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: “You could scale up to 100 terawatts of AI compute per year from the moon”</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d5a371cd</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: “You could scale up to 100 terawatts of AI compute per year from the moon”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d5a371cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX will build a system that allows anyone to travel to Moon. This will so insanely cool 🚀💫🤩</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9c9c29e3</link>
      <description>SpaceX will build a system that allows anyone to travel to Moon. This will so insanely cool 🚀💫🤩</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9c9c29e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
