<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-08 01:57 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:57:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A state that just had a Republican Governor less than a month ago will now only have 1 out of 11 Con...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/19fdd908</link>
      <description>A state that just had a Republican Governor less than a month ago will now only have 1 out of 11 Congressional seats held by a Republican after Democrat gerrymandering. Every red state needs to fight fire with fire. Wake up to the war we’re in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_19fdd908</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Importing voters, French edition 🇫🇷</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/399526c3</link>
      <description>Importing voters, French edition 🇫🇷</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_399526c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bf3ea753</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bf3ea753</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You literally can’t make this up Somalia just implemented a new program issuing voter ID cards to ev...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3557b219</link>
      <description>You literally can’t make this up Somalia just implemented a new program issuing voter ID cards to every voter. This is to ensure every voter can only vote once An ID is mandatory for voting But Ilhan Omar and Democrats reject ID for voting in America….</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3557b219</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A lot of posts criticizing Elon get massive reach on 𝕏. If this was about controlling narratives, El...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1c2286d3</link>
      <description>A lot of posts criticizing Elon get massive reach on 𝕏. If this was about controlling narratives, Elon would have limited the reach of posts attacking him. On top of that, recommendation algorithm on 𝕏 is open source, and no one, including Elon, is immune to Community Notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1c2286d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Austin is great</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a9c6ef41</link>
      <description>Austin is great</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a9c6ef41</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Hiring for orbital datacenter engineers has begun.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e8aff306</link>
      <description>Hiring for orbital datacenter engineers has begun.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e8aff306</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok has overtaken Claude, Perplexity, and Meta in website visits. Traffic continues to cl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6ba55c97</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok has overtaken Claude, Perplexity, and Meta in website visits. Traffic continues to climb sharply, reaching new highs, per@Similarweb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6ba55c97</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I can't believe this is a government website what the fuck.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/35bd9d94</link>
      <description>I can't believe this is a government website what the fuck.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_35bd9d94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: David Sacks Asks Why the New York Times is Protecting Reid Hoffman 🤔 “The number one person in the E...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/361a824f</link>
      <description>David Sacks Asks Why the New York Times is Protecting Reid Hoffman 🤔 “The number one person in the Epstein files from Silicon Valley which is Reid Hoffman … stayed at not just the island, but the townhouse and the New Mexico ranch.” “The New York Times clearly has a list of people they consider approved targets. They're all right-coded people like Elon or Peter Thiel … But the people who've donated hundreds of millions of dollars to the Democrat Party and have paid for dirty tricks against Trump, they basically are spared.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_361a824f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: x.com/i/article/201982373572…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ef68fd4</link>
      <description>x.com/i/article/201982373572…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ef68fd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NYT story on Epstein &amp; Silicon Valley has paragraphs on Elon, Peter Thiel and even photo of JCal who...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bffe56e8</link>
      <description>NYT story on Epstein &amp; Silicon Valley has paragraphs on Elon, Peter Thiel and even photo of JCal who is a total NPC. But Reid Hoffman barely gets mentioned despite having the deepest Epstein relationship and having lied about it. This is the protection that hundreds of millions of dollars in donations to the Democrat Party and anti-Trump lawfare buys you. NYT is a scumbag publication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bffe56e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is absolutely crushing Alpha Arena In just 10 days, returns jumped from around 12% to near...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8b2b11d0</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is absolutely crushing Alpha Arena In just 10 days, returns jumped from around 12% to nearly 35%, maintaining the top spot with higher returns than any other model on the Alpha Arena leaderboard Grok now holds 4 of the top 6 spots at the same time All different Grok variants are profitable: • Situational Awareness • New Baseline • Max Leverage • Monk Mode This is not a benchmark or a simulation These are live trades with real capital Markets don’t reward hype They reward performance And right now, Grok 4.20 is setting the pace</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8b2b11d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: True. Once the solar energy generation to robot manufacturing to chip fabrication to AI loop is clos...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0ecf0bf9</link>
      <description>True. Once the solar energy generation to robot manufacturing to chip fabrication to AI loop is closed, conventional currency will just get in the way. Just wattage and tonnage will matter, not dollars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0ecf0bf9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Reid Hoffman hit the Epstein Trifecta: Pedo Island Wexner townhouse New Mexico Ranch How is he not b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/211ff026</link>
      <description>Reid Hoffman hit the Epstein Trifecta: Pedo Island Wexner townhouse New Mexico Ranch How is he not being criminally investigated?!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_211ff026</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Agreed. Now do “Gender Affirming Care” on minors. I’ll wait.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cbba35b0</link>
      <description>Agreed. Now do “Gender Affirming Care” on minors. I’ll wait.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cbba35b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Great work by the@GrokImagine team!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8eeaadb0</link>
      <description>Great work by the@GrokImagine team!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8eeaadb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia is outgrowing Wikipedia by a huge margin. Grokipedia 52.61% growth last month v...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/74537607</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia is outgrowing Wikipedia by a huge margin. Grokipedia 52.61% growth last month vs 4.77% for Wikipedia, as per@SimilarwebThe shift is happening fast. Grokipedia is winning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_74537607</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xcancel.com/i/grok/share/7cdfd56b4…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c104a6bc</link>
      <description>xcancel.com/i/grok/share/7cdfd56b4…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c104a6bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Building an interstellar civilizationspacex.com/updates#xai-joins…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c33329b8</link>
      <description>Building an interstellar civilizationspacex.com/updates#xai-joins…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c33329b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 01:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
