<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-24 05:16 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:16:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Die Amerikaner verstehen nicht, dass wir einen zivilisatorischen Selbstmord begehen. Und das ist de...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c643916d</link>
      <description>"Die Amerikaner verstehen nicht, dass wir einen zivilisatorischen Selbstmord begehen. Und das ist der Grund dafür, dass wir uns mit den Republikanern sehr gut verstehen - weil wir diese Ansicht teilen!"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c643916d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More Americans have died from Biden and Harris’s open border policies than from 75 years of U.S. war...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7872f6e4</link>
      <description>More Americans have died from Biden and Harris’s open border policies than from 75 years of U.S. wars Since 1945, total U.S. combat deaths across Korea, Vietnam, the Gulf wars, Afghanistan, and the GWOT add up to about 103,000 In one year under Biden, over 110,000 Americans died from fentanyl and illicit drug overdoses That’s why the cartels are the enemy that's why the President Trump designated them as terrorists</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7872f6e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Stretch goal for Starship V4 is 300 tons of thrust per engine with 33 engines, so 10,000 tons of tot...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/37238dd9</link>
      <description>Stretch goal for Starship V4 is 300 tons of thrust per engine with 33 engines, so 10,000 tons of total thrust. That is 3 times the power of the Saturn V Moon rocket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_37238dd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The problem is that next time the senate flips, the left will break the filibuster immediately and p...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d443c334</link>
      <description>The problem is that next time the senate flips, the left will break the filibuster immediately and pass no voter ID nationally. After that, the senate will become supermajority left forever, like California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d443c334</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Business Insider review of FSD (Supervised) V14: "FSD proved to be a highly capable driver — so much...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/23b39feb</link>
      <description>Business Insider review of FSD (Supervised) V14: "FSD proved to be a highly capable driver — so much so that it has spoiled me into wishing that I didn't have to constantly babysit the system. At no point did I need to disengage FSD or question the system enough to take over the steering wheel.@TeslaFSD is a smooth and cautious driver. There were a few highlights. One was when FSD was cautious around pedestrians on Berkeley's campus. I recall a student who wasn't using the crosswalk but was close to it, walking across the road. FSD came to a rolling stop rather than an abrupt halt, which is exactly how I would've handled the situation. The system also managed to navigate the university's roads and perform a three-point turn when I stopped the car and added a new destination."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_23b39feb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Under the made-up blue slip rule, for a Trump judge or US Attorney nomination to go forward for appr...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/63ea1958</link>
      <description>Under the made-up blue slip rule, for a Trump judge or US Attorney nomination to go forward for approval, BOTH SENATORS, even from a Democrat state, must approve. Otherwise Grassley won't send the nominee forward. Because of the blue slip system, there are entire judicial regions (the 9th Circuit) where it's known by lawyers and other judges that the law doesn't apply. There's no way to reform the system, because the Senate won't change the rules. This also means that Trump, despite winning the popular vote and 7 for 7 swing states, cannot appoint US Attorneys who will enforce the will of the American people. One Democrat can veto anything. Even worse, there are line attorneys inside DOJ who are working to protect Democrats. They were hired by Biden. There's no way to remove them, because Trump cannot put his own US Atty inside the office. The blue slip system is made up, by the way. It's not in law. Grassley could end it today. Why won't he?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_63ea1958</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The difference between a conspiracy theory and the truth? About 6 months. This one is extremely dist...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/816f66b0</link>
      <description>The difference between a conspiracy theory and the truth? About 6 months. This one is extremely disturbing. Turns out mass immigration by flooding tens of millions of illegal immigrants under the Biden and Mayorkas regime was not incompetence. Democrats importing foreign voters is pure evil, anti-democratic, anti-American, and far worse than the current effort to uphold the law and deport those who are here illegally 🇺🇸</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_816f66b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: An exchange with Charlie Kirk: &gt; Whites have privilege. &gt; What can Whites do that Blacks can’t? &gt; No...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f6902d5f</link>
      <description>An exchange with Charlie Kirk: &gt; Whites have privilege. &gt; What can Whites do that Blacks can’t? &gt; Nothing. &gt; Then there’s no white privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f6902d5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: TryGrokipedia.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/eb8d8e62</link>
      <description>TryGrokipedia.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_eb8d8e62</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is how Palisades look right now. A year later…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/001189a3</link>
      <description>This is how Palisades look right now. A year later…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_001189a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Looks like a "ten strikes" rule would end more than a third.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/845deba5</link>
      <description>Looks like a "ten strikes" rule would end more than a third.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_845deba5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Well said</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9054b73c</link>
      <description>Well said</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9054b73c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We have a transracial violence epidemic</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cae4a8c1</link>
      <description>We have a transracial violence epidemic</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cae4a8c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Powerwall Storm Watch keeps the lights on for &gt;75k homes in the path of severe winter weather in the...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/24c07709</link>
      <description>Powerwall Storm Watch keeps the lights on for &gt;75k homes in the path of severe winter weather in the USxcancel.com/i/trending/20146170481…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_24c07709</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The@xAIteam is working on providing For You tabs that are specific to topics. For example, a “For Yo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/77027d54</link>
      <description>The@xAIteam is working on providing For You tabs that are specific to topics. For example, a “For You AI” that is focused only on artificial intelligence with no political rage bait. This would be like automatically generated follow lists with content ranked by quality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_77027d54</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is actually just a statistical artifact. Both conservative and liberal whites are almost exactl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3465cc79</link>
      <description>This is actually just a statistical artifact. Both conservative and liberal whites are almost exactly as racist as ALL other large groups - lib whites are just the only group to hate their OWN community. This balance creates a weird, artificial null result - zeroes out the data mean.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3465cc79</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This sounds pretty coolxcancel.com/i/grok/share/7ad460f8b…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4b6b9da3</link>
      <description>This sounds pretty coolxcancel.com/i/grok/share/7ad460f8b…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4b6b9da3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just. Grok. It.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ab4e71f2</link>
      <description>Just. Grok. It.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ab4e71f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Davos discussion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea7c03ad</link>
      <description>Davos discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea7c03ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
