<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-12 05:45 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:45:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok just ranked #1 in first-month new user growth ratio. Outpacing Gemini, ChatGPT, Claud...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/33c6d629</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok just ranked #1 in first-month new user growth ratio. Outpacing Gemini, ChatGPT, Claude, and others. Momentum is accelerating. 🚀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_33c6d629</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING Senator Joni Ernst (R-IA) just signed on as a cosponsor of the SAVE America Act. With@Based...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/23acc6fa</link>
      <description>BREAKING Senator Joni Ernst (R-IA) just signed on as a cosponsor of the SAVE America Act. With@BasedMikeLeeas the sponsor &amp; 39 cosponsors, we’re up to 40 Senators in support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_23acc6fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is what happens when Elon runs your company. xAI which is only 2.5 yrs old and has a team size ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/77b03e9d</link>
      <description>This is what happens when Elon runs your company. xAI which is only 2.5 yrs old and has a team size that is 1/10th of many competitors, its #1 in voice, image generation, image edits, forecasting, and many intelligence leaderboards, all while having the most powerful training center in the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_77b03e9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk predicts that AI will bypass coding entirely by the end of 2026 - just creates the binary ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/97737b96</link>
      <description>Elon Musk predicts that AI will bypass coding entirely by the end of 2026 - just creates the binary directly AI can create a much more efficient binary than can be done by any compiler So just say, "Create optimized binary for this particular outcome," and you actually bypass even traditional coding Current: Code → Compiler → Binary → Execute Future: Prompt → AI-generated Binary → Execute Grok Code is going to be state-of-the-art in 2–3 months Software development is about to fundamentally change</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_97737b96</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: So sick! Join the team!x.ai/careers</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/af04dc7d</link>
      <description>So sick! Join the team!x.ai/careers</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_af04dc7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Bro… Elon just laid out the blueprint on how xAI and SpaceX are getting to 1,000+ gigawatts per year...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/80db2def</link>
      <description>Bro… Elon just laid out the blueprint on how xAI and SpaceX are getting to 1,000+ gigawatts per year and beyond, in his closing statement at the xAI all-hands! IMO, this is why there will be no competition in space. 1/ Earth Supercomputers (Now) Build Memphis cluster to get us to &gt;1 GW of power. “We’re only right now using roughly one percent of the potential energy of Earth.” Plan: • 330,000+ Grace Blackwell GPUs • ~1M H100-equivalent compute • 1 gigawatt draw at full scale • Built in &lt;1 year • Tesla Megapacks stabilizing energy FYI, most AI companies are operating in hundreds of megawatts, yet xAI is already at a utility-scale gigawatt compute. 2/ Orbital Datacenters (Soon) Get to 100-200 GW per year launched into orbit with a path to ~1 terawatt (1,000 GW) total from Earth launches. “The next step beyond Earth data centers is our Earth orbital datacenters… launching at the 100-200 gigawatt per year level. Not cumulative, I mean per year.” Benefits: • Continuous solar exposure • No land constraints • No terrestrial grid bottlenecks • Virtually unlimited horizontal expansion FYI, 100–200 GW per year is equivalent to adding multiple large nation-scale grids annually. 3/ Moon Factories + Mass Driver (Mid Future) Get to 1,000+ GW per year, several orders of magnitude beyond Earth. “In order to do that you have to go to the Moon… We are actually going to have a mass driver on the Moon.” Plan: • Lunar factories build AI satellites • Electromagnetic mass driver launches them without fuel • Low lunar gravity reduces launch energy requirements • Scales far beyond Earth’s physical constraints FYI, this is when industrialized compute begins manufacturing off Earth. 4/ Solar System &amp; Beyond (Long Term Future) Today the sun outputs ~3.8 × 10²⁶ watts “If we wanted to use even a millionth of the Sun’s energy, that would be roughly a million times more energy than civilization currently uses.” This means • 0.000001 of the Sun’s output = ~1,000,000 × today’s global Earth energy usage. 🤯 “Earth is really a tiny, tiny dust mote in a vast darkness… The Sun is 99.8% of all mass in the solar system.” To access that scale: • Moon manufacturing • Mars expansion • Solar-orbit compute clusters • Eventually tapping meaningful fractions of stellar output So… the blueprint to get here is 1/ Start at 1 GW. 2/ Scale to 1 TW. 3/ Scale to 1,000+ GW per year. 4/ Then expand toward fractions of the Sun itself. It’s clear that xAI + SpaceX is building the AI infrastructure and pathway to a stellar-scale energy civilization. I really hope I’m still alive to witness all this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_80db2def</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Southwest Airlines has just announced that it will install@Starlinkacross its entire fleet. Th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7bb95e6</link>
      <description>NEWS: Southwest Airlines has just announced that it will install@Starlinkacross its entire fleet. The first Starlink-equipped aircraft will enter service this summer, and it will be available on more than 300 aircraft by the end of 2026. Starlink Wi-Fi will be free for all passengers. “Starlink delivers that at-home experience in the air, giving Customers the ability to stream their favorite shows from any platform, watch live sports, download music, play games, work, and connect with loved ones from takeoff to landing,” said Tony Roach, Executive Vice President, Chief Customer &amp; Brand Officer at Southwest Airlines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7bb95e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Improved version</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/14f4d9f3</link>
      <description>Improved version</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_14f4d9f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: Over 1 billion people use 𝕏. "The reason we say 1 billion users is actually over a billio...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e257f62d</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: Over 1 billion people use 𝕏. "The reason we say 1 billion users is actually over a billion users is that while our monthly users are, on average, around 600 million, the number of people who have the X app installed is well over a billion, it's just that most people only occasionally come to the X app when there's some major world event. But as we give people more reasons to use the X app, whether it's for communications, for Grok or for X money, whatever the case may be, we want it to be such that, if you wanted to, you could live your life on the X app, and as we make it more and more useful, we'll obviously give people compelling reasons to use the app every day, and have my expectation is well over a billion daily active users."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e257f62d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For all the fools that said 𝕏 would be dead by now.… here are the facts the team just shared at the ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/070e77d7</link>
      <description>For all the fools that said 𝕏 would be dead by now.… here are the facts the team just shared at the xAI all hands. • New users spend +43% more time in-app (all-time high) • Existing users spend +20% more time (all-time high) • Downloads are up +60% (all-time high) • Subscriptions crossed $1 billion (all-time high) • 120 million downloads per month (achieved 3 consecutive record months) • Highest all-time engagement in January, on track to beat it in February RIP to all the doubters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_070e77d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Join us to build AGI and understand the universe!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/de6aac3a</link>
      <description>Join us to build AGI and understand the universe!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_de6aac3a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk in new presentation: "I really want to see a mass driver on the Moon that is shooting AI s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6d8abc30</link>
      <description>Elon Musk in new presentation: "I really want to see a mass driver on the Moon that is shooting AI satellites into deep space. I can't image anything more epic than a mass driver on the Moon, a self-sustaining city on the Moon, and then going to Mars, throughout our solar system, and ultimately being out there amongst the stars and visiting all these star systems. Maybe we'll meet aliens."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6d8abc30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s clear. Elon has a bunch of super nerds, that are kind hearted, and extremely driven running xAI...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ac67b77e</link>
      <description>It’s clear. Elon has a bunch of super nerds, that are kind hearted, and extremely driven running xAI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ac67b77e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Only American citizens should decide American elections.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3d8758c1</link>
      <description>Only American citizens should decide American elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3d8758c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is great news!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5353bbdb</link>
      <description>This is great news!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5353bbdb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This should be the 1 congressional priority: &gt; in 15 states, you don't have to show **any** ID to vo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1028e764</link>
      <description>This should be the 1 congressional priority: &gt; in 15 states, you don't have to show **any** ID to vote &gt; 69% of liberal voters support photo ID requirements, but only one democratic senator has voted for the Save Act &gt; either voter ID is mandated now, or, whenever the senate next flips, the opposite will happen (mandated no-ID voting across the US) If the bill doesn't pass now, it would be an absolute disaster for electoral security, and would likely essentially create a permanent one-party state Huge bi-partisan support. It's just a common-sense requirement. The bill is stuck due to the zombie filibuster - where the minority can refuse to vote, without even standing and talking End the filibuster and pass the bill!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1028e764</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨NEW: Elon Musk explains the reason behind the SpaceX and xAI merger. "In order to understand the un...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/306bbf22</link>
      <description>🚨NEW: Elon Musk explains the reason behind the SpaceX and xAI merger. "In order to understand the universe, you must explore the universe. That's the motivation behind the combination of SpaceX and xAI is to accelerate humanity's future in understanding the universe and extending the light of consciousness to the stars. So in the grand scheme of things, when you look at how much energy Earth is actually using for civilization, we're only right now using, call it roughly 1% of the potential energy of Earth. And if we wanted to use even a millionth of the sun's energy, that would be roughly a million times more energy than civilization currently uses. The only way to access that energy, the energy of the sun is to extend beyond Earth. Earth is really a tiny, tiny dust Mote in a vast darkness. The sun is 99.8% of all mass in the solar system, so you have to expand beyond the tiny dust mode that is earth to make any significant dent in using the sun's energy like says, you'd have to expand roughly a million times just to get to 1,000,000th of our sun's energy, and then going beyond that, exploring extending to the Galaxy. So the the next step beyond Earth data centers is our Earth orbital data centers, and we'll be launching with SpaceX orbital data centers at the 100 to 200 gigawatt per year level, not cumulative, I mean, per year. And ultimately, we see a path to maybe launching as much as a terawatt per year of compute from Earth."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_306bbf22</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa93318c</link>
      <description>xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as quickly as xAI, the structure must evolve just like any living organism. This unfortunately required parting ways with some people. We wish them well in future endeavors. We are hiring aggressively. Join xAI if the idea of mass drivers on the Moon appeals to you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa93318c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
