<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-23 20:45 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:45:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia.comenhanced</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7539a5eb</link>
      <description>Grokipedia.comenhanced</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7539a5eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 WHEN JUDGES FORGET THEY'RE REFEREES, NOT PLAYERS The Supreme Court confirmation process has becom...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/725f164a</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 WHEN JUDGES FORGET THEY'RE REFEREES, NOT PLAYERS The Supreme Court confirmation process has become political theater because we've turned judges into politicians in robes. When every major decision splits 5-4 along predictable ideological lines, we're not seeing legal interpretation; we're seeing policy preferences dressed up as jurisprudence. This is a system problem. The real damage isn't any single ruling but the erosion of public trust. When citizens can predict how judges will rule based on who appointed them, the law becomes just politics by other means. Judges are supposed to be referees calling balls and strikes, not players trying to win the game themselves. Here's what's been lost: the idea that legal questions have legal answers, not just political ones. When judges start from their desired outcome and work backward to find justification, they're not interpreting law; they're making it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_725f164a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: WOW 🚨 Entire office buildings are being discovered in Portland Maine, each on packed with home healt...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f14c210d</link>
      <description>WOW 🚨 Entire office buildings are being discovered in Portland Maine, each on packed with home health care companies that are “rarely staffed” Multiple buildings with 20-22+ home health care companies found IN ONE BUILDING “It's the same thing that we're finding in Minnesota, just to be completely blunt, the same tactics being used to defraud Medicaid. In this case, Zombie offices, I call them, where large clusters of home health care businesses and providers in one location. We saw them in Minnesota and we're seeing them here and the business owners and building owners that we speak to here say, enough. We're here in Portland, Maine. We found of the businesses that are registered in here of the 20-something businesses, 10 of them are home health care businesses As you can see, Prestige Home Care, Bright Star Home Care, Atlanta Community Support, Five Stars Home Health Care, Prime Home Care, LLC. It's a trend we saw in Minnesota, one that the Minnesota House Oversight Committee on Fraud — Large clusters of healthcare providers in one location. This building right behind me has 22 different home and community-based healthcare companies registered in the building Inside this Portland office building — I think I got 10 healthcare companies — Healthcare, healthcare, healthcare, home healthcare.“</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f14c210d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Christmas Eve 2008. Tesla closed a funding round in the final hour, days from bankruptcy. Elon Musk ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e7978947</link>
      <description>Christmas Eve 2008. Tesla closed a funding round in the final hour, days from bankruptcy. Elon Musk put in all his money &amp; assets, borrowed from friends just to pay rent. If it missed, payroll would have bounced two days after Christmas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e7978947</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Everyone is talking about AGI, but nobody can agree on what it actually means. How would you define ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9e4990fc</link>
      <description>Everyone is talking about AGI, but nobody can agree on what it actually means. How would you define it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9e4990fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Because 𝕏 believes in freedom of speech within the bounds of the laws of a country</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f84d3211</link>
      <description>Because 𝕏 believes in freedom of speech within the bounds of the laws of a country</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f84d3211</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Interesting</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/55b05898</link>
      <description>Interesting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_55b05898</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Once you understand the incentives, the behavior is obvious</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32df7a0e</link>
      <description>Once you understand the incentives, the behavior is obvious</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32df7a0e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Die Amerikaner verstehen nicht, dass wir einen zivilisatorischen Selbstmord begehen. Und das ist de...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ab66894</link>
      <description>"Die Amerikaner verstehen nicht, dass wir einen zivilisatorischen Selbstmord begehen. Und das ist der Grund dafür, dass wir uns mit den Republikanern sehr gut verstehen - weil wir diese Ansicht teilen!"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ab66894</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More Americans have died from Biden and Harris’s open border policies than from 75 years of U.S. war...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/360a2157</link>
      <description>More Americans have died from Biden and Harris’s open border policies than from 75 years of U.S. wars Since 1945, total U.S. combat deaths across Korea, Vietnam, the Gulf wars, Afghanistan, and the GWOT add up to about 103,000 In one year under Biden, over 110,000 Americans died from fentanyl and illicit drug overdoses That’s why the cartels are the enemy that's why the President Trump designated them as terrorists</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_360a2157</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Stretch goal for Starship V4 is 300 tons of thrust per engine with 33 engines, so 10,000 tons of tot...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5267bdf6</link>
      <description>Stretch goal for Starship V4 is 300 tons of thrust per engine with 33 engines, so 10,000 tons of total thrust. That is 3 times the power of the Saturn V Moon rocket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5267bdf6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The problem is that next time the senate flips, the left will break the filibuster immediately and p...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1cb30430</link>
      <description>The problem is that next time the senate flips, the left will break the filibuster immediately and pass no voter ID nationally. After that, the senate will become supermajority left forever, like California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1cb30430</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Business Insider review of FSD (Supervised) V14: "FSD proved to be a highly capable driver — so much...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5d065312</link>
      <description>Business Insider review of FSD (Supervised) V14: "FSD proved to be a highly capable driver — so much so that it has spoiled me into wishing that I didn't have to constantly babysit the system. At no point did I need to disengage FSD or question the system enough to take over the steering wheel.@TeslaFSD is a smooth and cautious driver. There were a few highlights. One was when FSD was cautious around pedestrians on Berkeley's campus. I recall a student who wasn't using the crosswalk but was close to it, walking across the road. FSD came to a rolling stop rather than an abrupt halt, which is exactly how I would've handled the situation. The system also managed to navigate the university's roads and perform a three-point turn when I stopped the car and added a new destination."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5d065312</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Under the made-up blue slip rule, for a Trump judge or US Attorney nomination to go forward for appr...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/036ccb22</link>
      <description>Under the made-up blue slip rule, for a Trump judge or US Attorney nomination to go forward for approval, BOTH SENATORS, even from a Democrat state, must approve. Otherwise Grassley won't send the nominee forward. Because of the blue slip system, there are entire judicial regions (the 9th Circuit) where it's known by lawyers and other judges that the law doesn't apply. There's no way to reform the system, because the Senate won't change the rules. This also means that Trump, despite winning the popular vote and 7 for 7 swing states, cannot appoint US Attorneys who will enforce the will of the American people. One Democrat can veto anything. Even worse, there are line attorneys inside DOJ who are working to protect Democrats. They were hired by Biden. There's no way to remove them, because Trump cannot put his own US Atty inside the office. The blue slip system is made up, by the way. It's not in law. Grassley could end it today. Why won't he?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_036ccb22</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The difference between a conspiracy theory and the truth? About 6 months. This one is extremely dist...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c9bc3899</link>
      <description>The difference between a conspiracy theory and the truth? About 6 months. This one is extremely disturbing. Turns out mass immigration by flooding tens of millions of illegal immigrants under the Biden and Mayorkas regime was not incompetence. Democrats importing foreign voters is pure evil, anti-democratic, anti-American, and far worse than the current effort to uphold the law and deport those who are here illegally 🇺🇸</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c9bc3899</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: An exchange with Charlie Kirk: &gt; Whites have privilege. &gt; What can Whites do that Blacks can’t? &gt; No...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6b39d924</link>
      <description>An exchange with Charlie Kirk: &gt; Whites have privilege. &gt; What can Whites do that Blacks can’t? &gt; Nothing. &gt; Then there’s no white privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6b39d924</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: TryGrokipedia.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b98642b3</link>
      <description>TryGrokipedia.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b98642b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is how Palisades look right now. A year later…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/81f0d919</link>
      <description>This is how Palisades look right now. A year later…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_81f0d919</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Davos discussion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea7c03ad</link>
      <description>Davos discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea7c03ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
