<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-05 16:56 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:56:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I totally agree. For decades, our schools have focused on the moral failings of the West. Students l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6ce12790</link>
      <description>I totally agree. For decades, our schools have focused on the moral failings of the West. Students learn little about the West’s far more numerous and spectacular moral achievements. This imbalance has created a dangerous ethical illiteracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6ce12790</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And so we bid adieu or whatever they say in Somali to Traitor Tim</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/21df9b5e</link>
      <description>And so we bid adieu or whatever they say in Somali to Traitor Tim</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_21df9b5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Great quote from Cicero: ”A nation can survive its fools, and even the ambitious. But it cannot surv...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/450ef08e</link>
      <description>Great quote from Cicero: ”A nation can survive its fools, and even the ambitious. But it cannot survive treason from within. An enemy at the gates is less formidable, for he is known and he carries his banners openly. But the traitor moves among those within the gate freely, his sly whispers rustling through all the galleys, heard in the very hall of government itself. For the traitor appears not traitor - he speaks in the accents familiar to his victims, and wears their face and their garments, and he appeals to the baseness that lies deep in the hearts of all men. He rots the soul of a nation - he works secretly and unknown in the night to undermine the pillars of a city - he infects the body politic so that it can no longer resist. A murderer is less to be feared.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_450ef08e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Put the flag of Minnesota back</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dc45163a</link>
      <description>Put the flag of Minnesota back</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dc45163a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Seems like we could just make “spend a week at Disneyland” the test for US entry 🤷‍♂️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/15d72bc9</link>
      <description>Seems like we could just make “spend a week at Disneyland” the test for US entry 🤷‍♂️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_15d72bc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Banger 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4aed8fcc</link>
      <description>Banger 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4aed8fcc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: AUDIO/VIDEO CALLING is coming to the X CHAT web app! You'll be able to make audio or video...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b8b15a54</link>
      <description>BREAKING: AUDIO/VIDEO CALLING is coming to the X CHAT web app! You'll be able to make audio or video calls to your friends from your desktop!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b8b15a54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Why X Chat is Better Than Signal: 1. All-in-one integration: Seamlessly connected to the X platform ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/59b0c0f5</link>
      <description>Why X Chat is Better Than Signal: 1. All-in-one integration: Seamlessly connected to the X platform for quick chats from posts, replies, and communities—no need to switch apps. 2. No phone number required: Message anyone on X directly without sharing personal phone details (unlike Signal’s traditional setup). 3. Advanced features: Full encryption for files (up to large sizes), vanishing messages, edit/delete options, audio/video calls, and screenshot protection—built for modern, everyday use. 4. More reliable: Not dependent on centralized services that can go down during outages; designed as part of a robust super-app ecosystem. 5. Convenience for real conversations: Where your network already is—faster adoption and richer interactions without forcing contacts to download a separate app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_59b0c0f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: One giant scam</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/50aa64b4</link>
      <description>One giant scam</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_50aa64b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Zoolander-level-dumb giant scam</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5a607a24</link>
      <description>Zoolander-level-dumb giant scam</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5a607a24</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The new Grok Imagine upgrade is so good. 🔥</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6718c1c0</link>
      <description>The new Grok Imagine upgrade is so good. 🔥</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6718c1c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Theory of Mind</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/85556f1f</link>
      <description>Theory of Mind</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_85556f1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Meet Abdi Daisane, a Somali daycare owner running for Minnesota Congress as a Democrat. His Blooming...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d6d852d5</link>
      <description>Meet Abdi Daisane, a Somali daycare owner running for Minnesota Congress as a Democrat. His Blooming Kids Child Care Center has racked up 82 violations in 3 years, including having just ONE chair for 150+ kids—while pocketing millions in taxpayer funds. This gets worse every day. Can you believe this guy's about to be in office?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d6d852d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨BREAKING: Nick Shirley just Posted this Video exposing another Somali Daycare for getting shut down...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c8d33beb</link>
      <description>🚨BREAKING: Nick Shirley just Posted this Video exposing another Somali Daycare for getting shut down and REOPENING under a different name When they reopened… they got $2.4 million dollars ‘We The People’ want a REFUND. Do you support this? YES or NO?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c8d33beb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: America spends $7.8B monthly on SNAP. If ILLEGALS were removed from SNAP the cost would reduce 70%. ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5c819908</link>
      <description>America spends $7.8B monthly on SNAP. If ILLEGALS were removed from SNAP the cost would reduce 70%. If all benefits were CUT OFF they would LEAVE. 45% of ALL AFGHANI’s living in America receive FREE FOOD from YOU. Is this your American dream? Cause if sure isn't mine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5c819908</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yes, at massive scale! It is the biggest vote-buying fraud scheme in the history of America.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aad3bf88</link>
      <description>Yes, at massive scale! It is the biggest vote-buying fraud scheme in the history of America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aad3bf88</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
