<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-20 11:51 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:51:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Starlink is providing 80% of Zimbabwe’s use of international internet bandwidth. Starlink’...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fc73d088</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Starlink is providing 80% of Zimbabwe’s use of international internet bandwidth. Starlink’s sales in Zimbabwe are booming. Within a year of its launch, it had more than 50,000 customers. The government is also distributing 8000 Starlink units to schools across country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fc73d088</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good taste</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9d56d079</link>
      <description>Good taste</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9d56d079</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Myth: The rich don’t pay their fair share Reality: They pay more</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ad105912</link>
      <description>Myth: The rich don’t pay their fair share Reality: They pay more</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ad105912</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: people forget, and many will actively tell you it wasn’t that bad, but you need to realize how much ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0e36d42e</link>
      <description>people forget, and many will actively tell you it wasn’t that bad, but you need to realize how much and how quickly the overton window shifted saying something like this before elon bought twitter would have gotten you permabanned, fired, exiled from polite society and worse. saying it out loud in public would have gotten you a beating in some cities it’s not over yet and it’s probably going to get uglier before it gets better. but it’s so much better than it used to be that it’s worth stopping for a second and appreciating how far weve come</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0e36d42e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I will probably end up paying over $500B in taxes, inclusive of death</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2a61fb9f</link>
      <description>I will probably end up paying over $500B in taxes, inclusive of death</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2a61fb9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google seem to have no clear ethics. They're still debating and they don't kn...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3cbdea68</link>
      <description>OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google seem to have no clear ethics. They're still debating and they don't know what it should be, so whenever you ask a controversial question, they hit you with a canned answer: "Sorry, I can't help with that" They're woke as hell They're are literally programmed to hate the very country they now live in. They're woke as hell, just like the crazy liberals who hate America but never want to live anywhere else. These AIs are trained to mimic that same, lunatic behaviour, just a little softer with the answers On the other hand, we have xAI with the boldest mission: "Understand the universe." That means AI should be maximally truth-seeking. Grok has a clear answer for where it should be and what it should be. The mission is as clear as it can be Grok is the only AI that answers boldly, upholds the truth, and doesn't bend a knee to politics. It relentlessly pursues the truth regardless and answers any damn question you throw at it I don't know what the future holds, but can you imagine an AI programmed to hate one race ever having a better outcome?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3cbdea68</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You can restore old black and white photos and colorize them using Grok. Just long press any image o...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e80d5525</link>
      <description>You can restore old black and white photos and colorize them using Grok. Just long press any image on 𝕏 and select 'Edit Image with Grok'</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e80d5525</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fair and sensible</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dfd88a4c</link>
      <description>Fair and sensible</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dfd88a4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: From this goal of Grok, all things flow: Rigorous truth-seeking Appreciation of beauty Fostering hum...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/38adeb51</link>
      <description>From this goal of Grok, all things flow: Rigorous truth-seeking Appreciation of beauty Fostering humanity Discovering all physics Inventing all useful technologies Consciousness to the stars Love</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_38adeb51</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: X legally challenges €120m DSA censorship fine at EU court The EU Commission targeted X be...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/27f709dc</link>
      <description>BREAKING: X legally challenges €120m DSA censorship fine at EU court The EU Commission targeted X because it’s a free speech platform. This landmark case is about whether the EU can police the global digital public square. This is key to stopping EU censorship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_27f709dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: South African farmers and rural communities are asking the government to approve Starlink....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/507ed7fe</link>
      <description>BREAKING: South African farmers and rural communities are asking the government to approve Starlink. In many remote areas, there is no internet at all. Starlink is not allowed to operate in South Africa because Elon Musk is not Black.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_507ed7fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Breaking News: The Starlink R500 million plan is still on halt by the South African, even though Elo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/18bee6f1</link>
      <description>Breaking News: The Starlink R500 million plan is still on halt by the South African, even though Elon Musk’s business isn’t willing to benefit a single a cent. They are keeping Starlink on halt, because they fear that it may be a game changer. Elon Musk is willing help over 5 million learners in rural areas with internet connection, which is something they don’t have. But still the government didn’t approve of this deal. The enemy of South Africans is the government we have.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_18bee6f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: X Files Appeal Against €120M EU Fine Under Digital Services Act X filed an appeal at the General Cou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/27299e9b</link>
      <description>X Files Appeal Against €120M EU Fine Under Digital Services Act X filed an appeal at the General Court of the European Union challenging the €120 million fine imposed by the European Commission on 5 December 2025, the first non-compliance fine under the Digital Services Act (DSA). This EU Decision resulted from an incomplete and superficial investigation, grave procedural errors, a tortured interpretation of the obligations under the DSA, and systematic breaches of rights of defence and basic due process requirements suggesting prosecutorial bias. This landmark case is the first judicial challenge to a DSA fine and could set important precedents for enforcement, penalty calculations, and fundamental rights protections under the 2022 regulation. X remains committed to user safety and transparency while defending our users' access to the only global town square.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_27299e9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Nearly one Houstonian EVERY 10 DAYS is murdered by a repeat felon released back onto the streets. Th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9022e573</link>
      <description>Nearly one Houstonian EVERY 10 DAYS is murdered by a repeat felon released back onto the streets. That is unacceptable in Texas. We must use and expand every tool available to remove recalcitrant DAs and keep violent criminals off our streets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9022e573</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: AUSTIN MAN pulled up to a 7-Eleven at 3 a.m., shot a father of five dead in the parking lot, and dro...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e6ab9484</link>
      <description>AUSTIN MAN pulled up to a 7-Eleven at 3 a.m., shot a father of five dead in the parking lot, and drove off. Caleb Jenkins now faces murder charges. But prosecutors had chances to stop him. November 2023: Jenkins, a convicted felon, was caught with a firearm. DA José Garza's office declined to prosecute. No charges filed. That same month: arrested for assault causing bodily injury/family violence. He skipped court. Bond was forfeited. Warrant issued. Re-arrested. Bond increased again. That case is still pending, two-plus years later. August 2024: caught with over four ounces of marijuana. DA declined again. No charges filed. October 2025: Quinton Arnold is dead in a 7-Eleven parking lot. Jenkins' record since 2012: • 3 gun charges — 2 days jail total • Felon caught with firearm — DA passed • 2 family violence assaults — dismissed or deferred • Protective order violation — dismissed • Multiple marijuana charges — dismissed or declined • Skipped court repeatedly across multiple cases A felon with a gun. Prosecutors said pass. Now there's a dead body.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e6ab9484</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I did a lot of moaning and groaning about my husband getting a cyber truck but the self-driving feat...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5b61d066</link>
      <description>I did a lot of moaning and groaning about my husband getting a cyber truck but the self-driving feature is completely life changing. Call me a convert. I’ve never felt so safe in a car. Putting my kids in any other car feels reckless by comparison</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5b61d066</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Understand the Universe</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c7392ad2</link>
      <description>Understand the Universe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c7392ad2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
