<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-29 15:43 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:43:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Waymo does not respond to sirens from police cars or firetruck. However, Tesla vehicles respond to t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5ce7fc59</link>
      <description>Waymo does not respond to sirens from police cars or firetruck. However, Tesla vehicles respond to those sirens and stop the vehicle on the shoulder. We have seen these things through many videos. Tesla is the only vehicle that understands the real world best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5ce7fc59</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This one doesn’t exactly require Sherlock Holmes to figure it out, just someone who is brave and car...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/689f4d49</link>
      <description>This one doesn’t exactly require Sherlock Holmes to figure it out, just someone who is brave and cares</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_689f4d49</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good to know I’ve been slaving away for 2+ decades … taking on 100% of the bankruptcy risk, litigati...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4a412eca</link>
      <description>Good to know I’ve been slaving away for 2+ decades … taking on 100% of the bankruptcy risk, litigation risk, tax risk, audit risk, With all the daily headaches of matters of: •employment, •sales, •accounting, •legal, •insurance, •software, •vendors, •platforms, to form and run a law-abiding business, to earn a mediocre income, that I’ve created from 0 to 1, entirely by myself, bootstrapped out of my own savings, which has provided hundreds of jobs and livelihoods to employees and contractors that have touched our circle…. when all along I could’ve simply •created a shell corporation •with misspelled signage, •locked doors, •blacked out windows, •took in millions in fraudulent revenue, •payable 100% to me, never having to work an honest day, never improving the community around me, never benefiting others all in exchange for my vote. Sham. And shame. Everyone should be outraged because there’s 100% chance this is happening in your state too and everyone playing by the rules is getting rag dolled by a system that lies, cheats, steals from the builders and providers to *give* to those that can leverage that payoff into a vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4a412eca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The fraud of your taxpayer money is happening nationwide and is liberally applied to attract illegal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c9099e98</link>
      <description>The fraud of your taxpayer money is happening nationwide and is liberally applied to attract illegal (and some legal) immigrants who will reliably vote Democrat. The more you look, the more you find. And you don’t need to be a world-class detective to figure it out. This is brazen, daylight robbery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c9099e98</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Saving the world is a choice. Nick woke up one day and decided he was going to fight Gen Z needs mor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b71c131a</link>
      <description>Saving the world is a choice. Nick woke up one day and decided he was going to fight Gen Z needs more inspiration like this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b71c131a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: My lower bound guess for how much fraud there is nationally is ~20% of the Federal budget, which wou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6b7e5d46</link>
      <description>My lower bound guess for how much fraud there is nationally is ~20% of the Federal budget, which would mean $1.5 trillion per year. Probably much higher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6b7e5d46</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Views on Nick Shirley’s Minnesota Fraud Video 𝕏: 106.5 million YouTube: 1.27 million</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f9960696</link>
      <description>Views on Nick Shirley’s Minnesota Fraud Video 𝕏: 106.5 million YouTube: 1.27 million</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f9960696</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Adam Smith was a genius</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4f6f9b15</link>
      <description>Adam Smith was a genius</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4f6f9b15</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That’s really great culture!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8206d58b</link>
      <description>That’s really great culture!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8206d58b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: True, the Democrats were just breaking the law, so all that was needed was enforcing the law!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ef76242</link>
      <description>True, the Democrats were just breaking the law, so all that was needed was enforcing the law!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ef76242</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Scott Adams breaks down everything that had to happen at the same time for us to finally understand ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f3708613</link>
      <description>Scott Adams breaks down everything that had to happen at the same time for us to finally understand the world: • Trump exposing fake news + winning 2024 •@elonmuskbuying Twitter → turning it into X • DOGE +@MikeBenzCyberrevealing NGO/USAID distortions, censorship industrial complex, and international attacks on US speech •@grokexisting to summarize dense info (esp. Benz’s deep dives) • Discovering color revolutions were turned against America@ScottAdamsSays"We were this close to losing everything, and it almost seems like magic that all the right things happened at the same time. It's very unlikely that all of those things would happen at the same time, but they did. Kind of amazing."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f3708613</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Hopefully, 60 Minutes reports on it soon</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/75694813</link>
      <description>Hopefully, 60 Minutes reports on it soon</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_75694813</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Walz actively scamming elections</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/322ac153</link>
      <description>Walz actively scamming elections</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_322ac153</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c32bdaec</link>
      <description>Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. That’s how insanely awful the level of fraud actually is!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c32bdaec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
