<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-05 15:50 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:50:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine is only a few months old...impressive</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/370f649b</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine is only a few months old...impressive</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_370f649b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In most cases, it's a phase, or it's social.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/17fb1cab</link>
      <description>In most cases, it's a phase, or it's social.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_17fb1cab</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: JUST IN: X records its highest start-of-year engagement in company history, with yesterday ranking a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e3e972dc</link>
      <description>JUST IN: X records its highest start-of-year engagement in company history, with yesterday ranking among its biggest days of all time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e3e972dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Prompt Share: A beautiful young woman with dark hair in a loose updo, eyes closed in peaceful contem...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c463b93</link>
      <description>Prompt Share: A beautiful young woman with dark hair in a loose updo, eyes closed in peaceful contemplation, wearing an elegant one-shoulder flowing white gown with delicate golden floral embroidery and patterns, sitting relaxed on stone steps in ancient ruins with weathered stone columns and arches, a faded blue wooden door behind her, a large terracotta vase filled with tall dry pampas grass or wheat beside her, warm golden hour sunlight casting soft shadows, highly detailed oil painting style with visible brushstrokes, serene atmosphere, intricate textures, masterpiece, ultra detailed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c463b93</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Errrr actually small numbers of skilled craftsmen moved around Europe in the 13th century so you ha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bbb97b11</link>
      <description>"Errrr actually small numbers of skilled craftsmen moved around Europe in the 13th century so you have no right to object to paying for an infinite stream of unemployed boat migrants"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bbb97b11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I totally agree. For decades, our schools have focused on the moral failings of the West. Students l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e033f827</link>
      <description>I totally agree. For decades, our schools have focused on the moral failings of the West. Students learn little about the West’s far more numerous and spectacular moral achievements. This imbalance has created a dangerous ethical illiteracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e033f827</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And so we bid adieu or whatever they say in Somali to Traitor Tim</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bcea9a6d</link>
      <description>And so we bid adieu or whatever they say in Somali to Traitor Tim</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bcea9a6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Great quote from Cicero: ”A nation can survive its fools, and even the ambitious. But it cannot surv...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/99080c69</link>
      <description>Great quote from Cicero: ”A nation can survive its fools, and even the ambitious. But it cannot survive treason from within. An enemy at the gates is less formidable, for he is known and he carries his banners openly. But the traitor moves among those within the gate freely, his sly whispers rustling through all the galleys, heard in the very hall of government itself. For the traitor appears not traitor - he speaks in the accents familiar to his victims, and wears their face and their garments, and he appeals to the baseness that lies deep in the hearts of all men. He rots the soul of a nation - he works secretly and unknown in the night to undermine the pillars of a city - he infects the body politic so that it can no longer resist. A murderer is less to be feared.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_99080c69</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Put the flag of Minnesota back</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/19c151c4</link>
      <description>Put the flag of Minnesota back</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_19c151c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Seems like we could just make “spend a week at Disneyland” the test for US entry 🤷‍♂️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/77092c5f</link>
      <description>Seems like we could just make “spend a week at Disneyland” the test for US entry 🤷‍♂️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_77092c5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Banger 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8cc0eacd</link>
      <description>Banger 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8cc0eacd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: AUDIO/VIDEO CALLING is coming to the X CHAT web app! You'll be able to make audio or video...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/10d7ce82</link>
      <description>BREAKING: AUDIO/VIDEO CALLING is coming to the X CHAT web app! You'll be able to make audio or video calls to your friends from your desktop!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_10d7ce82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yes, at massive scale! It is the biggest vote-buying fraud scheme in the history of America.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aad3bf88</link>
      <description>Yes, at massive scale! It is the biggest vote-buying fraud scheme in the history of America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aad3bf88</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
