<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-18 16:48 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:48:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇰🇷 SOUTH KOREAN SHIPPING GIANT SWITCHES ENTIRE FLEET TO STARLINK Korea Line Corp, the shipping branc...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0c66f1d2</link>
      <description>🇰🇷 SOUTH KOREAN SHIPPING GIANT SWITCHES ENTIRE FLEET TO STARLINK Korea Line Corp, the shipping branch of SM Group, wrapped up installing Starlink on every single one of their 38 ships, bulk carriers, and LNG tankers alike. They're the first in South Korea's shipping scene to fully switch over. Now they've got lightning-fast data transfers, smoother ship-to-office comms, smarter operations, better navigation safety, and way happier crews on those epic voyages. Source:@serobinsonjr</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0c66f1d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink is quickly emerging as the go to inflight connectivity solution for airlines globally. Unit...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6c1d9803</link>
      <description>Starlink is quickly emerging as the go to inflight connectivity solution for airlines globally. United Airlines Emirates Air France British Airways Qatar Airways Korean Air Asiana Airlines Alaska Airlines Virgin Atlantic WestJet SAS Scandinavian Airlines Iberia Aer Lingus Vueling LEVEL flydubai airBaltic Jin Air ZIPAIR Tokyo Air Busan Air Seoul JSX Hawaiian Airlines Air Canada Any airline not using Starlink is falling behind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6c1d9803</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The left is openly and loudly laser focused on regaining power to imprison Republicans en masse whil...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3b5c63f5</link>
      <description>The left is openly and loudly laser focused on regaining power to imprison Republicans en masse while the Indiana republican majority thought it would be too disrespectful to redistrict the state to gain votes The right is cooked</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3b5c63f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That is what they will do</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aef81e73</link>
      <description>That is what they will do</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aef81e73</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Major scandal in the Netherlands after it’s revealed that 125 students were made to live with 125 as...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5d90d07c</link>
      <description>Major scandal in the Netherlands after it’s revealed that 125 students were made to live with 125 asylum seekers in an experiment to “foster integration” and that it ended in students falling victim to gang rape, several sexual assaults and knife crime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5d90d07c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Because the entire mainstream media frantically tells them this.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c78512f9</link>
      <description>Because the entire mainstream media frantically tells them this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c78512f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The left is telling me Greenland can have sovereign borders but America can’t. That’s weird.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/de94d032</link>
      <description>The left is telling me Greenland can have sovereign borders but America can’t. That’s weird.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_de94d032</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s high</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/16a7bdcf</link>
      <description>It’s high</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_16a7bdcf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Created using Grok Imagine. 6 base images, 6 videos. Images take &lt;3s to generate and videos &lt;20s.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cf844623</link>
      <description>Created using Grok Imagine. 6 base images, 6 videos. Images take &lt;3s to generate and videos &lt;20s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cf844623</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OK. Then blue states should resolve the entire problem by - starting in one month - simply turning o...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/12d3bb29</link>
      <description>OK. Then blue states should resolve the entire problem by - starting in one month - simply turning over every alien criminal requested by the administration at the jailhouse or whatever door. We all in agreement?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_12d3bb29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: x.com/i/article/201074278643…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f034c623</link>
      <description>x.com/i/article/201074278643…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f034c623</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: No other AI generates such HDR realistic videos in under 20 seconds. Grok is the fastest on the inte...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5355f59e</link>
      <description>No other AI generates such HDR realistic videos in under 20 seconds. Grok is the fastest on the internet. Download@Grokand give it a try!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5355f59e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tried to start a fight at the Tron: Ares premiere</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0974d3bd</link>
      <description>Tried to start a fight at the Tron: Ares premiere</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0974d3bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If we can’t pass the SAVE Act, we’re toast But we can pass the SAVE Act We must And we will—but firs...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/046c9d21</link>
      <description>If we can’t pass the SAVE Act, we’re toast But we can pass the SAVE Act We must And we will—but first we have to ditch the Zombie Filibuster Who’s on board?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_046c9d21</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: MIDTERMS: 21 Indiana Republicans killed a clean redistricting map after promises of cash from the Se...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f7f3bb45</link>
      <description>MIDTERMS: 21 Indiana Republicans killed a clean redistricting map after promises of cash from the Senate President Rodric Bray and GOP consultants. Democrats win, Trump gets stabbed in the back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f7f3bb45</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: x.com/i/article/201279200974…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0e393caf</link>
      <description>x.com/i/article/201279200974…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0e393caf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a31b6a70</link>
      <description>The path to the stars is the Moon and Mars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a31b6a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
