<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-12 04:17 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:17:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Americans voting overwhelmingly for mass deportation. Congress passed laws requiring it and then pas...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/50be6855</link>
      <description>Americans voting overwhelmingly for mass deportation. Congress passed laws requiring it and then passed new legislation to fully fund it. The response of the Democrat Party and its activists has been to support and orchestrate violent resistance against federal law enforcement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_50be6855</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Correct</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3eccc329</link>
      <description>Correct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3eccc329</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “We should be concerned about anything that undermines the 1st Amendment. There is a reason for the ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f43f9061</link>
      <description>“We should be concerned about anything that undermines the 1st Amendment. There is a reason for the 1st Amendment. People came from countries where they could not speak freely - where saying certain things would get you thrown in prison.” — Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f43f9061</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Medi Hasan talking about prosecuting Elon Musk isn't actually because Elon is breaking any laws. It'...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f30929b5</link>
      <description>Medi Hasan talking about prosecuting Elon Musk isn't actually because Elon is breaking any laws. It's because Elon is very powerful and effective. Think about this.. He owns the most free speech platform on the internet. He himself has over 230 million followers. He is on his way to being worth 1 trillion dollars. He owns the likely fastest advancing AI in the world. He is essentially 100% on the side of the republicans And he is only in his mid 50's meaning he has at least a 20 year runway. That is why democrats would want to prosecute him. He is too big of a threat to their political power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f30929b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Democrats don’t just cheat on Election Day… Presidential Election “Ballots” counted after Election D...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/322cd5ae</link>
      <description>Democrats don’t just cheat on Election Day… Presidential Election “Ballots” counted after Election Day: 2012 Dem: 60% GOP: 38% 2016: Dem: 60% GOP: 38% 2020: Dem: 65% GOP: 30% 2024: Dem: 55% GOP: 35% We haven’t had a legitimate election in decades. Pass the SAVE ACT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_322cd5ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More photos of this morning's Falcon 9 launch of the Twilight mission</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b89b192d</link>
      <description>More photos of this morning's Falcon 9 launch of the Twilight mission</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b89b192d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Turns out they banned Ozempic and LASIK in the future lol</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b7ce1bf1</link>
      <description>Turns out they banned Ozempic and LASIK in the future lol</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b7ce1bf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I know I am not supposed to show trade secrets of a Tesla. But this is how they power them. Don’t ba...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1bb4d0b8</link>
      <description>I know I am not supposed to show trade secrets of a Tesla. But this is how they power them. Don’t ban me Elon Musk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1bb4d0b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The day SpaceX sent humans to orbit for the first time 🍀</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0c9a4ca4</link>
      <description>The day SpaceX sent humans to orbit for the first time 🍀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0c9a4ca4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Things I learned today …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7ad2edff</link>
      <description>Things I learned today …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7ad2edff</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “It didn’t last long enough” and the suicide of a civilization HT:@BraedenSorbo</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/15ee71cc</link>
      <description>“It didn’t last long enough” and the suicide of a civilization HT:@BraedenSorbo</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_15ee71cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This happens a lot</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b550760d</link>
      <description>This happens a lot</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b550760d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Makes sense</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/31f3cef5</link>
      <description>Makes sense</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_31f3cef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Voter ID is standard practice. Only reason to oppose it is to commit fraud.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/268ff4d2</link>
      <description>Voter ID is standard practice. Only reason to oppose it is to commit fraud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_268ff4d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Minnesota healthcare companies caught having websites with stock ‘gibberish’ text - They just downlo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/585fefec</link>
      <description>Minnesota healthcare companies caught having websites with stock ‘gibberish’ text - They just downloaded a website template - Left the stock text that doesn’t make any sense - Didn’t bother to write any of their own information - Collect millions of US taxpayer dollars Savanah Hernandez “This is how little these people care”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_585fefec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: No ID, automatic voter registration by states and mail in ballots enable massive fraud. Those factor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3e0a484b</link>
      <description>No ID, automatic voter registration by states and mail in ballots enable massive fraud. Those factors also make it impossible to prove fraud, since there is no ID and no one actually showed up! You can’t conduct exit polls accurately or even count how many people went in to vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3e0a484b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
