<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-28 20:41 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:41:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What they actually want is to imprison and bankrupt those they disagree with</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/04774c67</link>
      <description>What they actually want is to imprison and bankrupt those they disagree with</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_04774c67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Traitor” Tim Walz</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6735fc73</link>
      <description>“Traitor” Tim Walz</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6735fc73</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Somali pirates watching Somali daycare owners make millions without ever firing a shot</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ebae5889</link>
      <description>Somali pirates watching Somali daycare owners make millions without ever firing a shot</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ebae5889</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Well, the reason for the call today, John, is…something just came across my desk. John, it is perhap...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b26e63b9</link>
      <description>Well, the reason for the call today, John, is…something just came across my desk. John, it is perhaps the best thing I've seen in the last 6 months. The company is ‘Quality Learning Center’, a cutting edge children’s daycare center located in the heart of Minneapolis</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b26e63b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fair point</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5c437b41</link>
      <description>Fair point</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5c437b41</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Why did they still receive funding and keep their license after so many violations and Zoolander-lev...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ca36bd29</link>
      <description>Why did they still receive funding and keep their license after so many violations and Zoolander-level-obvious fraud? Prosecute@GovTimWalz. He knew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ca36bd29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Promoting fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b0916ae2</link>
      <description>Promoting fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b0916ae2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wait until@Polymarketfinds out Democrats in Minnesota passed a law to allow people to claim a genera...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9af0d0d8</link>
      <description>Wait until@Polymarketfinds out Democrats in Minnesota passed a law to allow people to claim a general "physical area" like a park or a highway underpass as their residential address when they register to vote on Election Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9af0d0d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Shame on her. Moriarty is responsible for the subsequent rape.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5083a122</link>
      <description>Shame on her. Moriarty is responsible for the subsequent rape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5083a122</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Now for the find out part of FAFO …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/07d4a995</link>
      <description>Now for the find out part of FAFO …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_07d4a995</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Lots of conversation on here about the massive fraud in Minnesota. Read all our reporting right here...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/45f60033</link>
      <description>Lots of conversation on here about the massive fraud in Minnesota. Read all our reporting right here:cbsn.ws/4qnIeq0</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_45f60033</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More Zoolander-level scam bs 🤦‍♂️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9bcdfe56</link>
      <description>More Zoolander-level scam bs 🤦‍♂️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9bcdfe56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Where was the Minneapolis Star Tribune on the Somali mass fraud scandal? Too busy supporting Tim Wal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ef7567e</link>
      <description>Where was the Minneapolis Star Tribune on the Somali mass fraud scandal? Too busy supporting Tim Walz’s radical trans agenda to bother doing what a 23-year-old took the time to do &amp; break the biggest fraud story in the country?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ef7567e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: CASE UPDATE: MINNESOTA FRAUD SCHEME The FBI is aware of recent social media reports in Minnesota. Ho...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e8c468a7</link>
      <description>CASE UPDATE: MINNESOTA FRAUD SCHEME The FBI is aware of recent social media reports in Minnesota. However, even before the public conversation escalated online, the FBI had surged personnel and investigative resources to Minnesota to dismantle large-scale fraud schemes exploiting federal programs. Fraud that steals from taxpayers and robs vulnerable children will remain a top FBI priority in Minnesota and nationwide. To date, the FBI dismantled a $250 million fraud scheme that stole federal food aid meant for vulnerable children during COVID. The investigation exposed sham vendors, shell companies, and large-scale money laundering tied to the Feeding Our Future network. The case led to 78 indictments and 57 convictions. Defendants included Abdiwahab Ahmed Mohamud, Ahmed Ali, Hussein Farah, Abdullahe Nur Jesow, Asha Farhan Hassan, Ousman Camara, and Abdirashid Bixi Dool, each charged for roles ranging from wire fraud to money laundering and conspiracy. These criminals didn’t just engaged in historic fraud, but tried to subvert justice as well. Abdimajid Mohamed Nur and others were charged for attempting to bribe a juror with $120,000 in cash. Those responsible pleaded guilty and were sentenced, including a 10-year prison term and nearly $48 million in restitution in related cases. The FBI believes this is just the tip of a very large iceberg. We will continue to follow the money and protect children, and this investigation very much remains ongoing. Furthermore, many are also being referred to immigrations officials for possible further denaturalization and deportation proceedings where eligible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e8c468a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Doesn’t sound super legit 🧐</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8fdaf2d7</link>
      <description>Doesn’t sound super legit 🧐</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8fdaf2d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7b28166</link>
      <description>The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain vast numbers of illegal (and legal, in some cases) immigrants to win elections and turn America into a single-party state, destroying any real democracy. The more you look at it, the more you will be horrified at what your tax money is doing and the fact that, if this is not reversed, your vote will mean nothing. The most obvious case example is the Somali voting bloc in Minnesota, a state that historically had zero Somalis, electing Ilhan Omar to the US Congress. The same is happening in Europe, UK, Canada, Australia and New Zealand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7b28166</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
