<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-02 16:52 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:52:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia is growing rapidly. Will far exceed Wikipedia this year.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ab73f8bc</link>
      <description>Grokipedia is growing rapidly. Will far exceed Wikipedia this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ab73f8bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🧠 Why Neuralink is a game-changer for people with disabilities: For millions living with paralysis, ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fb2740a2</link>
      <description>🧠 Why Neuralink is a game-changer for people with disabilities: For millions living with paralysis, ALS, or severe motor/speech impairment, simple things like using a computer, communicating, or creating are impossible without constant help. Neuralink’s brain implant changes that—letting users control devices purely with thoughts. Noland, paralyzed below the shoulders from a diving accident, used to rely on a painful mouth stick and family caregivers. Now he independently browses, plays games like Civilization, and studies math, philosophy, &amp; languages daily—reclaiming his autonomy and planning to return to school. Alex, quadriplegic after a car crash, lost his passion for designing auto parts. With Neuralink, he’s back to 3D CAD modeling, graphics, and even coding—pushing creative boundaries again. Brad, in late-stage ALS and unable to speak/move, was trapped indoors by unreliable eye-tracking tech. Now he communicates outdoors, attends his kid’s soccer games, and dreams of travel. This isn’t sci-fi. Real patients are already living more independent, connected lives. Future steps: robotic arms, speech restoration, even vision. Neuralink restores dignity, freedom, and hope. It’s one of the most important advancements for the disabled today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fb2740a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I can't imagine any other president fixing the massive fraud problem. First, he had to dismantle the...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6588db35</link>
      <description>I can't imagine any other president fixing the massive fraud problem. First, he had to dismantle the DEI mind virus. Second, he had to not be in on the scams, directly or indirectly. Third, you need balls of steel to block these good-sounding-but-corrupt schemes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6588db35</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They are all lying propagandists</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ea46266</link>
      <description>They are all lying propagandists</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ea46266</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Two Somali sisters living next door to each other in tax-payer funded housing can make $387,000 per ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6c2caea5</link>
      <description>Two Somali sisters living next door to each other in tax-payer funded housing can make $387,000 per annum by looking after each other's 4 children. If they have 8 children each, they make $774,000. We are paying for our ethnic replacement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6c2caea5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: See for yourself: It's impossible to ignore the overlap of states where &gt; illegal immigrants can get...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/63fb1260</link>
      <description>See for yourself: It's impossible to ignore the overlap of states where &gt; illegal immigrants can get state-funded medicaid &gt; photo id is *not* required to vote &gt; the state voted blue in 2024 Anyone can see this creates a perverse incentive system for politicians to cheat. If we don't pass a federal voter ID law - and crack down on fraud like never before - it will be impossible to trust our electoral process ___ California Minnesota New York Illinois Oregon Washington Colorado ... etc</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_63fb1260</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 ICE CRACKDOWN IN MINNESOTA: OVER 500 ARRESTS TO START 2026 A sweeping immigration enforcement cam...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/12249b34</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 ICE CRACKDOWN IN MINNESOTA: OVER 500 ARRESTS TO START 2026 A sweeping immigration enforcement campaign is underway in Minnesota as part of "Operation Metro Surge," with ICE arresting hundreds of undocumented individuals across the state. More than 500 arrests have already been made in early January, targeting people with prior deportation orders, fraud ties, or criminal records. Arrests have been confirmed at sites including a Hennepin County building in Minnetonka and a construction site in Chanhassen, with particular focus on Somali communities. Analysts say 2026 could break last year’s record for deportations under Trump’s immigration policies. Sources:@EricLDaugh</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_12249b34</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just telling it like it is</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/47b7a944</link>
      <description>Just telling it like it is</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_47b7a944</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly. The “Democratic” Party paid to import voters from overseas and disenfranchise Americans.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/96f2885f</link>
      <description>Exactly. The “Democratic” Party paid to import voters from overseas and disenfranchise Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_96f2885f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Today I sent Secretary Simon a letter demanding records pertaining to Minnesota’s “vouching” system ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8ea2015d</link>
      <description>Today I sent Secretary Simon a letter demanding records pertaining to Minnesota’s “vouching” system for voter registration, pursuant to my authority under the Civil Rights Act of 1960. This system seems facially inconsistent with the Help America Vote Act of 2002. We’ll see!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8ea2015d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "I hold one passport now &amp; forever: America. I will live &amp; die here. Or Mars (part of America)." 一 E...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1bad5219</link>
      <description>"I hold one passport now &amp; forever: America. I will live &amp; die here. Or Mars (part of America)." 一 Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1bad5219</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fire him</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48260b93</link>
      <description>Fire him</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48260b93</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That’s not easy</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7d9d10b4</link>
      <description>That’s not easy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7d9d10b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Because they aren’t actually news organizations, they are legacy media propaganda pushers for the fa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cfe58ec9</link>
      <description>Because they aren’t actually news organizations, they are legacy media propaganda pushers for the far left</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cfe58ec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Arrest him</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/026eea7e</link>
      <description>Arrest him</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_026eea7e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Then it is war</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dabf3dd9</link>
      <description>Then it is war</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dabf3dd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
