<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-20 11:03 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The greatest psyop of the last century.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/18fd73bd</link>
      <description>The greatest psyop of the last century.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_18fd73bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Neuralink is hiring with more than 70 open roles right now across engineering, manufacturing, softwa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b9022ccd</link>
      <description>Neuralink is hiring with more than 70 open roles right now across engineering, manufacturing, software, robotics, biology, quality, clinical &amp; more If you want to help build the future of brain-computer interfaces, this is your movement Apply here:neuralink.com/careers</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b9022ccd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good question</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f640d5cd</link>
      <description>Good question</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f640d5cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We recently hosted students from@musowls. We always enjoying teaching students about the technologic...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/93cf44bb</link>
      <description>We recently hosted students from@musowls. We always enjoying teaching students about the technological capabilities and complexity of powering@grok.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_93cf44bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨LARRY KUDLOW: Grok is the only AI that's not woke.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/726d048f</link>
      <description>🚨LARRY KUDLOW: Grok is the only AI that's not woke.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_726d048f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Falcon 9 lands on the Just Read the Instructions droneship off the coast of The Bahamas</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/59249e71</link>
      <description>Falcon 9 lands on the Just Read the Instructions droneship off the coast of The Bahamas</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_59249e71</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Now even gov websites are linking to Grokipedia. The shift away from Wikipedia to Grokiped...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/caf0c3cb</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Now even gov websites are linking to Grokipedia. The shift away from Wikipedia to Grokipedia is officially underway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_caf0c3cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon understands</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4e75ccbd</link>
      <description>Elon understands</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4e75ccbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And Grok 4.20 coming soon</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/40bd44a3</link>
      <description>And Grok 4.20 coming soon</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_40bd44a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Starlink is providing 80% of Zimbabwe’s use of international internet bandwidth. Starlink’...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9830a1d4</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Starlink is providing 80% of Zimbabwe’s use of international internet bandwidth. Starlink’s sales in Zimbabwe are booming. Within a year of its launch, it had more than 50,000 customers. The government is also distributing 8000 Starlink units to schools across country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9830a1d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good taste</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8fbcd627</link>
      <description>Good taste</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8fbcd627</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Myth: The rich don’t pay their fair share Reality: They pay more</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5742f3b3</link>
      <description>Myth: The rich don’t pay their fair share Reality: They pay more</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5742f3b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: people forget, and many will actively tell you it wasn’t that bad, but you need to realize how much ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/999dd4b8</link>
      <description>people forget, and many will actively tell you it wasn’t that bad, but you need to realize how much and how quickly the overton window shifted saying something like this before elon bought twitter would have gotten you permabanned, fired, exiled from polite society and worse. saying it out loud in public would have gotten you a beating in some cities it’s not over yet and it’s probably going to get uglier before it gets better. but it’s so much better than it used to be that it’s worth stopping for a second and appreciating how far weve come</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_999dd4b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I will probably end up paying over $500B in taxes, inclusive of death</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/08a2786b</link>
      <description>I will probably end up paying over $500B in taxes, inclusive of death</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_08a2786b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google seem to have no clear ethics. They're still debating and they don't kn...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/abef34f4</link>
      <description>OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google seem to have no clear ethics. They're still debating and they don't know what it should be, so whenever you ask a controversial question, they hit you with a canned answer: "Sorry, I can't help with that" They're woke as hell They're are literally programmed to hate the very country they now live in. They're woke as hell, just like the crazy liberals who hate America but never want to live anywhere else. These AIs are trained to mimic that same, lunatic behaviour, just a little softer with the answers On the other hand, we have xAI with the boldest mission: "Understand the universe." That means AI should be maximally truth-seeking. Grok has a clear answer for where it should be and what it should be. The mission is as clear as it can be Grok is the only AI that answers boldly, upholds the truth, and doesn't bend a knee to politics. It relentlessly pursues the truth regardless and answers any damn question you throw at it I don't know what the future holds, but can you imagine an AI programmed to hate one race ever having a better outcome?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_abef34f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Understand the Universe</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4b09a55c</link>
      <description>Understand the Universe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4b09a55c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You can restore old black and white photos and colorize them using Grok. Just long press any image o...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7e3486b2</link>
      <description>You can restore old black and white photos and colorize them using Grok. Just long press any image on 𝕏 and select 'Edit Image with Grok'</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7e3486b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fair and sensible</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/011c444b</link>
      <description>Fair and sensible</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_011c444b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
