<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-10 12:57 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:57:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SpaceX's Plan: 1. Create off-site backups of humans ASAP to ensure the survival of consciousness &amp; l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a47d6969</link>
      <description>SpaceX's Plan: 1. Create off-site backups of humans ASAP to ensure the survival of consciousness &amp; life 2. Use Grok to better understand the universe/discover new physics (incl. how to extend consciousness &amp; life to the stars) 3. Extend consciousness &amp; life to the stars Any questions?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a47d6969</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Pass voter ID!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0365de2b</link>
      <description>Pass voter ID!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0365de2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/88591a47</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_88591a47</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: An 11 year old was raped in a park. The Police arrested HER for being drunk and disorderly. They lef...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/86bd43c0</link>
      <description>An 11 year old was raped in a park. The Police arrested HER for being drunk and disorderly. They left the men. A 12 year old was being raped and her dad went to save her from the flat The Police Arrested the DAD They left the men. Awful</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_86bd43c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨BREAKING: TWO of Keir Starmer's inner circle government officials, Morgan McSweeney and Tim Allan, ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4fa75970</link>
      <description>🚨BREAKING: TWO of Keir Starmer's inner circle government officials, Morgan McSweeney and Tim Allan, have now RESIGNED in the last 24 hours It's OVER for him. The Epstein files are going to take the communist down…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4fa75970</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 1920, Mises dropped an intellectual atom bomb on socialism with a simple question: "How do you kn...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/07667844</link>
      <description>In 1920, Mises dropped an intellectual atom bomb on socialism with a simple question: "How do you know what anything costs without market prices?" While Soviet planners were drowning in millions of arbitrary calculations, trying to set prices for everything from bread to bulldozers by committee, Mises had already proven it impossible. As Rothbard later quipped: "Socialist calculation is like trying to play chess blindfolded while your opponent keeps moving the board." Today's central bankers face the same delusion, believing they can calculate the "correct" interest rate for an entire economy. The result? The same chaos Soviet planners created, just with better marketing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_07667844</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This video was live-streamed from Antarctica using@Starlink</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/17c4a898</link>
      <description>This video was live-streamed from Antarctica using@Starlink</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_17c4a898</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s unbelievable what has happened to Britain. Just a few generations ago they were the greatest em...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/99b4636b</link>
      <description>It’s unbelievable what has happened to Britain. Just a few generations ago they were the greatest empire in the history of the world. Now their girls are being taken to Pakistan as sex slaves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_99b4636b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Asmongold says we need to be even more aggressively hostile against woke, because they will do it to...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a2d88d3d</link>
      <description>Asmongold says we need to be even more aggressively hostile against woke, because they will do it to you (and have). I often say that the biggest tactical error is to not believe you are in a war, when the other side is eagerly warring against you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a2d88d3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 1861, to prevent border states from seceding, Lincoln occupied them with troops. He arrested the ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c2d350ac</link>
      <description>In 1861, to prevent border states from seceding, Lincoln occupied them with troops. He arrested the mayor of Baltimore and secessionist legislators in Maryland. SCOTUS said he exceeded his powers. Lincoln ignored SCOTUS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c2d350ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Hear me out… honeymoons on the actual Moon</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b583dcc</link>
      <description>Hear me out… honeymoons on the actual Moon</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b583dcc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What you see on 𝕏 today is literally tomorrow's breaking news on every other platform and media outl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/53465e2b</link>
      <description>What you see on 𝕏 today is literally tomorrow's breaking news on every other platform and media outlet</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_53465e2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: “You could scale up to 100 terawatts of AI compute per year from the moon”</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d01e6848</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: “You could scale up to 100 terawatts of AI compute per year from the moon”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d01e6848</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "But that darn Elon just went and tried it and it worked, and they cancelled our WHOLE program!" Her...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f5ed55d4</link>
      <description>"But that darn Elon just went and tried it and it worked, and they cancelled our WHOLE program!" Here's an interesting story about how Elon Musk ambitiously skipped to the last step when trying to land on a barge with a rocket, proving supersonic retro-propulsion worked.@DrPhiltillknew someone working on a supersonic reentry program at NASA at the time who was shocked Elon was able to skip ahead, thus canceling their need for the program. Failing fast and forward not only saves so much money, but is more efficient and skips over steps you might not need. This lesson could even apply in your own life. This is my favorite part of my recent interview with Dr. Metzger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f5ed55d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The world needs more electricity ⚡</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2d2f69d6</link>
      <description>The world needs more electricity ⚡</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2d2f69d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I read court transcripts of the Oxford rape gang trial. The details of the torture of one thirteen-y...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a4a1643c</link>
      <description>I read court transcripts of the Oxford rape gang trial. The details of the torture of one thirteen-year-old girl have never left me. Utterly horrific. No wonder the government wants this material erased. It is imperative these archives are preserved and made freely available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a4a1643c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The UK has become Orwell’s worst nightmare</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/689d89c9</link>
      <description>The UK has become Orwell’s worst nightmare</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_689d89c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Today at the inquiry we're focusing on the NHS, who in my view have as many questions to answer as t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6945464e</link>
      <description>Today at the inquiry we're focusing on the NHS, who in my view have as many questions to answer as the police. Young girls presenting with sexually transmitted infections, miscarriages? Wounds from obvious beatings? Clear signs of rape? Did nobody senior enough in these hospitals think to seriously sound the alarm? When hundreds of young girls are coming in, beaten? Individuals across senior management in certain NHS trusts knew EXACTLY what was going on, and did nothing. They should go to prison.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6945464e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Life cannot just be about one sad thing after another. There must also be things that make us super ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5befe243</link>
      <description>Life cannot just be about one sad thing after another. There must also be things that make us super excited and inspired about the future. This is one of things. Bigtime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5befe243</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
