<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-24 13:42 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:42:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: DISH has introduced its@StarlinkInternet plans in the U.S. "Get DISH and Starlink for the powe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d788b85a</link>
      <description>NEWS: DISH has introduced its@StarlinkInternet plans in the U.S. "Get DISH and Starlink for the powerful, reliable service you need to watch and stream all your favorite content, even in the most remote locations."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d788b85a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is so great 🤩</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2edd5fbb</link>
      <description>This is so great 🤩</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2edd5fbb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: “The fundamental moral flaw of the left is empathy for the criminals and not empathy for ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/de413876</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: “The fundamental moral flaw of the left is empathy for the criminals and not empathy for the victims. There's been immense judicial overreach that is unconstitutional. It's undermining the people's faith in the legal system. It needs to stop. It's gone too far."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_de413876</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It is the only way to protect innocent people</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b765d9f4</link>
      <description>It is the only way to protect innocent people</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b765d9f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: After “The Bail Project” NGO posted bail for repeat offenders… Donnie Allen killed Benjamin McComas....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5f0b73d8</link>
      <description>After “The Bail Project” NGO posted bail for repeat offenders… Donnie Allen killed Benjamin McComas. Travis Lang killed Dylan McGinnis. Marcus Garcia killed Christie Holt. Samuel Lee Scott killed Marcia Johnson. It’s not just Judges. NGOs are involved too. How many more?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5f0b73d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The violent man who slashed an elderly woman across the face with a nail and destroyed her eye after...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fc17651e</link>
      <description>The violent man who slashed an elderly woman across the face with a nail and destroyed her eye after years of being allowed to punch random women in the face without consequence identifies as a woman, according to his defense attorney.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fc17651e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You can sense the sentience maturing</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b48a3df4</link>
      <description>You can sense the sentience maturing</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b48a3df4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is a brilliant post. Took me about 5 minutes to relax, and about 2 weeks to realize it was bett...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48f1724f</link>
      <description>This is a brilliant post. Took me about 5 minutes to relax, and about 2 weeks to realize it was better than me, something my ego was late to accept. I lost a very good friend in high-school to completely preventable accident. I don't want anyone to make that statement again!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48f1724f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 10 hours into Tesla FSD v14.2.2 and here are my thoughts: Zero lane change hesitation at all. Extrem...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ed5f4929</link>
      <description>10 hours into Tesla FSD v14.2.2 and here are my thoughts: Zero lane change hesitation at all. Extremely refined, excellent lane choices and some parking improvements are a few things to note. Really stoked about the lane changes on this build. There is ZERO lane indecisiveness, no hesitation, no stuttering. Nothing. I had never really seen much before, but this build you can tell its decision making process is much quicker and it commits. Mad Max mode is definitely mad again and I love it. Seems even quicker than v14.2.1.25 which was an improvement, but the lane changes + choices are better now. Hurry mode seems quicker on the highways and larger roads than before and very close to Mad Max, it was perfect before on v14.2.1.25. The new addition on the release notes for arrival pin being adjusted based on arrival option works. It changes the route based on if you’re going curbside, or to the lot or street parking. It behaved that way before usually but now it’s visualized. Parking is improved and impressive this build. Every single spot I parked in, it performed excellent. Centered in the lines, quick one and done parking jobs and they were great, improvement over early v14.2 builds. In parking garages, it now pulls up exactly at the ticket dispenser where in earlier v14.2 builds it would stop 9 inches short like I mentioned in previous v14.2+ build reviews. That’s fixed and worked great- couldn’t have asked for it to be any better. Perfect distance and approach- will do a lot more of this testing tomorrow. Canyon roads were insanely impressive. Did the snake 3 times which is a super narrow and twisty road and each time it performed great. Speeds were good, took the proper lines and even accelerated out of corners very well. These were all in the dark too very late at night- will post some more videos of it. Stop and go traffic performance in rush hour was awesome as before, with some added notes for how well it waited to enter an intersection if there was stopped traffic on the other side. It waited 3/3 lights I encountered where if it went and the light changed, it would be sticking into traffic so it didn’t go. Exactly like a human wouldn’t but the car judged it better than I did. One time it creeped a bit slow, but other than that fine since. Saw one instance of red hands but before I could react, it had already recovered itself. Still so impressed with how well it handles lane splitting motorcycles. It sees them approaching before I even do, and moves over just enough to be courteous to the rider as well as the car or shoulder next to me. Nice touch, and glad to see it perform well. One thing I noticed is how smooth its steering inputs always are. It just takes corners with such precision and smoothness that no human could ever come close to it. Especially noticeable on twisty roads- it drives better than almost every human on them. And I encountered a power outage tonight and the car still drove perfectly even with pitch black around. Overall, loving what I’m seeing with this build. Will report back in the day time with more but I am going to head home to get some sleep. Another huge thank you to all the magicians@Tesla_AIfor working so hard during the holiday season to get these updates out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ed5f4929</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Arrested for violence 8 times and let go each time …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/90b3ea21</link>
      <description>Arrested for violence 8 times and let go each time …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_90b3ea21</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tell this story every single day until this monster in a judge’s robe is either impeached or steps d...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f2882612</link>
      <description>Tell this story every single day until this monster in a judge’s robe is either impeached or steps down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f2882612</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What company attracts talented and driven people? One where people enjoy work intrinsically, are fai...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fc8ba21b</link>
      <description>What company attracts talented and driven people? One where people enjoy work intrinsically, are fairly compensated, and their work makes a difference in the world. That place is@xAI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fc8ba21b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Rankings Update — Dec 23 🥇 #1 Overall on OpenRouter Leaderboard 🥇 #1 in Programming Market Shar...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9a8f102d</link>
      <description>Grok Rankings Update — Dec 23 🥇 #1 Overall on OpenRouter Leaderboard 🥇 #1 in Programming Market Share 🥇 #1 in Python-Specific Tasks 🥇 #1 in Categories Token Share 🥇 #1 on Kilo Code Leaderboard 🥇 #1 on BLACKBOXAI Leaderboard 🥇 #1 on Roo Code Leaderboard 🥇 #1 on Cline Leaderboard 🥇 #1 on EQ-Bench3</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9a8f102d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Financial Times word of the year is ‘Remigration’</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0a173e7f</link>
      <description>Financial Times word of the year is ‘Remigration’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0a173e7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Merry Opti-mas!🎄 Thank you to our owners, employees &amp; supporters – you rock ❤️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/27a9007c</link>
      <description>Merry Opti-mas!🎄 Thank you to our owners, employees &amp; supporters – you rock ❤️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_27a9007c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Stop the invasion of Europe!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/831f1bfd</link>
      <description>Stop the invasion of Europe!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_831f1bfd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Space based data centers for the win</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5dcc36db</link>
      <description>Space based data centers for the win</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5dcc36db</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What is@grok? It is deep empathy! From Heinlein’s Stranger in a Strange Land: Grok means "identicall...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e29a805d</link>
      <description>What is@grok? It is deep empathy! From Heinlein’s Stranger in a Strange Land: Grok means "identically equal". The human cliché "This hurts me worse than it does you" has a distinctly Martian flavor. The Martian seems to know instinctively what we learned painfully from modern physics, that observer acts with observed through the process of observation. Grokmeans to understand so thoroughly that the observer becomes a part of the observed — to merge, blend, intermarry, lose identity in group experience. It means almost everything that we mean by religion, philosophy, and science and it means as little to us as color does to a blind man.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e29a805d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDANCE for all!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5fa68fac</link>
      <description>The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDANCE for all!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5fa68fac</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
