<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-30 05:52 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:52:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Oh look: Giving men testosterone induces a red shift in democrats, reduces lying and makes them more...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/551732f7</link>
      <description>Oh look: Giving men testosterone induces a red shift in democrats, reduces lying and makes them more likely to do what they believe is right. Who would have thought?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_551732f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We will bring an end to the Somali fraud network.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c4538a9f</link>
      <description>We will bring an end to the Somali fraud network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c4538a9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Democrats hate when this gets shared</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/114a4209</link>
      <description>Democrats hate when this gets shared</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_114a4209</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: DHS is on the ground in Minneapolis, going DOOR TO DOOR at suspected fraud sites. The American peopl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d95dab05</link>
      <description>DHS is on the ground in Minneapolis, going DOOR TO DOOR at suspected fraud sites. The American people deserve answers on how their taxpayer money is being used and ARRESTS when abuse is found. Under the leadership of@Sec_Noem, DHS is working to deliver results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d95dab05</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Not even an address</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0e20d801</link>
      <description>Not even an address</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0e20d801</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For years, people attacked Elon Musk over government contracts won by SpaceX....... contracts that s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/86080785</link>
      <description>For years, people attacked Elon Musk over government contracts won by SpaceX....... contracts that saved taxpayers billions and literally rescued U.S. spaceflight Yet those same people never ask: • Where did the $13-15B go on California’s invisible high-speed rail? • Why is there silence on $1B+ daycare fraud by Somalis in Minnesota? • Other 100s of Billions in Fraud Let’s be clear..... If not for Elon, the U.S. would’ve been begging Russia or China to reach the ISS NASA gave Boeing $4.2B SpaceX got $2.6B Here are the result: • SpaceX: Years of successful crew &amp; cargo missions • Boeing: Years late, budget overruns, and stranded astronauts..... SpaceX had to step in Today, SpaceX handles ~90% of the world’s payload to orbit For comparison: • Space Shuttle: 135 missions in 30 years • SpaceX: 165+ Falcon 9 missions in 2025 SpaceX earned those contracts because no one else could do the job....... and did it cheaper, faster, and safer And while some people cry about contracts, Elon is pushing US forward in: • Space • EVs • Manufacturing • AI • Energy Without Elon, U.S. would be behind China in all of it Think about that...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_86080785</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Over 4 billion visits per month</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a4f6d1d9</link>
      <description>Over 4 billion visits per month</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a4f6d1d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here is how voter fraud is done</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/35aefa77</link>
      <description>Here is how voter fraud is done</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_35aefa77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s not just the Somalis in Minnesota. The Dems opened up our nation to anyone who would come here ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c3a1e53</link>
      <description>It’s not just the Somalis in Minnesota. The Dems opened up our nation to anyone who would come here and vote for them, in exchange for our tax dollars. They use shell companies to funnel public money to the immigrants, meaning we are slaves that fund the people replacing us. This is why the Dems so desperately don’t want voter ID. Because they are wittingly engaged in a scheme to let the illegals vote, which allows them to stay in power, which allows them to continue to steal our tax dollars. It’s all one giant racket, an We the People are the suckers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c3a1e53</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yeah, and the scheme was working too</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ad54987f</link>
      <description>Yeah, and the scheme was working too</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ad54987f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We have charged 98 individuals in relation to fraud in Minnesota. More than 60 have pled guilty or b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6246d32a</link>
      <description>We have charged 98 individuals in relation to fraud in Minnesota. More than 60 have pled guilty or been convicted. More to come.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6246d32a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wikipedia has been completely weaponized It’s essential you understand this</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c90b26ab</link>
      <description>Wikipedia has been completely weaponized It’s essential you understand this</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c90b26ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Humans are hardware. Cultures are software. We have fundamentally the same hardware, but adopt very ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1aab3e77</link>
      <description>Humans are hardware. Cultures are software. We have fundamentally the same hardware, but adopt very different software. Not all software is compatible. America's software is built on universal principles and respect for law. Developing countries often run software that prioritizes tribe, custom, and heritage. That's okay. But it's incompatible. When an immigrant comes to America, they need to choose America's software over the software of the place they're leaving. Otherwise, America gets buggy and dysfunctional. Some countries have software more similar to America - and immigrants from those places will likely have an easier time integrating. That's pattern recognition, not prejudice. But the promise of America is that anyone who adopts our software and adds value to the lives of people already here gets to be here. You don't get to be here just because you want to be here. You need to bring something to the table. Millions of people want to come. We can have empathy for all of them, but we can't accommodate all of them. That's why merit-based immigration is the only rational path forward. Don't let people scare you into silence by calling you racist for recognizing this. This is how citizens of other countries approach their country. Why should America be any different?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1aab3e77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here’s how vouching works for Minnesota residential facilities: Shukran: “I work for a residential f...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1ad83f43</link>
      <description>Here’s how vouching works for Minnesota residential facilities: Shukran: “I work for a residential facility. My 300 residents want to vote.” Election Day Worker: “Show me you’re an employee.” Shukran: “Here you go.” *Shows badge* Election Day Worker: “All 300 can vote.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1ad83f43</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Starlink’s Direct to Cell service helped One NZ users send over 7 million texts via satell...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/067614b9</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Starlink’s Direct to Cell service helped One NZ users send over 7 million texts via satellites across New Zealand this year even in remote spots without regular coverage. More than 700,000 customers are covered and usage spiked during extreme weather and outages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_067614b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia.comis growing</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1752ddc5</link>
      <description>Grokipedia.comis growing</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1752ddc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Democrats want to legalize all illegals, which would turn all swing state blue immediately and ensu...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7f55c4a8</link>
      <description>"Democrats want to legalize all illegals, which would turn all swing state blue immediately and ensure permanent one-party rule in America!" 一 Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7f55c4a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: "The Democrats… [are] paying [illegals] to come here and then turning them into voters… T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4eeb7278</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: "The Democrats… [are] paying [illegals] to come here and then turning them into voters… This is why the Democrats are so upset… if we turn off this gigantic money magnet for illegal immigrants, then they will leave and they'll lose voters."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4eeb7278</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c32bdaec</link>
      <description>Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. That’s how insanely awful the level of fraud actually is!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c32bdaec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
