<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-30 06:59 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:59:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Over 4 billion visits per month</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f57e5625</link>
      <description>Over 4 billion visits per month</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f57e5625</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here is how voter fraud is done</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f63e5372</link>
      <description>Here is how voter fraud is done</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f63e5372</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s not just the Somalis in Minnesota. The Dems opened up our nation to anyone who would come here ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/948cac25</link>
      <description>It’s not just the Somalis in Minnesota. The Dems opened up our nation to anyone who would come here and vote for them, in exchange for our tax dollars. They use shell companies to funnel public money to the immigrants, meaning we are slaves that fund the people replacing us. This is why the Dems so desperately don’t want voter ID. Because they are wittingly engaged in a scheme to let the illegals vote, which allows them to stay in power, which allows them to continue to steal our tax dollars. It’s all one giant racket, an We the People are the suckers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_948cac25</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yeah, and the scheme was working too</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/83de95b5</link>
      <description>Yeah, and the scheme was working too</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_83de95b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We have charged 98 individuals in relation to fraud in Minnesota. More than 60 have pled guilty or b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/76bdf8a4</link>
      <description>We have charged 98 individuals in relation to fraud in Minnesota. More than 60 have pled guilty or been convicted. More to come.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_76bdf8a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wikipedia has been completely weaponized It’s essential you understand this</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/72b80241</link>
      <description>Wikipedia has been completely weaponized It’s essential you understand this</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_72b80241</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Humans are hardware. Cultures are software. We have fundamentally the same hardware, but adopt very ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/87f6cbbe</link>
      <description>Humans are hardware. Cultures are software. We have fundamentally the same hardware, but adopt very different software. Not all software is compatible. America's software is built on universal principles and respect for law. Developing countries often run software that prioritizes tribe, custom, and heritage. That's okay. But it's incompatible. When an immigrant comes to America, they need to choose America's software over the software of the place they're leaving. Otherwise, America gets buggy and dysfunctional. Some countries have software more similar to America - and immigrants from those places will likely have an easier time integrating. That's pattern recognition, not prejudice. But the promise of America is that anyone who adopts our software and adds value to the lives of people already here gets to be here. You don't get to be here just because you want to be here. You need to bring something to the table. Millions of people want to come. We can have empathy for all of them, but we can't accommodate all of them. That's why merit-based immigration is the only rational path forward. Don't let people scare you into silence by calling you racist for recognizing this. This is how citizens of other countries approach their country. Why should America be any different?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_87f6cbbe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here’s how vouching works for Minnesota residential facilities: Shukran: “I work for a residential f...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/eef9f621</link>
      <description>Here’s how vouching works for Minnesota residential facilities: Shukran: “I work for a residential facility. My 300 residents want to vote.” Election Day Worker: “Show me you’re an employee.” Shukran: “Here you go.” *Shows badge* Election Day Worker: “All 300 can vote.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_eef9f621</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Starlink’s Direct to Cell service helped One NZ users send over 7 million texts via satell...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/eb1cdea1</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Starlink’s Direct to Cell service helped One NZ users send over 7 million texts via satellites across New Zealand this year even in remote spots without regular coverage. More than 700,000 customers are covered and usage spiked during extreme weather and outages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_eb1cdea1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia.comis growing</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0a302a4a</link>
      <description>Grokipedia.comis growing</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0a302a4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Democrats want to legalize all illegals, which would turn all swing state blue immediately and ensu...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/934bf7b7</link>
      <description>"Democrats want to legalize all illegals, which would turn all swing state blue immediately and ensure permanent one-party rule in America!" 一 Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_934bf7b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: "The Democrats… [are] paying [illegals] to come here and then turning them into voters… T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cb3d9efd</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: "The Democrats… [are] paying [illegals] to come here and then turning them into voters… This is why the Democrats are so upset… if we turn off this gigantic money magnet for illegal immigrants, then they will leave and they'll lose voters."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cb3d9efd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok (xAI) is no longer chasing the market — it’s defining it. 📊 40.3% OpenRouter LLM market share 🔥...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2f8cef95</link>
      <description>Grok (xAI) is no longer chasing the market — it’s defining it. 📊 40.3% OpenRouter LLM market share 🔥 2.85 TRILLION tokens processed 🏆 Clear #1 by a massive margin This isn’t incremental growth. This is dominance powered by real usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2f8cef95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I've been noting scams like what the Somalis in Minnesota are doing as a major source of fraudulent ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9cd5a488</link>
      <description>I've been noting scams like what the Somalis in Minnesota are doing as a major source of fraudulent autism diagnoses for a while now. So much of the apparent 'autism epidemic' is this style of grift.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9cd5a488</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Asmongold goes off on the Minnesota Somali Daycare fraud and how wealthy Americans (and Hasan) defen...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b053338a</link>
      <description>Asmongold goes off on the Minnesota Somali Daycare fraud and how wealthy Americans (and Hasan) defend it: "Average Americans are tired of having their country rotted out, looted, pillaged by a bunch of random f-ing 3rd worlders and then asked to apologize for it because of something that happened before we were born." "It's outrageous. These insulated, generally white liberals who live in gate communities...they never have to see it."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b053338a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: When Elon made a hand gesture in passion, they wrote hundreds of articles calling him racist When So...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2fd321ed</link>
      <description>When Elon made a hand gesture in passion, they wrote hundreds of articles calling him racist When Somalis steal billions of dollars, they call the people who are upset racist It appears that the best way to loot the country is to call everyone racist</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2fd321ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie availab...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d8e32a22</link>
      <description>My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie available to subscribers. I recommend taking this approach for text/image/video content on 𝕏.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d8e32a22</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
