<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-08 19:33 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:33:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink is not allowed to have an Internet provider license in South Africa for the sole reason tha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6aa6875a</link>
      <description>Starlink is not allowed to have an Internet provider license in South Africa for the sole reason that I am not Black. This is not ok.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6aa6875a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Palantir cofounder Peter Thiel on echo chambers and why people left the left: “At some point, the ne...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0e79d48b</link>
      <description>Palantir cofounder Peter Thiel on echo chambers and why people left the left: “At some point, the need to be in lockstep was too much.” “If you have to have a full-frontal lobotomy to remain a democrat in good standing, it’s too much.” Via@RubinReport</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0e79d48b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok is hitting all time high usage. Massive global demand is driving Grok to the #1 rank ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/607b09ff</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok is hitting all time high usage. Massive global demand is driving Grok to the #1 rank and making it one of the most downloaded apps across multiple countries worldwide. xAI team is bringing additional compute online in real time to support the continued growth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_607b09ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They really hate humor. That’s one way to tell who the good guys are: who has the best sense of humo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d0b68bd5</link>
      <description>They really hate humor. That’s one way to tell who the good guys are: who has the best sense of humor?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d0b68bd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk “California's going to need a crisis to have deregulation and delitigation. The two entiti...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dcd23090</link>
      <description>Elon Musk “California's going to need a crisis to have deregulation and delitigation. The two entities that most control the Democratic Party are the unions and, secondarily, the plaintiff bar, basically, the lawyers that sue, especially class action. That's who controls the Democratic Party. Anyone who's familiar with the inside baseball of this will agree with me. This is, in fact, the case, especially in California.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dcd23090</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Suicidal empathy for the criminals, but apathy for the victims is the epitome of cruelty</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ce3b4440</link>
      <description>Suicidal empathy for the criminals, but apathy for the victims is the epitome of cruelty</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ce3b4440</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is #1 in more and more countries</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/22a7501b</link>
      <description>Grok is #1 in more and more countries</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_22a7501b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨DOGE BREAKING: DOGE has updated its website, estimated savings are now $215 billion.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/38404c4b</link>
      <description>🚨DOGE BREAKING: DOGE has updated its website, estimated savings are now $215 billion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_38404c4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Engineering is magic Starship is the first ever rocket designed to take us to Mars.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b6b884c7</link>
      <description>Engineering is magic Starship is the first ever rocket designed to take us to Mars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b6b884c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk@elonmusk, who co-founded and invested in an open source, non-profit OpenAI ~$50 million: I...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/247cc8df</link>
      <description>Elon Musk@elonmusk, who co-founded and invested in an open source, non-profit OpenAI ~$50 million: I AM THE REASON OpenAI EXISTS “I am the reason OpenAI exists... I used to be a close friend with Larry Page, and I was staying at his house, and we'd have these conversations long into the evening about AI, and I would be constantly urging him to be careful about the danger of AI. And he was really not concerned about the danger of AI and was quite cavalier about it. And at the time, Google, especially after the acquisition of DeepMind, had three-quarters of the world's AI talent; they had a lot of computers, a lot of money, so it was a unipolar world for AI. And we got a unipolar world, but the person who controls that does not, or at least did not seem to be concerned about AI safety. That sounded like a real problem. The final straw was Larry calling me a speciest for being a pro-human consciousness instead of machine consciousness, and I like, 'Well, yes, I guess I am a speciest.' I came up with the name [OpenAI], which refers to open source. The intent was to what is the opposite of Google, would be an open source non-profit, because Google is closed source profit, and that profit motivation could be dangerous... It does seem weird that something can be a nonprofit, open source, and somehow transform itself into a for-profit, closed source. I mean, this would be like, let's say you founded the organization to save the Amazon rainforest, but instead, they became a lumber company and chopped down the forest and sold it for money. And you'd be, therefore, like, 'Wait a second, that's the exact opposite of what I gave the money for. Is that legal?' That doesn't seem legal. And if, in general, it is legal to start a company as a non-profit and then take the IP and transfer it to a for-profit that then makes tons of money, shouldn't everyone start? Shouldn't that be the default? And I also think it is important to understand, like when push comes to shove, let's say they do create some digital super intelligence, almost Godlike intelligence, well, who is in control, and what is exactly the relationship between OpenAI and Microsoft? And I do worry that Microsoft actually may be more in control than the leadership team at OpenAI realizes. I mean, Microsoft, as part of Microsoft Investment, has rights to all of the software, all of the model weights, and everything necessary to run the inference system. At any point, Microsoft could cut off OpenAI.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_247cc8df</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk was right He BLASTS Dems: 'Biggest voter fraud in history!' Illegals on Social Security DO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e4df973d</link>
      <description>Elon Musk was right He BLASTS Dems: 'Biggest voter fraud in history!' Illegals on Social Security DOUBLING yearly. Dem operatives 'farm votes' with fake IDs — utility bills, school IDs — get SSNs, hit voter rolls. This is why we need Voter ID!”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e4df973d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: South Africa is blocking Starlink solely because Elon Musk is not Black. This is not regulation, it ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7e30e706</link>
      <description>South Africa is blocking Starlink solely because Elon Musk is not Black. This is not regulation, it is discrimination, and it is shameful</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7e30e706</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk :"Whenever there’s some sort of natural disaster somewhere, we always provide people with ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/33d8994c</link>
      <description>Elon Musk :"Whenever there’s some sort of natural disaster somewhere, we always provide people with free Starlink internet connectivity We don’t want to take advantage of a tragic situation "If there’s a natural disaster, it’s free during the disaster" We don’t want to put a paywall up while somebody is trying to get help. That would be wrong"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_33d8994c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Today would be a good day to start listening to Charlie Kirk.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8904a9f5</link>
      <description>Today would be a good day to start listening to Charlie Kirk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8904a9f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk. People just don't understand that solar is everything. “People just don't understand that...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bb7c9b0f</link>
      <description>Elon Musk. People just don't understand that solar is everything. “People just don't understand that solar is everything. Compared to the sun, all other energy sources are like cavemen throwing some twigs into a fire. The sun is over 99.8% of all mass in the solar system. Jupiter is around 0.1% of the mass. So, even if you burnt Jupiter, the energy produced by the sun would still round up to 100%. And then if you teleported three more Jupiters into our solar system and burnt them too, the sun still rounds up to 100% of energy.” From: Discussion with Peter Diamandis and Dave Blundin, January 6, 2026</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bb7c9b0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The judge said there’s "plenty of evidence" OpenAI broke its promise to stay non-profit</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d8b6f692</link>
      <description>The judge said there’s "plenty of evidence" OpenAI broke its promise to stay non-profit</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d8b6f692</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is great</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9c8f2c84</link>
      <description>This is great</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9c8f2c84</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wow, Frey is super deep in the fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3a661d7b</link>
      <description>Wow, Frey is super deep in the fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3a661d7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “The Department of Homeland Security will continue to operate on the ground in Minnesota — not only ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e8dcf3f9</link>
      <description>“The Department of Homeland Security will continue to operate on the ground in Minnesota — not only to remove criminal illegal aliens, but also to continue conducting door-to-door investigations of the rampant fraud that has taken place in the state...”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e8dcf3f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the only way to stop civilizational suicide. It is critical that we take these steps to avoi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/257f5d2c</link>
      <description>This is the only way to stop civilizational suicide. It is critical that we take these steps to avoid annihilation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_257f5d2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
