<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-08 17:59 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This clown,@Jacob_Frey, is an affront to honour, dignity, decency, and masculinity. He is the poster...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2c5871e5</link>
      <description>This clown,@Jacob_Frey, is an affront to honour, dignity, decency, and masculinity. He is the poster child of the West's death spiral.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2c5871e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Guys guys guys, Everybody calm down, She was only trying to run over ice agents, it’s not like she w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0385314f</link>
      <description>Guys guys guys, Everybody calm down, She was only trying to run over ice agents, it’s not like she was doing something crazy like speaking freely on a Utah college campus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0385314f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Minneapolis is a literal circus. I stand with ICE.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ca0f1631</link>
      <description>Minneapolis is a literal circus. I stand with ICE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ca0f1631</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is how the average leftist reacted to the death of Charlie Kirk, so spare me the sympathy for a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1d9d82a8</link>
      <description>This is how the average leftist reacted to the death of Charlie Kirk, so spare me the sympathy for a domestic terrorist who attempted to kill an ICE agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1d9d82a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: 𝕏 is officially the #1 news app in Austria 𝕏 is the most unbiased and trusted news source ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/163749b0</link>
      <description>BREAKING: 𝕏 is officially the #1 news app in Austria 𝕏 is the most unbiased and trusted news source in the world</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_163749b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just a reminder, many of these people laughed and even celebrated when Charlie Kirk was murdered in ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ae23a4be</link>
      <description>Just a reminder, many of these people laughed and even celebrated when Charlie Kirk was murdered in cold blood. Now they’re outraged about a girl getting shot by law enforcement after she broke the law repeatedly. She: Obstructed federal law enforcement. Ignored commands to get out of her vehicle Aggressively accelerated and hit an agent with her vehicle before she was shot. The left is NOT the party of law and order. Nor do they seem to care about right or wrong.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ae23a4be</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The mayor of Minneapolis is a virtue signaling joke. He’s more focused on ICE for legally enforcing ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4e07ca32</link>
      <description>The mayor of Minneapolis is a virtue signaling joke. He’s more focused on ICE for legally enforcing our immigration law than he is his own citizens breaking the law and obstructing ICE. It’s backwards. He should be telling people to stay out of ICE’s way and comply. Instead he’s attacking ICE for doing its job..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4e07ca32</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They stopped being funny long ago</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/da7e1f04</link>
      <description>They stopped being funny long ago</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_da7e1f04</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Beautiful</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4ef3de2f</link>
      <description>Beautiful</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4ef3de2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "Confiscation of land from anyone who isn’t Black was formally passed into law in South A...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ce9892e9</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "Confiscation of land from anyone who isn’t Black was formally passed into law in South Africa. That is where America is headed if not stopped."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ce9892e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I send you all the best thoughts in the world. Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0c931478</link>
      <description>I send you all the best thoughts in the world. Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0c931478</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Heavy usage growth of@Grokis causing occasional slowdowns in responses. Additional computers are bei...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e8c83825</link>
      <description>Heavy usage growth of@Grokis causing occasional slowdowns in responses. Additional computers are being brought online as I type this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e8c83825</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Our friend@jgebbiais doing amazing work as the Chief Design Officer of the USA. Proud to support his...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e500fdb0</link>
      <description>Our friend@jgebbiais doing amazing work as the Chief Design Officer of the USA. Proud to support his team along with others - they are working on hundreds of key government sites, and just getting going!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e500fdb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The facts are there for anyone to observe. South Africa now has more anti-White laws than there were...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/80fea778</link>
      <description>The facts are there for anyone to observe. South Africa now has more anti-White laws than there were anti-Black laws under Apartheid! I am extremely opposed to anti-Black laws, but equally opposed to the laws against White people or other races too. There should be a fair and even playing field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_80fea778</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink is not allowed to have an Internet provider license in South Africa for the sole reason tha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b936a942</link>
      <description>Starlink is not allowed to have an Internet provider license in South Africa for the sole reason that I am not Black. This is not ok.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b936a942</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Palantir cofounder Peter Thiel on echo chambers and why people left the left: “At some point, the ne...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f664b360</link>
      <description>Palantir cofounder Peter Thiel on echo chambers and why people left the left: “At some point, the need to be in lockstep was too much.” “If you have to have a full-frontal lobotomy to remain a democrat in good standing, it’s too much.” Via@RubinReport</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f664b360</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok is hitting all time high usage. Massive global demand is driving Grok to the #1 rank ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4e096b79</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok is hitting all time high usage. Massive global demand is driving Grok to the #1 rank and making it one of the most downloaded apps across multiple countries worldwide. xAI team is bringing additional compute online in real time to support the continued growth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4e096b79</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the only way to stop civilizational suicide. It is critical that we take these steps to avoi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/257f5d2c</link>
      <description>This is the only way to stop civilizational suicide. It is critical that we take these steps to avoid annihilation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_257f5d2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
