<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-31 09:46 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:46:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is a must download. It’s the most resourceful tool on my phone. There isn’t a day that I don’t ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b2a3d197</link>
      <description>Grok is a must download. It’s the most resourceful tool on my phone. There isn’t a day that I don’t use it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b2a3d197</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Only about 6 months ago, Giga Berlin produced the 8 millionth vehicle globally and now we hit the 9 ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/157a9ca0</link>
      <description>Only about 6 months ago, Giga Berlin produced the 8 millionth vehicle globally and now we hit the 9 million vehicles milestone! Insane accomplishment by our 4 factories around the globe! Cannot wait for the 10 millionth car to be produced!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_157a9ca0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s this simple, folks: stop all illegal immigration. Deport all illegal aliens here now. Enact Vot...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a3b79dc9</link>
      <description>It’s this simple, folks: stop all illegal immigration. Deport all illegal aliens here now. Enact Voter ID laws. That will solve every problem America has. We will reduce taxes, stop crime, fraud, Democrat DEI scams, inflation, homelessness, and the housing crisis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a3b79dc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the way</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d23c0dbd</link>
      <description>This is the way</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d23c0dbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Turning off payments and forcing verification before taxpayer money flows out the door is one of the...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ca41d837</link>
      <description>Turning off payments and forcing verification before taxpayer money flows out the door is one of the most important steps we can take to end the fraud in Minnesota. But there will be many more to come. Great job to@HHS_Jimand@SecKennedy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ca41d837</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grandma, you rock</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/032c59e6</link>
      <description>Grandma, you rock</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_032c59e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Once we restore honest elections in America—Every. Other. Problem. Is. Solved.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7b111ee</link>
      <description>Once we restore honest elections in America—Every. Other. Problem. Is. Solved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7b111ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s not "white supremacy" to investigate fraud. This attack no longer works.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d06e7311</link>
      <description>It’s not "white supremacy" to investigate fraud. This attack no longer works.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d06e7311</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the harrowing reality of what detransitioners face, says@ChloeCole: “The moment that I detra...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cd2dece3</link>
      <description>This is the harrowing reality of what detransitioners face, says@ChloeCole: “The moment that I detransitioned, I was human garbage to them. I was subhuman even. … They told me: ‘This is all your fault. Don't put this on us. You were the one who said yes, you were the one who wanted this. You were a complete idiot for not knowing that you weren't truly transgender. So don't come crying to us. And you should shut up about this because you might scare somebody out of getting the care that they really need. And you are a waste of resources. You are a waste of the love and support of your family. You didn't deserve the support of your doctors. You didn't deserve any of this. So stay quiet and stop being a problem.’ …There were people who were trying to compel me to retransition, people who were trying to tell me to kill myself, even just for the fact that I was going against the dogma. And I stayed low for a little bit. I apologized to the same people who were abusing me because I was a freshly traumatized 16 year old girl. I had been bullied in school before, but nobody had ever treated me this horribly over such a painful part of my life. But after a while of being painfully isolated. I started to really think the way that they are treating me is not deserved. I'm speaking to nothing but my experience, to the way that I feel and to reality. I'm going to speak up, regardless of whether they want me to or not. And I just knew that there had to be other detransitioners out there. And very quickly, I learned that they were in the thousands. And I'm sure that it's doubled, tripled, quadrupled over the years, the amount of us who are out there. We are never going to know the real numbers. …And some of the harassment, the hatred I faced over the years has gotten worse. I've been doxxed. I have had people assaulting me, chasing after me in government buildings, who have tried to hurt me, who have wished death upon me.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cd2dece3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Everybody needs to stop caring about being called a racist. It's been absolutely weaponized. It mean...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/17681430</link>
      <description>Everybody needs to stop caring about being called a racist. It's been absolutely weaponized. It means nothing now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_17681430</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is why I sought and achieved the repeal of in-state tuition for illegals (which was enacted pri...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ff6f2d4</link>
      <description>This is why I sought and achieved the repeal of in-state tuition for illegals (which was enacted prior to my tenure). It rewards illegal entry but also treats an illegal alien better than a US citizen from 49 other states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ff6f2d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia launched just 2 months ago with ~885K articles It has now crossed 1.7M+ Articles 73K+ Gro...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a9766b11</link>
      <description>Grokipedia launched just 2 months ago with ~885K articles It has now crossed 1.7M+ Articles 73K+ Grok-approved edits Try Grokipedia today Strongly recommend it to your friends and family as a truth-first encyclopedia</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a9766b11</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: South Korea Hits Record Low Fertility in 2025 – Demographic Crisis Deepens to Historic Wor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/14865163</link>
      <description>BREAKING: South Korea Hits Record Low Fertility in 2025 – Demographic Crisis Deepens to Historic Worst! South Korea’s Total Fertility Rate (TFR) has plummeted over 70 years, but 2025 marks the worst year yet, with preliminary data showing a continued decline amid the world’s most acute population crisis. Key Historical TFR Trends: • 1950s–1960: ~6.0–6.3 (post-war peak) • 1970: 4.2 • 1980: 2.8 • 1990s: 1.6–1.8 • 2000s: ~1.2 • 2020: 0.84 • 2023: 0.72 (previous record low) • 2024: Slight rebound to ~0.75 • 2025: Ongoing decline in projections, hitting a new historic nadir despite monthly birth fluctuations From over 6 children per woman in the 1950s to below 0.8 today, this is one of the sharpest global drops – warning of population halving by 2100 if unchecked. Persistent challenges make 2025 the bleakest in South Korea’s fertility history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_14865163</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine prompt: monochromatic black and white image in a cyberpunk anime art style, blending fu...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ccdc0a1</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine prompt: monochromatic black and white image in a cyberpunk anime art style, blending futuristic and mechanical character elements, with an intricately detailed character design inspired by Shiguroi Suijima, featuring a female cyborg character with a serious expression, her face partially covered by a sleek, reflective visor with faint, glowing crimson circuitry, shown as a close-up portrait focusing on her upper body and face, with a subtle, high-contrast chiaroscuro lighting effect highlighting her angular features, framed in a dynamic diagonal composition that enhances her futuristic aura</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ccdc0a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Last year today,grok.comwas opened for early access Over the following days, it rolled out more broa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b9c44657</link>
      <description>Last year today,grok.comwas opened for early access Over the following days, it rolled out more broadly to users Fast forward to today: Grok gets well over 200M visits per month and growing So much progress in just one year</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b9c44657</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is essential</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/624258a7</link>
      <description>This is essential</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_624258a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Minnesota Fraud Scandal is merely the tip of the iceberg that is the Democrat-Immigration Corrup...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4bcd385a</link>
      <description>The Minnesota Fraud Scandal is merely the tip of the iceberg that is the Democrat-Immigration Corruption Complex.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4bcd385a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/723dfe9f</link>
      <description>xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try@Grok. Download latest app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_723dfe9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
