<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-17 21:52 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just asked the four Grok 4.20 (Beta) agents to build me an artificial life simulator. My mind is blo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48e9016b</link>
      <description>Just asked the four Grok 4.20 (Beta) agents to build me an artificial life simulator. My mind is blown. What should I get him to build next? &gt;&gt;&gt; grok prompt Build an artificial life simulator in one single HTML file. Hundreds of glowing neon particles in different cyberpunk colors. Each pair of colors has its own attraction/repulsion force that you control with sliders. You get emergent “creatures”, swarms, orbiting rings, exploding clusters, chasing packs, it feels alive. Features: - Click/drag to spawn particles of selected color - Real-time force matrix (6×6 sliders) - Randomize rules button (insane results every time) - Pause, speed, particle count, trails/glow toggle - Dark cyberpunk UI with scanlines + glitch effects optional</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48e9016b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Grok 4.2 release candidate (public beta) is now available for use. You need to select it specifi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/df1441ed</link>
      <description>The Grok 4.2 release candidate (public beta) is now available for use. You need to select it specifically. Critical feedback is appreciated. Unlike prior versions of Grok, 4.2 is able to learn rapidly, so there will be improvements every week with release notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_df1441ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Congratulations to the Tesla team on making the first production Cybercab!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/89c1c8e6</link>
      <description>Congratulations to the Tesla team on making the first production Cybercab!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_89c1c8e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is most physically accurate of the four. Opus rear bike frame makes no sense structurally, ther...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/84fec834</link>
      <description>Grok is most physically accurate of the four. Opus rear bike frame makes no sense structurally, there is no connection from pedals to rear wheel, both legs of Pelican are on the right side of the bike and handle bars are disconnected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_84fec834</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.2 will be about an order of magnitude smarter and faster than Grok 4 when the public beta con...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0e4bf8f1</link>
      <description>Grok 4.2 will be about an order of magnitude smarter and faster than Grok 4 when the public beta concludes next month. Still many bug fixes and improvements landing every day. The public beta gives us more critical feedback to address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0e4bf8f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Right wing groups used Asian students to challenge race discrimination in college admissions because...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b2e68ffc</link>
      <description>Right wing groups used Asian students to challenge race discrimination in college admissions because it’s taboo for White people to actually advocate for ourselves openly. This taboo must be destroyed. Anyone trying to weasel around this core issue is part of the problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b2e68ffc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is genuinely fun to use Love that new model smell</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1ece10d1</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is genuinely fun to use Love that new model smell</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1ece10d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Predicting the future accurately is the best measure of intelligence</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dd5fb21e</link>
      <description>Predicting the future accurately is the best measure of intelligence</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dd5fb21e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is funny, based &amp; smart 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5e7c906d</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is funny, based &amp; smart 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5e7c906d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OpenAI quietly dropped "safely" and "no financial motive" from its mission</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/98e73e27</link>
      <description>OpenAI quietly dropped "safely" and "no financial motive" from its mission</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_98e73e27</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is ridiculously good. Multiple agents push it into another league.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4affd691</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is ridiculously good. Multiple agents push it into another league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4affd691</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You can just take a picture of your medical data or upload the file to get a second opinion from Gro...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5f503190</link>
      <description>You can just take a picture of your medical data or upload the file to get a second opinion from Grok</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5f503190</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: True words</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a6868f4a</link>
      <description>True words</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a6868f4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Population collapse has been underway for many years</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ce3b1400</link>
      <description>Population collapse has been underway for many years</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ce3b1400</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: What do you think of the Grok 4.20 answer?grok.com/share/bGVnYWN5_78e7…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7627e0d6</link>
      <description>What do you think of the Grok 4.20 answer?grok.com/share/bGVnYWN5_78e7…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7627e0d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The currently released Grok 4.20 is the "small" version with 500B parameters. Medium and Large versi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d5de8760</link>
      <description>The currently released Grok 4.20 is the "small" version with 500B parameters. Medium and Large versions of Grok 4.20 will follow later from@xai.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d5de8760</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You cannot spend decades treating a group as a collective “problem” and then act shocked when its me...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0b81db2d</link>
      <description>You cannot spend decades treating a group as a collective “problem” and then act shocked when its members begin to think in collective terms. The Left has consistently attacked the European roots of America, broadly labeling it “White culture,” while critiquing American institutions, history, and traditions as “White supremacy” and “privilege.” Yet they simultaneously celebrate and fund the group interests of their preferred racial and ethnic blocs. Congress openly organizes broad caucuses for Black, Hispanic, and Asian interests, but any advocacy for the group that laid America’s foundation is treated as uniquely illegitimate. This game is rigged. They strategically demand the break down of White identity into small sub-groups while they organize theirs into political monoliths. It’s heads they win, tails you lose.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0b81db2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cybercab, which has no pedals or steering wheel, starts production in April</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9425b973</link>
      <description>Cybercab, which has no pedals or steering wheel, starts production in April</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9425b973</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
