<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-07 17:00 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:00:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: No ID and mailing in ballots make fraud trivial. Both of those need to be fixed to restore democracy...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c60ab904</link>
      <description>No ID and mailing in ballots make fraud trivial. Both of those need to be fixed to restore democracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c60ab904</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Weird how the left never complains about this billionaire…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bb67dab5</link>
      <description>Weird how the left never complains about this billionaire…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bb67dab5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: basically imo the left has positioned themselves as the incompetent party, the party of smug moral s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/94ea30ec</link>
      <description>basically imo the left has positioned themselves as the incompetent party, the party of smug moral superiority where dissent and discussion isn’t tolerated, the party of optics over outcomes that party needs to level up their competence or complaining about trump lands flat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_94ea30ec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try and download the Grok app. It’s the most resourceful app and I don’t use Google Search anymore.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/66003bd6</link>
      <description>Try and download the Grok app. It’s the most resourceful app and I don’t use Google Search anymore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_66003bd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They know that mail in voting makes fraud trivial</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1686c111</link>
      <description>They know that mail in voting makes fraud trivial</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1686c111</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: &gt; Minnesota had $9b of fraud (so far) against an average annual expenditure of $54b &gt; Even if CA is ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/93166b4f</link>
      <description>&gt; Minnesota had $9b of fraud (so far) against an average annual expenditure of $54b &gt; Even if CA is *only* the same % fraud as MN, that would be $69b of fraud &gt; that would make CA fraud &gt;&gt; than the entire budget of MN &gt; California has more NGO's, more welfare, and a track record of absolute incompetence Just remember the $100b "railway to nowhere". Buckle up</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_93166b4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI raised $20B in a Series E that was targeting $15B 600M monthly active users. 1M+ H100 GPU equiva...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/55ed06b0</link>
      <description>xAI raised $20B in a Series E that was targeting $15B 600M monthly active users. 1M+ H100 GPU equivalents. Grok 5 already in training. The AI race is getting wild.x.ai/news/series-e</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_55ed06b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Make beautiful videos with@Grok</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9f866cdf</link>
      <description>Make beautiful videos with@Grok</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9f866cdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And here it is: More damning declassified documents and emails released by@CIADirectorreveal Hillary...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bd64d813</link>
      <description>And here it is: More damning declassified documents and emails released by@CIADirectorreveal Hillary Clinton conspired with the intelligence community and George Soros to overthrow the United States government in 2016: Documents declassified by CIA Director John Ratcliffe—at the Olympic level. Emails from George Soros’ Open Society Terrorist Foundation: “It will be a long-term affair to demonize Putin and Trump,” approved by HRC—Hillary Rodham Clinton—“to tie Trump to Russia as a means of distracting people from her own missing emails, especially if the affair reaches an Olympic level. For now, it serves to provide a post-convention bounce. Later, the FBI will be right there to add more oil to the fire.” In other words—yes indeed—Barack Hussein Obama was right there, taking it to the Olympic level by ordering a newly manufactured ICA report—as part of a seditious conspiracy to overthrow the United States government in 2016 and a long-term effort to overthrow the duly elected president of the United States@realDonaldTrumpin 2017. Followed by two impeachments, multiple investigations, arrests, indictments, raids, two assassination attempts, and ultimately, the overthrow of the U.S. government in 2020. Any questions?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bd64d813</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Somali Man in Ohio Says "America Will Become a Muslim State!...Our Goal is to Make America Islamic!"...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/951d8e93</link>
      <description>Somali Man in Ohio Says "America Will Become a Muslim State!...Our Goal is to Make America Islamic!" At the Global Mall in Columbus, Ohio, we saw a poster that said "NO ICE." After we took a photo of the poster, we were swarmed. This is what happened. Follow@realmuckraker</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_951d8e93</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: New version of Grok Imagine just dropped. Update your app.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/933f8022</link>
      <description>New version of Grok Imagine just dropped. Update your app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_933f8022</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good Morning, 𝕏. Try the new 'Club Beats' template on Grok Imagine.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8e4b2f22</link>
      <description>Good Morning, 𝕏. Try the new 'Club Beats' template on Grok Imagine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8e4b2f22</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Some people really do</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ca41def</link>
      <description>Some people really do</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ca41def</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI moves fast. Don’t miss the train. Update your Grok app to version 1.3.30.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cd4d225b</link>
      <description>xAI moves fast. Don’t miss the train. Update your Grok app to version 1.3.30.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cd4d225b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Prompt Share: Highly detailed fantasy portrait of a beautiful young woman with long dark hair elegan...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9a0a8595</link>
      <description>Prompt Share: Highly detailed fantasy portrait of a beautiful young woman with long dark hair elegantly styled, adorned with intricate gold jewelry and a floral headdress featuring large pink and gold flowers, wearing an opulent black corset gown with elaborate gold embroidery, pink floral accents, voluminous petal like shoulder details, long black sleeves sparkling with gold elements, luxurious baroque style, dramatic lighting, ethereal atmosphere, intricate details, masterpiece, ultra realistic digital art.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9a0a8595</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine 🤯</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bbffa905</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine 🤯</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bbffa905</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "When I was the most mentally ill I've ever been, I was super liberal."</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a1d591ae</link>
      <description>"When I was the most mentally ill I've ever been, I was super liberal."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a1d591ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Grok It’s unbelievably good and actually fun to use</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ab4b816b</link>
      <description>Try Grok It’s unbelievably good and actually fun to use</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ab4b816b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: VEGAS LOOP: ELON’S UNDERGROUND NETWORK IS EXPANDING FASTER THAN ANYONE EXPECTED The Boring Company’s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a9f59670</link>
      <description>VEGAS LOOP: ELON’S UNDERGROUND NETWORK IS EXPANDING FASTER THAN ANYONE EXPECTED The Boring Company’s Vegas Loop is no longer just a novelty, it’s quietly becoming the fastest-growing transit system in the U.S. •⁠ ⁠5 miles and 5 stations in 2022 has exploded to 70+ miles and 93 stations approved •⁠ ⁠Currently connects the Las Vegas Convention Center, Resorts World, and multiple hotels with zero above-ground traffic •⁠ ⁠Tunnels take less time to permit and build than any public infrastructure in Vegas history •⁠ ⁠More than 2M rides completed with Teslas since launch No traffic, no stoplights, just Teslas in tunnels, and it’s working. Source:@boringcompany,@Tesla,@elonmusk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a9f59670</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
