<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-28 09:36 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:36:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8f21b019</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8f21b019</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Not even CBS? Hmm.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ce7af7a6</link>
      <description>Not even CBS? Hmm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ce7af7a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: why not just raise income tax rates? because your real intent is not to just “provide healthcare”. y...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/be49ea27</link>
      <description>why not just raise income tax rates? because your real intent is not to just “provide healthcare”. you’re masking that you are proposing the creation of, for the first time in the 250 years of this American republic, an organized government seizure of private property from citizens. you’re calling it a “wealth tax” or a “billionaires tax” or “millionaires tax” or whatever nom du jour polls well. but at the end of the day, it’s the seizure of private property from citizens by the government. citizens that earned money, paid their fair taxes on those earnings (53% if they live in California) and are now being told they need to hand over after-tax assets because the government has failed to provide promised services with the revenue it’s collected, and are now re-casting their own failure to be a socio-economic inequity that must be justly resolved... a slippery slope that has never gone anywhere good (see economic effects in USSR, Cuba, Venezuela, France and Norway wealth tax etc.) the American founders fled tyranny in Europe and this amazing nation was populated by immigrants (myself and your parents) from around the world not just looking for a “better life” but for a place where they could have freedom from tyrannical governments that can take what they want from private citizens. a great nation borne of property rights, the rule of law, and endowed freedoms to believe, speak, or act. these principles led to the greatest run of innovations, successes, and widespread increase in prosperity, for all citizens, ever seen. the citizens, the individuals, not the institutions, delivered this progress. those who invented, who toiled, who bled, who sacrificed, who took risk and persevered, who led, and who changed the world, are not charlatans, kleptocrats, or oligarchs. they’re what made us all better off. prosperity is a measure of america’s success, not its failure. it is your principle that is so offensive, as evidenced by the broad disdain for your flippant flirtation with the darkest of human fantasy - socialism. you and other neo-socialists have led so many of us to reflect on America’s history and what it is becoming. that now leads so many to consider, so unnecessarily, leaving their homes for a place where everyone stands up to shout down the principle you suggest. because if your ideas are now considered moderate, it’s clear this titanic is sinking. that a “simple tax” of taking assets that have been earned, through toil and tribulation, rightly taxed, and preserved, should now be unjustly seized, is your solution to a problem of obvious government mismanagement and outright fraud, tells us that your true motivation lies not in giving people healthcare but in cutting down success and deleting the system of prosperity and opportunity for all. i don’t care, and neither should anyone else, what the sum total market value of a private citizens private assets might be. it is none of my business and should be none of yours. because, again, once you open that pandora’s box, we might as well study Lord of the Flies … there is literally nothing stopping 51% of citizens demanding that their government go out and seize 100% of the private property of the 49%. want to give healthcare to people in need? do your job and fix healthcare. make it affordable. want to be lazy about it? then do your job lazily and raise income taxes. want to take private property from private citizens who have paid their fair share of taxes and legally earned their property, then honestly declare that it is envy, not inequity, that you strive to resolve…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_be49ea27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Any memetic structure that inhibits biological reproduction must necessarily transfer to the minds o...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b54f9378</link>
      <description>Any memetic structure that inhibits biological reproduction must necessarily transfer to the minds of those who do reproduce or it will die out. They target the youth especially, because their mental firewalls are not yet strong.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b54f9378</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This 25-year-old illegal migrant from Mali stabbed 3 women, including a pregnant one, on the Paris s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/df855854</link>
      <description>This 25-year-old illegal migrant from Mali stabbed 3 women, including a pregnant one, on the Paris subway yesterday. The attacker had previously been sentenced for sexual assault and had been issued a deportation order earlier this year. As usual, his deportation wasn’t executed due to lack of consular documents, and he was released from migrant detention after the maximum retention period and allowed to roam the streets. 🇫🇷🇲🇱</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_df855854</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Zoolander irl 😂😢</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/89b19434</link>
      <description>Zoolander irl 😂😢</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_89b19434</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Word of the year</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0ead9b35</link>
      <description>Word of the year</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0ead9b35</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Significant net negative</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a07a250d</link>
      <description>Significant net negative</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a07a250d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Someone should write an alternate historical novel where Americans are the first to master the autom...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8043fc88</link>
      <description>Someone should write an alternate historical novel where Americans are the first to master the automobile, the first in flight, the first to harness the atom, the first to land on the moon — but just keep going and never open our borders to the entire third world for sixty years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8043fc88</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 SOMALI BALLOT HARVESTING EXPOSÉ IN MINNESOTA WAS SUPPRESSED... THEN THE FRAUD EXPLODED In Septemb...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/123b96af</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 SOMALI BALLOT HARVESTING EXPOSÉ IN MINNESOTA WAS SUPPRESSED... THEN THE FRAUD EXPLODED In September 2020, James O'Keefe's Project Veritas dropped undercover footage alleging a massive ballot-harvesting racket in Ilhan Omar's Minneapolis district. Paid operatives illegally scooped absentee ballots from elderly Somali immigrants, stuffing envelopes and even bragging on Snapchat about hauling 300 for City Council hopeful Jamal Osman. Whistleblower Omar Jamal spilled that it was an "open secret," with Omar's crew like staffer Ali Gainey coordinating the cash-fueled scheme, exploiting vulnerable folks for DFL power plays. But media "fact-checkers" swarmed, branding it racist kryptonite without debunking evidence, cops claimed no proof, and the story vanished like the Hunter laptop weeks later. NY Post's Miranda Devine got hammered for covering it, yet fraud festered: Fast-forward to 2025, and Minnesota's drowning in $9B+ Somali-linked scams from Feeding Our Future to Medicaid ghost services, same MO of milking taxpayer programs for riches and votes. Why does it keep happening? Incentives galore, lax election laws, unchecked welfare flows, and bloc voting power keep the cycle spinning for crooks and pols. Govt needs to gut 'em: Enforce strict voter ID, audit programs ruthlessly, tie aid to citizenship/residency checks, and deport fraudsters. Slash the rewards, kill the motivation, or watch the "3rd world" playbook swallow more states. Source: NY Post (2020), CBS News, FOX9,@mirandadevine,@JamesOKeefeIII</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_123b96af</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The prospect of a state income tax on millionaires has already got some of the state's richer reside...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0cd96ebf</link>
      <description>The prospect of a state income tax on millionaires has already got some of the state's richer residents talking about leaving. History says it's mostly just talk.st.news/49a3A39</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0cd96ebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Mass migration from the third world is a pro-rape policy.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1c3bf9ae</link>
      <description>Mass migration from the third world is a pro-rape policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1c3bf9ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Any elected official that puts foreigners before their citizens is committing treason against their ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8ecf0131</link>
      <description>Any elected official that puts foreigners before their citizens is committing treason against their country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8ecf0131</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Racist” is just a magic spell to make you stop objecting to the surrender of your nations. Luckily ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ce632a7</link>
      <description>“Racist” is just a magic spell to make you stop objecting to the surrender of your nations. Luckily some of its wielders, like this guy, are clumsy enough to make this obvious, even to normies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ce632a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cool@Starlink</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/21f7b604</link>
      <description>Cool@Starlink</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_21f7b604</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: As I was saying …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d0847f31</link>
      <description>As I was saying …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d0847f31</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Awesome</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2b1b47d7</link>
      <description>Awesome</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2b1b47d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7b28166</link>
      <description>The radical left has been using fraudulent government programs for a long time to import and retain vast numbers of illegal (and legal, in some cases) immigrants to win elections and turn America into a single-party state, destroying any real democracy. The more you look at it, the more you will be horrified at what your tax money is doing and the fact that, if this is not reversed, your vote will mean nothing. The most obvious case example is the Somali voting bloc in Minnesota, a state that historically had zero Somalis, electing Ilhan Omar to the US Congress. The same is happening in Europe, UK, Canada, Australia and New Zealand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7b28166</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
