<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-14 07:08 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:08:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨JOHN CLEESE SAYS BBC ARE "DISGRACEFUL" FOR IGNORING RAPE GANG INQUIRY Couldn't agree with you more ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bd08d2c9</link>
      <description>🚨JOHN CLEESE SAYS BBC ARE "DISGRACEFUL" FOR IGNORING RAPE GANG INQUIRY Couldn't agree with you more John Defund the BBC 🚫</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bd08d2c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A great morning for human spaceflight. Congratulations to the teams at NASA, SpaceX, and our interna...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/625ae176</link>
      <description>A great morning for human spaceflight. Congratulations to the teams at NASA, SpaceX, and our international partners who worked tirelessly to launch Crew 12 safely on a journey to the International Space Station. If this is what is possible today, imagine what tomorrow will bring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_625ae176</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: From@WSJEditorial Board: "Such data would have shown the surge in what is alleged to be fake autism ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e2edc006</link>
      <description>From@WSJEditorial Board: "Such data would have shown the surge in what is alleged to be fake autism diagnoses and treatments in Minnesota that were billed by fly-by-night Medicaid providers."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e2edc006</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Medicaid data has been open sourced, so the level of fraud is easy to identify.@DOGEis not a departm...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b7af7ba0</link>
      <description>Medicaid data has been open sourced, so the level of fraud is easy to identify.@DOGEis not a department, it’s a state of mind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b7af7ba0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia traffic is surging worldwide. Website visits are now up 52.61% compared to last...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/309fc484</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia traffic is surging worldwide. Website visits are now up 52.61% compared to last month. Visits are rising sharply month over month, as per@SimilarwebKeep sharing Grokipedia links to defeat the Woke Wikipedia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_309fc484</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 1707, two thousand sailors DROWNED. Not because of a storm. Because nobody could tell where they ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9b611175</link>
      <description>In 1707, two thousand sailors DROWNED. Not because of a storm. Because nobody could tell where they were at sea 🇬🇧 This was the longitude problem. The deadliest puzzle in science. Parliament offered £20,000 to anyone who could solve it. Nearly four million today. Every great scientist in Europe tried. Newton. Halley. The finest minds alive. All of them failed. The man who solved it was a carpenter from Yorkshire. His name was John Harrison. No formal education. No university. No wealthy patron. He taught himself clockmaking. Built timepieces out of wood. His idea was “simple”. If you know the exact time at home and the exact time at sea, you can calculate exactly where you are. The problem? No clock could keep accurate time on a moving ship. Heat warps metal. Cold contracts it. The ocean never stops moving. Harrison spent DECADES on it. H1. Twenty years of work. Not good enough. H2. Better. Still not enough. H3. Seventeen years. Over 700 parts. Still not enough. Then he did something nobody expected. He stopped building clocks. He built a watch. H4. Thirteen centimetres across. The most important watch ever made. They sent it across the Atlantic. Eighty-one days at sea. When they arrived, it had lost five seconds. Five seconds. In eighty-one days. The problem was solved. But here's the uncomfortable part. They didn't give him the prize. The Board of Longitude was run by astronomers. The very men who'd been trying to solve it their own way. The Astronomer Royal was both judge and competitor. They changed the rules. Demanded his designs. Refused to pay. A working-class carpenter had beaten every astronomer in Europe. And the establishment couldn't accept it. Harrison was nearly EIGHTY before he got justice. He went directly to King George III. The king tested the watch himself and told Harrison to petition Parliament with the king's full backing. Parliament paid. Harrison died three years later. After his death, every ship on earth carried a chronometer based on his design. Every GPS satellite. Every ship's navigation. Every flight path. All of it traces back to a carpenter from Yorkshire who taught himself to build a watch. His watches are still at the Royal Observatory in Greenwich. Still ticking. Still perfect. The establishment tried to bury him once. We're not letting it happen again 👇proudofus.co.uk/supportBe part of us. Be proud of us. 🇬🇧</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9b611175</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Read this whole paragraph, then imagine trying to explain to a normal person??</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cbbd2a53</link>
      <description>Read this whole paragraph, then imagine trying to explain to a normal person??</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cbbd2a53</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink now at 10 million active users</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/78064470</link>
      <description>Starlink now at 10 million active users</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_78064470</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: While you were sleeping, SpaceX sent astronauts into space.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/849d2284</link>
      <description>While you were sleeping, SpaceX sent astronauts into space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_849d2284</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Falcon is the first orbital-class rocket capable of recovery and reuse. The first stage booster supp...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/96610fd1</link>
      <description>Falcon is the first orbital-class rocket capable of recovery and reuse. The first stage booster supporting this mission will complete the first landing at Landing Zone 40 at Cape Canaveral, our newest recovery site</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_96610fd1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨🇺🇸 REID HOFFMAN CLAIMS "THE FBI CLEARED ME" ON EPSTEIN... THE FILES SAY OTHERWISE Reid Hoffman is n...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/02bcb5a2</link>
      <description>🚨🇺🇸 REID HOFFMAN CLAIMS "THE FBI CLEARED ME" ON EPSTEIN... THE FILES SAY OTHERWISE Reid Hoffman is now claiming the FBI cleared him of any wrongdoing related to Epstein. Let's review what the files actually show: He visited Epstein's island in November 2014. Stayed at his Manhattan townhouse. Went to his New Mexico ranch. Weeks after Virginia Giuffre's sex trafficking allegations went public in December 2014, Hoffman sent Epstein Christmas gifts: ice cream for him or "for the girls" and "something that may strike your funny bone for the island." He sent Epstein a metal sculpture saying it would "have an appropriate nature to the island." Then he offered to help manage the scandal: "Been giving a bit of thought to how I can help with the recent press fu." He left his passport at Epstein's place in 2016. Continued meeting with him through 2018, despite previously claiming contact ended in 2015. There's a photo of him sitting at a table with Epstein. "Cleared" is doing a lot of heavy lifting here. The files show a man who knew about the allegations, kept visiting, sent gifts "for the girls," and offered PR help. I think the word he was looking for was ‘documented,’ not ‘cleared.’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_02bcb5a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Think in probabilities</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/26100d52</link>
      <description>Think in probabilities</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_26100d52</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Solar will utterly dominate future electricity production</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/99a88e66</link>
      <description>Solar will utterly dominate future electricity production</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_99a88e66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: x.com/i/article/202203119829…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/070d0c80</link>
      <description>x.com/i/article/202203119829…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_070d0c80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Reid Hoffman is lying. He has not been cleared by the FBI and should be investigated. - 1737 emails ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3c708ffd</link>
      <description>Reid Hoffman is lying. He has not been cleared by the FBI and should be investigated. - 1737 emails - Confirmed visits to the Epstein Island - Sent gifts to the island and “for the girls” - Stayed at Epstein’s island, Epstein’s ranch in New Mexico and Epstein’s house in New York. - Offered to help him with PR. - Lying about his relationship with Epstein - Maintained very close relationship with Epstein right up to the end. • July 2015: Epstein texts Hoffman praising his diet progress. Hoffman replies he's making "slow progress" and is "planning to see him in August." • April 2016: Dinner reservation at upscale Palo Alto sushi restaurant. • April 29, 2016: Scheduled meeting at MIT. • June 20, 2016: Skype call. • June 25, 2016: "Phone date." • July 24, 2016: In-person meeting in Bedford, NY. • Sept 30, 2017: Hoffman emails Epstein after hurricane hits USVI: "You good?" • March 24, 2018: One-on-one Skype call. • March 16, 2019: Google notification suggests possible meeting that morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3c708ffd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Katherine Boyle just identified Elon Musk’s most important contribution to America, and it has nothi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1f8a5169</link>
      <description>Katherine Boyle just identified Elon Musk’s most important contribution to America, and it has nothing to do with the products he shipped. Boyle, General Partner at a16z: “I think Elon’s most important contribution to this country is training two generations of engineers to work with their hands again.” For ten years, America’s sharpest technical minds optimized ad clicks and built messaging apps. Software consumed ambition. The physical world became something you abstracted into APIs, not something you touched or understood. Elon didn’t reverse that through inspiration. He reversed it by building companies that required understanding manufacturing or failing completely. SpaceX and Tesla forced engineers to learn how metal fractures, how tolerances cascade through systems, how physical iteration costs months and millions per failure. No debugging. No patches. Just physics that doesn’t negotiate. Boyle: “Training two generations of engineers.” The product isn’t the cars. It’s the people. Look at who’s founding America’s critical hard-tech companies now. The common thread isn’t Stanford or MIT. It’s time on factory floors at SpaceX or Tesla. They learned welding. They learned that “impossible” just means unsolved engineering, not violated physics. They learned failure in the physical domain where mistakes compound instead of reverting. Elon didn’t build companies. He accidentally rebuilt industrial knowledge that had been decaying for thirty years while America’s best minds chased digital scale. Boyle: “Work with their hands again.” Three words that sound quaint but describe a civilizational inflection point. Software dominated because it scaled infinitely at zero marginal cost. Physical manufacturing was slow, expensive, unfashionable. Building real things became what you did if you couldn’t code. Elon made atoms matter again. Made manufacturing the hardest problem worth solving. Made physical engineering prestigious in ways it hadn’t been since humans walked on the moon. The evidence is everywhere now. Technical talent that doesn’t default to “which app” but asks “which physical thing should exist that currently doesn’t.” Ambition redirected from optimizing engagement metrics to building rockets. From scaling users to scaling factories. From virtual products to physical infrastructure. That shift matters more than any vehicle or spacecraft Musk delivered. Products obsolesce. Redirecting an entire generation’s engineering ambition from digital to physical compounds across decades and rebuilds industrial capability at civilizational scale. We stopped just coding the future. We started machining it, welding it, breaking it in reality until physics confirms it works. That transformation from virtual to tangible ambition is reconstructing American manufacturing one engineer at a time. And those engineers are now training the next wave. The compounding has started. The School of Elon doesn’t need Elon anymore. It’s self-sustaining, spreading through an entire generation that learned building real things matters more than building virtual ones. That’s not just a business achievement. That’s a civilization remembering how to make things that matter in the physical world again. And it might be the only thing that saves American technological leadership when the competition is just building faster because they never forgot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1f8a5169</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Join Rupert Lowe in Restore Britain, because he is the only one who will actually do it!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ee48c343</link>
      <description>Join Rupert Lowe in Restore Britain, because he is the only one who will actually do it!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ee48c343</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: From 2021-2024, Democrats exercised total control over US immigration policy. They willfully create ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ac1534f5</link>
      <description>From 2021-2024, Democrats exercised total control over US immigration policy. They willfully create the largest and deadliest tsunami of illegal immigration, child sex trafficking, drug trafficking and gang infiltration in history. These are the Democrats now shutting down DHS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ac1534f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa93318c</link>
      <description>xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as quickly as xAI, the structure must evolve just like any living organism. This unfortunately required parting ways with some people. We wish them well in future endeavors. We are hiring aggressively. Join xAI if the idea of mass drivers on the Moon appeals to you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa93318c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
