<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-13 23:51 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:51:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If you're a journalist interested in telling a balanced narrative and want the 'pro' orbital data ce...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ba5384f1</link>
      <description>If you're a journalist interested in telling a balanced narrative and want the 'pro' orbital data centers logic/math, we've made it VERY VERY easy. These articles are all open and ungated. You can just grok them if you need help parsing the numbers. Please take the time to understand the math and physics behind the pro case before publishing the skeptic case as fact. Launch limiters and initial math -research.33fg.com/analysis/i…Energy Cost from space -research.33fg.com/analysis/o…Location for ODCs why SSO -research.33fg.com/analysis/w…Debunking the cooling/radiator problem -research.33fg.com/analysis/d…The ODC landscape/China's role -research.33fg.com/analysis/o…explaining the Chips for ODCs -research.33fg.com/analysis/e…We take pride in anchoring our analysis in physics and math. We also try to communicate any assumptions when made. We welcome genuine feedback. It's worth noting that we layer on a lot of conservatism in our timelines. I wouldn't be all that surprised that Elon and others make our predictions look stupid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ba5384f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Expansion of consciousness to understand the universe is the reason</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/76f92ead</link>
      <description>Expansion of consciousness to understand the universe is the reason</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_76f92ead</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: From Day One,@xAIhas been upgrading grid infrastructure and ensuring ratepayers don’t pick up our ta...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/01e39705</link>
      <description>From Day One,@xAIhas been upgrading grid infrastructure and ensuring ratepayers don’t pick up our tab. Today, we are continuing our commitment by installing our own power lines to power our MACROHARD facilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_01e39705</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: No more waiting for high-speed internet! We have removed waitlists for Starlink in every country whe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7a7eaae6</link>
      <description>No more waiting for high-speed internet! We have removed waitlists for Starlink in every country where Starlink is available today. Go tostarlink.comto find the best available service plan that works for you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7a7eaae6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Worse than the worst nightmare I could have imagined</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/98b59ff9</link>
      <description>Worse than the worst nightmare I could have imagined</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_98b59ff9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Banger</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/85b2479a</link>
      <description>Banger</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_85b2479a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Get stuff done@xAI</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/39dc2cb8</link>
      <description>Get stuff done@xAI</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_39dc2cb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: After a successful launch, Crew-12 is en route to the@Space_Station, scheduled to arrive at about 3:...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4d6e1367</link>
      <description>After a successful launch, Crew-12 is en route to the@Space_Station, scheduled to arrive at about 3:15pm ET (2015 UTC) on Feb. 14. Learn when and where to watch—with or without a Valentine:go.nasa.gov/4qz1Wig</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4d6e1367</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Dragon has separated from Falcon 9’s second stage</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/28508654</link>
      <description>Dragon has separated from Falcon 9’s second stage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_28508654</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨JOHN CLEESE SAYS BBC ARE "DISGRACEFUL" FOR IGNORING RAPE GANG INQUIRY Couldn't agree with you more ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7e18213f</link>
      <description>🚨JOHN CLEESE SAYS BBC ARE "DISGRACEFUL" FOR IGNORING RAPE GANG INQUIRY Couldn't agree with you more John Defund the BBC 🚫</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7e18213f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A great morning for human spaceflight. Congratulations to the teams at NASA, SpaceX, and our interna...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/338e1388</link>
      <description>A great morning for human spaceflight. Congratulations to the teams at NASA, SpaceX, and our international partners who worked tirelessly to launch Crew 12 safely on a journey to the International Space Station. If this is what is possible today, imagine what tomorrow will bring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_338e1388</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: From@WSJEditorial Board: "Such data would have shown the surge in what is alleged to be fake autism ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fb311e53</link>
      <description>From@WSJEditorial Board: "Such data would have shown the surge in what is alleged to be fake autism diagnoses and treatments in Minnesota that were billed by fly-by-night Medicaid providers."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fb311e53</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Medicaid data has been open sourced, so the level of fraud is easy to identify.@DOGEis not a departm...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/456f09b2</link>
      <description>Medicaid data has been open sourced, so the level of fraud is easy to identify.@DOGEis not a department, it’s a state of mind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_456f09b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia traffic is surging worldwide. Website visits are now up 52.61% compared to last...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c58c8258</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia traffic is surging worldwide. Website visits are now up 52.61% compared to last month. Visits are rising sharply month over month, as per@SimilarwebKeep sharing Grokipedia links to defeat the Woke Wikipedia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c58c8258</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In 1707, two thousand sailors DROWNED. Not because of a storm. Because nobody could tell where they ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9e1c9e05</link>
      <description>In 1707, two thousand sailors DROWNED. Not because of a storm. Because nobody could tell where they were at sea 🇬🇧 This was the longitude problem. The deadliest puzzle in science. Parliament offered £20,000 to anyone who could solve it. Nearly four million today. Every great scientist in Europe tried. Newton. Halley. The finest minds alive. All of them failed. The man who solved it was a carpenter from Yorkshire. His name was John Harrison. No formal education. No university. No wealthy patron. He taught himself clockmaking. Built timepieces out of wood. His idea was “simple”. If you know the exact time at home and the exact time at sea, you can calculate exactly where you are. The problem? No clock could keep accurate time on a moving ship. Heat warps metal. Cold contracts it. The ocean never stops moving. Harrison spent DECADES on it. H1. Twenty years of work. Not good enough. H2. Better. Still not enough. H3. Seventeen years. Over 700 parts. Still not enough. Then he did something nobody expected. He stopped building clocks. He built a watch. H4. Thirteen centimetres across. The most important watch ever made. They sent it across the Atlantic. Eighty-one days at sea. When they arrived, it had lost five seconds. Five seconds. In eighty-one days. The problem was solved. But here's the uncomfortable part. They didn't give him the prize. The Board of Longitude was run by astronomers. The very men who'd been trying to solve it their own way. The Astronomer Royal was both judge and competitor. They changed the rules. Demanded his designs. Refused to pay. A working-class carpenter had beaten every astronomer in Europe. And the establishment couldn't accept it. Harrison was nearly EIGHTY before he got justice. He went directly to King George III. The king tested the watch himself and told Harrison to petition Parliament with the king's full backing. Parliament paid. Harrison died three years later. After his death, every ship on earth carried a chronometer based on his design. Every GPS satellite. Every ship's navigation. Every flight path. All of it traces back to a carpenter from Yorkshire who taught himself to build a watch. His watches are still at the Royal Observatory in Greenwich. Still ticking. Still perfect. The establishment tried to bury him once. We're not letting it happen again 👇proudofus.co.uk/supportBe part of us. Be proud of us. 🇬🇧</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9e1c9e05</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Read this whole paragraph, then imagine trying to explain to a normal person??</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/940da94b</link>
      <description>Read this whole paragraph, then imagine trying to explain to a normal person??</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_940da94b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink now at 10 million active users</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa97127e</link>
      <description>Starlink now at 10 million active users</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa97127e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: While you were sleeping, SpaceX sent astronauts into space.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/38141c67</link>
      <description>While you were sleeping, SpaceX sent astronauts into space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_38141c67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa93318c</link>
      <description>xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as quickly as xAI, the structure must evolve just like any living organism. This unfortunately required parting ways with some people. We wish them well in future endeavors. We are hiring aggressively. Join xAI if the idea of mass drivers on the Moon appeals to you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa93318c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
