<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-16 17:49 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:49:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Undersecretary Sarah Rogers and I discuss this email from@Keir_Starmer's COS Morgan McSweeney to@brh...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/67ff026f</link>
      <description>Undersecretary Sarah Rogers and I discuss this email from@Keir_Starmer's COS Morgan McSweeney to@brhodesdiscussing collaboration against "right wing culture wars." A senior Starmer staffer is cc'd on email. QUESTION: Are Brits interfering in US domestic politics?@ryangrim@TheCanaryUK@SamCoatesSky@jsolomonReports@benclerkin@afshinrattansi@JoshTBoswell@freddiesayers@joshrogin</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_67ff026f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: UK GOVERNMENT IS COMMITTING A HORRIFYING CRIME AGAINST HUMANITY Nearly 280k babies aborted in Englan...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c184a08f</link>
      <description>UK GOVERNMENT IS COMMITTING A HORRIFYING CRIME AGAINST HUMANITY Nearly 280k babies aborted in England &amp; Wales in just one year in 2023 - the highest number ever recorded At the same time, the Labour Govt has voted to decriminalise self-induced abortions. A woman can now end a pregnancy after 24 weeks (even up to birth) without facing prosecution At the same time: • “Buffer zones” around abortion clinics make it illegal to silently pray or offer help within 150 metres • People have been arrested simply for praying quietly in their own heads • Pro-life counsellors offering alternatives are criminalised • Anyone trying to persuade a woman against abortion risks arrest The state is actively facilitating the destruction of life, while criminalising conscience, prayer, and peaceful persuasion Over a quarter of a million lives gone in one year. This is horrifying</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c184a08f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is a whole of government effort and the result of@realDonaldTrumpleadership letting good cops b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/76b8d1cf</link>
      <description>This is a whole of government effort and the result of@realDonaldTrumpleadership letting good cops be cops. At the@FBIfor example we had a 31% increase in fentanyl seizures 2025, 2,100 kilos - what would’ve been enough to kill 150+ million Americans. Real lives being saved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_76b8d1cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Democrat Senator John Fetterman on illegal aliens: “Round up all the criminals, deport them. They de...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3bc3c32c</link>
      <description>Democrat Senator John Fetterman on illegal aliens: “Round up all the criminals, deport them. They definitely have to go… As a Democrat, it should not be unreasonable to want to secure our border.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3bc3c32c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is how CNN covered ICE under President Barack Obama. Notice anything different?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/03d743a2</link>
      <description>This is how CNN covered ICE under President Barack Obama. Notice anything different?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_03d743a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The lawsuit between Elon Musk and OpenAI is surfacing some pretty interesting evidence: OpenAI's Gre...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a0c758ef</link>
      <description>The lawsuit between Elon Musk and OpenAI is surfacing some pretty interesting evidence: OpenAI's Greg Brockman: "It'd be wrong to steal the non-profit from him. to convert to a b-corp without him. that'd be pretty morally bankrupt. and he's really not an idiot." Days later, Brockman further wrote under the heading "our plan" that "it would be nice to be making the billions" and explained that "we've been thinking that maybe we should flip to a for profit." Earlier Greg said: "Cannot say that we are committed to the non-profit. don't want to say that we're committed. if three months later we're doing b-corp then it was a lie. Not feeling so great about all of this. The true answer is that we want [Musk] out. Can't see us turning this into a for-profit without a very nasty fight. I'm just thinking about the office and we're in the office. and his story will correctly be that we weren't honest with him in the end about still wanting to do the for profit just without him."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a0c758ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: JD Vance has a message for Germany: "You don’t have shared values if you silence your people."</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e37690ea</link>
      <description>JD Vance has a message for Germany: "You don’t have shared values if you silence your people."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e37690ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 HOLY CRAP. Somali men STORM out of "child care" building that gets $2M from Minnesota and go BERSE...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f26a2c3f</link>
      <description>🚨 HOLY CRAP. Somali men STORM out of "child care" building that gets $2M from Minnesota and go BERSERK on Nick Shirley "Get out! GET OUT!" That's not how normal child cares operate 🤯 - All vehicles sitting there with 2 feet of snow on them - Windows blacked out - "Over 100 children" - No footprints at the door RAID THIS BUILDING!@nickshirleyy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f26a2c3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It is the only way to save America</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9784df78</link>
      <description>It is the only way to save America</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9784df78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For the fake news peddling misinformation about the appellate ruling for Mahmoud Khalil, here is our...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/834a0ede</link>
      <description>For the fake news peddling misinformation about the appellate ruling for Mahmoud Khalil, here is our stance in simple terms: If you sympathize with terrorists, your presence is contrary to the national and foreign policy interests of the United States. You are not welcome here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_834a0ede</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
