<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-30 22:40 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:40:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Great!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f8380139</link>
      <description>Great!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f8380139</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More fraud in Columbus Ohio as well? This daycare has a Facebook Page that is posting about things u...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3708ea29</link>
      <description>More fraud in Columbus Ohio as well? This daycare has a Facebook Page that is posting about things unrelated to their daycare business. I think the federal government should be going around at a national level and making sure these locations around the country are not taking advantage of American tax payers. Many have said this is just the tip of the iceberg. They may be right...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3708ea29</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Vegas Loop dropoff at the Airport! Still in the early phases of the program, providing a small numbe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9bd51ef3</link>
      <description>Vegas Loop dropoff at the Airport! Still in the early phases of the program, providing a small number of rides each day. The ride includes both a tunnel portion and a long surface portion, with the latter shifting to subsurface when the 2.25 mile Airport Connector twin tunnels open, hopefully in Q1 2026. Thanks to@LASAirport@LVCVA@ClarkCountyNV@NevadaDBIin reaching this milestone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9bd51ef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Should be non-partisan, but it isn’t, because Dems and their donors are the fraudsters</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/501bc5b2</link>
      <description>Should be non-partisan, but it isn’t, because Dems and their donors are the fraudsters</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_501bc5b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Oh it just gets worse by the minute … Feds covered up Ohio adoption hub who sold children to Somali ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dc2a7ed0</link>
      <description>Oh it just gets worse by the minute … Feds covered up Ohio adoption hub who sold children to Somali sex gangs 😔</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dc2a7ed0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Babe wake up new entry on the It’s Not Happening meme just dropped</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/06e41b81</link>
      <description>Babe wake up new entry on the It’s Not Happening meme just dropped</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_06e41b81</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The mayor of an American city waving the flag of a foreign country on American soil in order to rema...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2abd71d7</link>
      <description>The mayor of an American city waving the flag of a foreign country on American soil in order to remain politically viable. We are under foreign occupation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2abd71d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tesla Model Y is now officially the world’s best-selling car for the third year in a row!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/994da011</link>
      <description>Tesla Model Y is now officially the world’s best-selling car for the third year in a row!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_994da011</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: There's that little app called Google on your phone. I added "Minnesota" to the alerts and sometimes...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/827a9000</link>
      <description>There's that little app called Google on your phone. I added "Minnesota" to the alerts and sometimes I check it to give me a little boost during the day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_827a9000</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Correct, they would much rather raise taxes than fix fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e0eef252</link>
      <description>Correct, they would much rather raise taxes than fix fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e0eef252</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Similarly, we cannot subsidize fraud and expect people to become more honest</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8954620e</link>
      <description>Similarly, we cannot subsidize fraud and expect people to become more honest</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8954620e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: FLASHBACK Serena Williams tells Letterman: “Men’s &amp; women’s tennis are completely different sports. ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/45315b50</link>
      <description>FLASHBACK Serena Williams tells Letterman: “Men’s &amp; women’s tennis are completely different sports. If I played Andy Murray, I’d lose 6-0, 6-0 in 5 minutes…. It’s true. He would kill me. Men are a lot faster, serve harder, and hit harder. I only want to play girls.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_45315b50</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OMG. Massachusetts caseworker EXPOSES widespread Somali daycare fraud happening in her state. “When ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/428d5914</link>
      <description>OMG. Massachusetts caseworker EXPOSES widespread Somali daycare fraud happening in her state. “When I had an appointment to service a child who went to a daycare that received a voucher, I was NEVER let in 100% of the time.” The fraud is EVERYWHERE</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_428d5914</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The REAL HERO in the Minnesota Somali fraud exposure is this man below, David. Despite knowing all t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/596917e2</link>
      <description>The REAL HERO in the Minnesota Somali fraud exposure is this man below, David. Despite knowing all the risks involved, and that his life could be in danger at any given time for going down this rabbit hole, David still laced his boots up and risked the last 5+ years of his life on the streets of Minnesota, investigating, gathering, recording and documenting all the fraud that was happening on Tim Walz’s watch. Thank you to David for exposing it, and to Nick Shirley for shining a bright light on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_596917e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Because fraudsters want to kill him for telling the truth</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9bae0086</link>
      <description>Because fraudsters want to kill him for telling the truth</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9bae0086</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Optimus hardware and@Tesla_AIteam are doing incredible work!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b5d51b2f</link>
      <description>The Optimus hardware and@Tesla_AIteam are doing incredible work!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b5d51b2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 HOLY CRAP! FBI Director Kash Patel just revealed the Biden admin "BURIED" Minnesota fraud investig...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/20489c9b</link>
      <description>🚨 HOLY CRAP! FBI Director Kash Patel just revealed the Biden admin "BURIED" Minnesota fraud investigations because it potentially implicated BIDEN ALLIES. The FBI is now also investigating fraud links to ELECTED OFFICIALS and t*rrorists. Imagine that. The FBI is additionally surging forensic accountants and data teams to MN, per@C__HerridgeDOZENS of investigations have been opened since the middle of this year up through December. DHS agents were spotted on the ground this week, going door-to-door as well 👇 KEEP INVESTIGATING and LOCK THEM UP! The American people demand accountability.@FBIDirectorKash</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_20489c9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/723dfe9f</link>
      <description>xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try@Grok. Download latest app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_723dfe9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
