<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-19 20:56 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:56:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Physics is beautiful - woke up to find my truck covered in fern frost. A rare phenomenon that occurs...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ac6fd1ae</link>
      <description>Physics is beautiful - woke up to find my truck covered in fern frost. A rare phenomenon that occurs in just the right conditions. Surface temp drops below the freezing point of nearby humid air, ice crystals form propagating out from nucleation sites making these cool patterns</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ac6fd1ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 beta example Years ago, I made a crypto wallet but missed writing a few seed phrase words....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/94a2de72</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 beta example Years ago, I made a crypto wallet but missed writing a few seed phrase words. This account has a measly 40$ but I keep asking AI to try opening it for fun Grok 4.1 spent 6 days of trying and failed Grok 4.20 cracked it in 492 seconds, correctly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_94a2de72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk showing Tesla Roadster to Arnold Schwarzenegger in 2008.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/82348e10</link>
      <description>Elon Musk showing Tesla Roadster to Arnold Schwarzenegger in 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_82348e10</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just asked the 16 Grok 4.20 Heavy agents to build me a GLSL shader, no libraries. Alien bioluminesce...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/128be6cf</link>
      <description>Just asked the 16 Grok 4.20 Heavy agents to build me a GLSL shader, no libraries. Alien bioluminescent ocean floor. Hydrothermal vents, caustic light, rising particles, layered noise terrain. Mouse = underwater flashlight. 60fps. Collapsible control panel with uniforms. It cooked. &gt;&gt;&gt; grok 4.20 heavy prompt Build a single HTML page with a full-screen GLSL fragment shader rendered via WebGL. No libraries raw WebGL setup with a full-screen quad. The shader should render an alien bioluminescent ocean floor imagine deep sea hydrothermal vents with pulsing organic light. Use layered simplex/value noise for undulating terrain, glowing particles rising like volcanic embers, caustic light patterns rippling across the surface, and color palettes shifting between deep indigo, electric cyan, magenta, and molten gold. The mouse position should act as an underwater flashlight illuminating nearby terrain and revealing hidden details. Include a subtle camera drift so it feels like you're slowly gliding over the seabed. Everything should be smooth at 60fps. Add a small collapsible control panel in the corner with sliders for: glow intensity, drift speed, color temperature, and particle density these should feed into the shader as uniforms. The page background should be black with no scrollbars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_128be6cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 100 men? Even in high school, it was hard getting 10 guys together if we had to fight another squad....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2e5e1f2c</link>
      <description>100 men? Even in high school, it was hard getting 10 guys together if we had to fight another squad. It was hard getting ten guys together for a BASEBALL GAME. Do you know ONE man you could invite over for some rape or domestic violence?! What type a' animals are we dealing with here?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2e5e1f2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a1818215</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a1818215</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0aea500a</link>
      <description>Grokipedia.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0aea500a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 8 years ago, SpaceX launched Falcon Heavy for the first time Payload was Elon Musk’s cherry-red Tesl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/18cd5f18</link>
      <description>8 years ago, SpaceX launched Falcon Heavy for the first time Payload was Elon Musk’s cherry-red Tesla Roadster with Starman - a spacesuit-wearing mannequin in the driver’s seat Etched inside the car: “Made on Earth by Humans” One of the most legendary moments in space history</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_18cd5f18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇩🇪 Germany's state broadcaster got caught airing fake AI footage of ICE "troops" arresting immigrant...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/65fa15a3</link>
      <description>🇩🇪 Germany's state broadcaster got caught airing fake AI footage of ICE "troops" arresting immigrants ZDF ran AI-generated images with a visible OpenAI Sora watermark on screen. And called them "troops" instead of agents. Did ZDF generate this themselves? If Germany's biggest state broadcaster is making fake news footage in-house, how often has this happened before?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_65fa15a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Big difference between Grok and WokeGPT</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/328d376e</link>
      <description>Big difference between Grok and WokeGPT</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_328d376e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try@Teslaself-driving, it’s awesome!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/31ebb506</link>
      <description>Try@Teslaself-driving, it’s awesome!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_31ebb506</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wikipedia won’t die, but it will dwindle into irrelevance over time</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d1523a66</link>
      <description>Wikipedia won’t die, but it will dwindle into irrelevance over time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d1523a66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Like google search , it feels so out dated now after using Grok for everything!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/249f430d</link>
      <description>Like google search , it feels so out dated now after using Grok for everything!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_249f430d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Glad you’re ok! ❤️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8a69e4db</link>
      <description>Glad you’re ok! ❤️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8a69e4db</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This needs to be said, as there has been unrelenting hate and poisonous propaganda in the West again...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/14ff97c4</link>
      <description>This needs to be said, as there has been unrelenting hate and poisonous propaganda in the West against anyone White, straight or male over the past decade or more! It went WAY too far. No more guilt trips. ENOUGH.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_14ff97c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Let’s maybe ask … I dunno … the CO-FOUNDER of Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8d50c0a2</link>
      <description>Let’s maybe ask … I dunno … the CO-FOUNDER of Wikipedia</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8d50c0a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The legacy media is nonstop lunatic left propaganda</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fc7712b6</link>
      <description>The legacy media is nonstop lunatic left propaganda</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fc7712b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You really will. It’s awesome.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cae65706</link>
      <description>You really will. It’s awesome.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cae65706</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I’ve been reading the dishonesty and extreme negativity in the mainstream media for 20 years. It is ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9fee3d70</link>
      <description>I’ve been reading the dishonesty and extreme negativity in the mainstream media for 20 years. It is really hard to cope with hateful headlines when Elon is doing amazing things worldwide. I’ve just finished writing another book, and include how I shamed the news outlets and the journalists on Twitter five years ago. They didn’t care. Every day, I’m happy that Elon bought Twitter and renamed it X.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9fee3d70</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
