<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-08 22:46 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:46:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk@elonmusk, who co-founded and invested in an open source, non-profit OpenAI ~$50 million: I...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa8dd864</link>
      <description>Elon Musk@elonmusk, who co-founded and invested in an open source, non-profit OpenAI ~$50 million: I AM THE REASON OpenAI EXISTS “I am the reason OpenAI exists... I used to be a close friend with Larry Page, and I was staying at his house, and we'd have these conversations long into the evening about AI, and I would be constantly urging him to be careful about the danger of AI. And he was really not concerned about the danger of AI and was quite cavalier about it. And at the time, Google, especially after the acquisition of DeepMind, had three-quarters of the world's AI talent; they had a lot of computers, a lot of money, so it was a unipolar world for AI. And we got a unipolar world, but the person who controls that does not, or at least did not seem to be concerned about AI safety. That sounded like a real problem. The final straw was Larry calling me a speciest for being a pro-human consciousness instead of machine consciousness, and I like, 'Well, yes, I guess I am a speciest.' I came up with the name [OpenAI], which refers to open source. The intent was to what is the opposite of Google, would be an open source non-profit, because Google is closed source profit, and that profit motivation could be dangerous... It does seem weird that something can be a nonprofit, open source, and somehow transform itself into a for-profit, closed source. I mean, this would be like, let's say you founded the organization to save the Amazon rainforest, but instead, they became a lumber company and chopped down the forest and sold it for money. And you'd be, therefore, like, 'Wait a second, that's the exact opposite of what I gave the money for. Is that legal?' That doesn't seem legal. And if, in general, it is legal to start a company as a non-profit and then take the IP and transfer it to a for-profit that then makes tons of money, shouldn't everyone start? Shouldn't that be the default? And I also think it is important to understand, like when push comes to shove, let's say they do create some digital super intelligence, almost Godlike intelligence, well, who is in control, and what is exactly the relationship between OpenAI and Microsoft? And I do worry that Microsoft actually may be more in control than the leadership team at OpenAI realizes. I mean, Microsoft, as part of Microsoft Investment, has rights to all of the software, all of the model weights, and everything necessary to run the inference system. At any point, Microsoft could cut off OpenAI.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa8dd864</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk was right He BLASTS Dems: 'Biggest voter fraud in history!' Illegals on Social Security DO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/454e0079</link>
      <description>Elon Musk was right He BLASTS Dems: 'Biggest voter fraud in history!' Illegals on Social Security DOUBLING yearly. Dem operatives 'farm votes' with fake IDs — utility bills, school IDs — get SSNs, hit voter rolls. This is why we need Voter ID!”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_454e0079</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: South Africa is blocking Starlink solely because Elon Musk is not Black. This is not regulation, it ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/478e0be9</link>
      <description>South Africa is blocking Starlink solely because Elon Musk is not Black. This is not regulation, it is discrimination, and it is shameful</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_478e0be9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk :"Whenever there’s some sort of natural disaster somewhere, we always provide people with ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b7735b09</link>
      <description>Elon Musk :"Whenever there’s some sort of natural disaster somewhere, we always provide people with free Starlink internet connectivity We don’t want to take advantage of a tragic situation "If there’s a natural disaster, it’s free during the disaster" We don’t want to put a paywall up while somebody is trying to get help. That would be wrong"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b7735b09</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Today would be a good day to start listening to Charlie Kirk.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/884562f1</link>
      <description>Today would be a good day to start listening to Charlie Kirk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_884562f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk. People just don't understand that solar is everything. “People just don't understand that...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2cff5ed5</link>
      <description>Elon Musk. People just don't understand that solar is everything. “People just don't understand that solar is everything. Compared to the sun, all other energy sources are like cavemen throwing some twigs into a fire. The sun is over 99.8% of all mass in the solar system. Jupiter is around 0.1% of the mass. So, even if you burnt Jupiter, the energy produced by the sun would still round up to 100%. And then if you teleported three more Jupiters into our solar system and burnt them too, the sun still rounds up to 100% of energy.” From: Discussion with Peter Diamandis and Dave Blundin, January 6, 2026</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2cff5ed5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The judge said there’s "plenty of evidence" OpenAI broke its promise to stay non-profit</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1702eb88</link>
      <description>The judge said there’s "plenty of evidence" OpenAI broke its promise to stay non-profit</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1702eb88</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is great</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1eea6761</link>
      <description>This is great</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1eea6761</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wow, Frey is super deep in the fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8b1c8202</link>
      <description>Wow, Frey is super deep in the fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8b1c8202</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “The Department of Homeland Security will continue to operate on the ground in Minnesota — not only ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/435cdcc9</link>
      <description>“The Department of Homeland Security will continue to operate on the ground in Minnesota — not only to remove criminal illegal aliens, but also to continue conducting door-to-door investigations of the rampant fraud that has taken place in the state...”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_435cdcc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Secretary Bessent is right</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4b5f4761</link>
      <description>Secretary Bessent is right</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4b5f4761</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS:@xAIjust unveiled the 800,000 sqft building that will house the company's multi-billion dollar ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2492ecd9</link>
      <description>NEWS:@xAIjust unveiled the 800,000 sqft building that will house the company's multi-billion dollar next-generation Colossus 3 datacenter. It will be the new largest supercomputer in the world. Massive amount of compute and power. The building (pictured below) is located in Southaven, Mississippi.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2492ecd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We should have listened to@elonmusk</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ac6a554c</link>
      <description>We should have listened to@elonmusk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ac6a554c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: So it is true that South Africa does not allow Elon Musk to operate Starlink because he is not black...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d7225b23</link>
      <description>So it is true that South Africa does not allow Elon Musk to operate Starlink because he is not black ! He needs at least 30% ownership in it by black. I thought Elon was exaggerating … but it’s TRUE WooW</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d7225b23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This js the hard truth</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fac5d51b</link>
      <description>This js the hard truth</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fac5d51b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: URGENT ALERT: Reports indicate the UK authorities are exploring a potential block on 𝕏. As the leadi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8ee3de45</link>
      <description>URGENT ALERT: Reports indicate the UK authorities are exploring a potential block on 𝕏. As the leading news application in the UK, 𝕏 serves as a vital daily resource for millions seeking accurate, unfiltered information. X is #1 for news in the UK</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8ee3de45</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I've seen a lot of dishonest coverage from the media during my time in politics, but the last 24 hou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c3296bd0</link>
      <description>I've seen a lot of dishonest coverage from the media during my time in politics, but the last 24 hours may have set a new low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c3296bd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the only way to stop civilizational suicide. It is critical that we take these steps to avoi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/257f5d2c</link>
      <description>This is the only way to stop civilizational suicide. It is critical that we take these steps to avoid annihilation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_257f5d2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
