<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-16 14:52 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:52:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: HEARTBREAKING: Harvey Mucklebust's grandmother speaks after the 11-month-old was suffocated to death...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f866c071</link>
      <description>HEARTBREAKING: Harvey Mucklebust's grandmother speaks after the 11-month-old was suffocated to death at a daycare: "Every day, we will say your name. Every day, we will continue to fight for you. And in the end, we will make sure that justice has been served." JUSTICE FOR HARVEY</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f866c071</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Once again, Tesla tops the charts for vehicle safety According to Euro NCAP: • Tesla Model 3 — Best ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f0ef0cf2</link>
      <description>Once again, Tesla tops the charts for vehicle safety According to Euro NCAP: • Tesla Model 3 — Best in Class: Large Family Car • Tesla Model Y — Best in Class: Small SUV Both earned top scores in Safety Assist and Occupant Protection Tesla keeps safety as its first priority and once again leads the industry where it matters most: protecting people and saving lives</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f0ef0cf2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: WEAPONIZATION: RINOs in Congress overruled the president to fund the anti-America, anti-Free Speech ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/34891021</link>
      <description>WEAPONIZATION: RINOs in Congress overruled the president to fund the anti-America, anti-Free Speech NGO called the National Endowment for Democracy (NED). Its CEO, Damon Wilson, makes more than the president and his husband runs a government-funded hair salon in Washington DC. Why do taxpayers need to support every grifting Democrat and their pet NGOs?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_34891021</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If you are the founder of a highly valued illiquid startup, set some time aside and read this entire...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/25477de8</link>
      <description>If you are the founder of a highly valued illiquid startup, set some time aside and read this entire article. The act is designed to bankrupt you and to personally punish any appraiser or accountant who disagrees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_25477de8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Reminder than San Francisco County could halve its budget from $16B to $8B and still be the best-fun...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c5330ca</link>
      <description>Reminder than San Francisco County could halve its budget from $16B to $8B and still be the best-funded major county in the USA. Services are just bad bc of endemic corruption. Saikat is either lying or stupid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c5330ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Colleges have become radical left indoctrination camps</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c199e6c1</link>
      <description>Colleges have become radical left indoctrination camps</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c199e6c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They knew</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/785f5a94</link>
      <description>They knew</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_785f5a94</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They openly discuss their conspiracy to commit fraud and steal the charity</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/83df5ef6</link>
      <description>They openly discuss their conspiracy to commit fraud and steal the charity</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_83df5ef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Case closed. Elon has OAI dead to rights.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5c9c1a78</link>
      <description>Case closed. Elon has OAI dead to rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5c9c1a78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Easily half of our national debt is Democrat fraud. If not more…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/13bae340</link>
      <description>Easily half of our national debt is Democrat fraud. If not more…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_13bae340</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Time for a math problem : In the 2024 presidential election, 2,308,256 people in Oregon voted, repre...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d26e1414</link>
      <description>Time for a math problem : In the 2024 presidential election, 2,308,256 people in Oregon voted, representing a turnout rate of 75.4% among the state's 3,060,374 registered voters. 800,000 registered voters were ‘improperly registered’ voters. That means a WHOPPING 34% of votes were fraudulent. Kamala won Oregon by 321,000 votes…. Donald Trump received 919,480 votes. Kamala Harris had 1,240,600. There appears to be a high correlation to the cities and states obstructing federal law enforcement operations and ‘improperly registered’ voters. It obvious why Walz is breaking numerous federal laws…he’s playing for keeps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d26e1414</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: GDP hits 5.5%. Meaning the American economy is now growing faster than China. - Productivity growth ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f3bed0da</link>
      <description>GDP hits 5.5%. Meaning the American economy is now growing faster than China. - Productivity growth tripled - Wages are growing 3.8% - Layoffs are the lowest since 2022 - Inflation is just 1.7% per Truflation This is the crash legacy media and economists swore was coming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f3bed0da</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: They stole a charity, plain and simple</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/652eaeb5</link>
      <description>They stole a charity, plain and simple</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_652eaeb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Incredibly unjust</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6bf22c67</link>
      <description>Incredibly unjust</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6bf22c67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia traffic surges more than 10,000% since November, as Wikipedia's monopoly comes ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/34b11742</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia traffic surges more than 10,000% since November, as Wikipedia's monopoly comes to an end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_34b11742</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Diversity, equity, and inclusion are three wonderful sounding words that are, in fact, a scheme to ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ef3b3005</link>
      <description>"Diversity, equity, and inclusion are three wonderful sounding words that are, in fact, a scheme to do the exact opposite"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ef3b3005</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨OpenAI is warning investors to expect “outlandish” claims from Elon Musk as the April trial approac...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2e31e30e</link>
      <description>🚨OpenAI is warning investors to expect “outlandish” claims from Elon Musk as the April trial approaches. Translation: Scam Altman freaking out, he's nervous 😅 Elon’s lawsuit is exposing how a “nonprofit” became a $500B for-profit machine. Even the judge said the case is “extremely concerning” 👀 He’s shining light where others won’t 👊</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2e31e30e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Feeling Optimustic about the future!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/627d016d</link>
      <description>Feeling Optimustic about the future!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_627d016d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
