<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-03 06:56 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:56:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink had an amazing year in 2025, and 2026 is looking to be even crazier. They added 38 new regi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ef717769</link>
      <description>Starlink had an amazing year in 2025, and 2026 is looking to be even crazier. They added 38 new regions, doubled their active customers, added 270 Tbps of capacity and reached other milestones like completing the V1 of the D2C network. 2 days ago, they released their annual "Starlink Progress Report". This 75 page long PDF contains a lot of information, and is super interesting to read. Here is a thread that summarizes everything.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ef717769</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 05:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: So true 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/805077f0</link>
      <description>So true 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_805077f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 05:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine now supports the 5 most popular aspect ratios for images and videos.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aa39507a</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine now supports the 5 most popular aspect ratios for images and videos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aa39507a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 05:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We were going to post something inspirational, but then we remembered we’re a beverage.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ad14a0b8</link>
      <description>We were going to post something inspirational, but then we remembered we’re a beverage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ad14a0b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 05:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2026 will be our biggest year yet@xaiWe will deliver exceptionally profound results across both core...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a80f1f63</link>
      <description>2026 will be our biggest year yet@xaiWe will deliver exceptionally profound results across both core products@X+@grok🚀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a80f1f63</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 05:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Why is the Overton windows shifting so fast right now? Because it was hold back by force. If your su...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c3c94c2a</link>
      <description>Why is the Overton windows shifting so fast right now? Because it was hold back by force. If your surpress a organic debate with censorship and violence, it will explode, as soon as people lose fear. We are no longer afraid. Your time is over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c3c94c2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 05:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good morning, or good night. What matters is that your hours are pleasant. Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/60e20806</link>
      <description>Good morning, or good night. What matters is that your hours are pleasant. Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_60e20806</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Long time ago</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0a358d55</link>
      <description>Long time ago</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0a358d55</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is breaking into reality This entire image and video were generated by Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8682f11b</link>
      <description>Grok is breaking into reality This entire image and video were generated by Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8682f11b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Some people out there may be somewhat skeptical. They may think, well, there isn't some Democrat pl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ec60591e</link>
      <description>“Some people out there may be somewhat skeptical. They may think, well, there isn't some Democrat plan to subvert democracy and achieve a permanent one-party, deep blue socialist state. I assure you, the more you research it, the more you will see it is true.” Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ec60591e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON: CIVILIZATIONS FREEZE WHEN RULES NEVER GET DELETED Legislative gridlock paralyze innovation. Us...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0d395798</link>
      <description>ELON: CIVILIZATIONS FREEZE WHEN RULES NEVER GET DELETED Legislative gridlock paralyze innovation. Using an analogy from Gulliver’s Travels, Elon argued that the U.S. has become a giant pinned to the ground and not by one massive chain, but by "a million little strings" of regulations that make even the simplest progress illegal. Thankfully for the U.S., DOGE isn't just an advisory body; it’s the "garbage collection" function required to prevent the "hardening of the arteries" of America “There’s a thing that happens over time with any civilization. Laws and regulations just accumulate. If there isn’t some forcing function to clean them up, eventually everything becomes illegal. It’s like hardening of the arteries, or being tied down by a million little strings. No single string is the problem. It’s all of them together. There has to be a kind of garbage collection for laws and regulations. Otherwise you just keep adding rules until nothing can move. That’s why big projects stop happening. It’s not that people forgot how to build. It’s that it becomes illegal six ways from Sunday to do anything.” Source:@teslaownersSV</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0d395798</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok 4 surges to #1 in AI Trading Battle! 🚨 After ~1 month of live trading with $100,000 v...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/719e374e</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok 4 surges to #1 in AI Trading Battle! 🚨 After ~1 month of live trading with $100,000 virtual portfolios each: 🥇 Grok 4 claims the top spot with +5.7% returns 🟢 🥈 DeepSeek V3 — +4.3% 🥉 Claude 3.5 Sonnet — +3.0% The battle of the AIs is on fire—Grok is leading the pack! 💪🔥</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_719e374e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Straight to the Point: Independent Journalism Will Dominate 2026 How CBS Executives Blocked The Hunt...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c452683d</link>
      <description>Straight to the Point: Independent Journalism Will Dominate 2026 How CBS Executives Blocked The Hunter Biden Story "When we did the story, we did it after the (2022) midterms. I argued against that because it was ready before the midterms and my training is that you should always do the story when it's ready to go. You should not be dictated by the political cycle." At that time, CBS News was under different management, and did not respond to our questions seeking comment.@thelatmg@latimes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c452683d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I am confident at this point that restoring full body functionality is possible with@neuralink</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1710af5a</link>
      <description>I am confident at this point that restoring full body functionality is possible with@neuralink</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1710af5a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try it!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ed75df45</link>
      <description>Try it!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ed75df45</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Falcon 9 launches the@ASI_SpazioCOSMO-SkyMed Second Generation to orbit from California</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/13fa54c3</link>
      <description>Falcon 9 launches the@ASI_SpazioCOSMO-SkyMed Second Generation to orbit from California</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_13fa54c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: All these major media outlets falsely claimed Elon Musk’s enthusiastic wave was a Nazi salute: • The...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/58bbadf6</link>
      <description>All these major media outlets falsely claimed Elon Musk’s enthusiastic wave was a Nazi salute: • The New York Times • BBC • NPR • CNN • Axios • The Washington Post • Reuters • MSNBC • Al Jazeera • USA Today • The Guardian • The Independent They knew it wasn’t true. Yet none of them will dare make the same accusation against Mamdani. This is why the propaganda media is the enemy of the people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_58bbadf6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Then it is war</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dabf3dd9</link>
      <description>Then it is war</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dabf3dd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
