<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-29 07:50 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:50:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇨🇳 CHINA'S MAGLEV HITS 700 KM/H IN 2 SECONDS - PLANNING 1,000 KM/H - WHILE AMERICA ARGUES ABOUT FIXI...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0e7fae8e</link>
      <description>🇨🇳 CHINA'S MAGLEV HITS 700 KM/H IN 2 SECONDS - PLANNING 1,000 KM/H - WHILE AMERICA ARGUES ABOUT FIXING POTHOLES China just tested a maglev platform that accelerates to 700 km/h (435 mph) in 2 seconds. Target speed: 1,000 km/h (621 mph). That's faster than commercial aircraft. On the ground. The acceleration alone is borderline violent - 0 to 435 mph in two seconds is 9.8g. Fighter jet territory. Passengers would need specialized seating just to survive the launch. But let's address reality: This is a test platform. Prototype speeds don't mean operational trains. China announces ambitious projects constantly. Some materialize (their existing 430 km/h maglev in Shanghai works). Others disappear quietly. The pattern though? They're attempting scale nobody else is. High-speed rail connecting every major city. Maglev research pushed to extremes. Infrastructure spending that makes Western investment look microscopic. Meanwhile in America: Amtrak averages 105 km/h between cities. California's high-speed rail project started in 2008, burned $10+ billion, and hasn't moved a passenger. The fastest train in the U.S. hits 240 km/h for exactly one 54-mile stretch. China's going for 1,000 km/h. Even if they only achieve 800 km/h operationally, that's still triple America's maximum. Here's why this matters beyond trains: Infrastructure capacity signals industrial capability. If China can build and operate 1,000 km/h trains, they can manufacture the precision components, power systems, and control mechanisms that transfer to aerospace, military, and manufacturing. The U.S. won the 20th century partly because it built the Interstate Highway System when others couldn't. China's betting the 21st century winner will be whoever builds impossible infrastructure first. They might fail. Engineering challenges at 1,000 km/h are extreme - air resistance, track precision, emergency braking, passenger safety. But they're trying while America argues whether to fix the L train in New York. Even Chinese failure puts them ahead. You learn more from attempting the impossible than from successfully maintaining mediocrity. Source: Xinhua, CGTN</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0e7fae8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here’s a list of the news outlets who have NOT covered Nick Shirley's fraud story: - NYTimes - CNN -...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ed8cc95</link>
      <description>Here’s a list of the news outlets who have NOT covered Nick Shirley's fraud story: - NYTimes - CNN - Washington Post - MSNBC - NPR - USA Today - Reuters - Axios - ABC News - PBS Every single one of them wrote stories on an Elon Musk hand gesture... …do you get it yet?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ed8cc95</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Trust in media has fallen to its lowest level ever at just 28%. At the same time, 𝕏 recent...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7dde59cd</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Trust in media has fallen to its lowest level ever at just 28%. At the same time, 𝕏 recently recorded all time high usage. That is a clear sign people are shifting where they get their news. 𝕏 is the #1 source of news in the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7dde59cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More than any the daily readership of all newspapers in America combined</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1791e9f0</link>
      <description>More than any the daily readership of all newspapers in America combined</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1791e9f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Corruption</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ee5a304</link>
      <description>Corruption</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ee5a304</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is crazy. In 2022 a disabled Somali whistleblower came forward to expose some of the fraud happ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4c531abd</link>
      <description>This is crazy. In 2022 a disabled Somali whistleblower came forward to expose some of the fraud happening in Minnesota. Afterwards he feared retribution from the Somali community so he fled to Africa but when he arrived there they beat him for talking. 🤣</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4c531abd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48bdd30a</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48bdd30a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starting in 1973, my mom ran an at home day care. Six kids, zero to 5 yrs old, 8 to 10 hrs a day, mo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a4d4c2d8</link>
      <description>Starting in 1973, my mom ran an at home day care. Six kids, zero to 5 yrs old, 8 to 10 hrs a day, mostly by herself, for decades. Her kids still visit her. She never got a million dollar gov't grant for it. States that fund fraud in the name of compassion will get fraud alone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a4d4c2d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Suicidal</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a9e7d5ee</link>
      <description>Suicidal</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a9e7d5ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thanks to you 🤝 by Elon purchasing X a few things happened: - Unlocked free speech on the internet -...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/775ba5fb</link>
      <description>Thanks to you 🤝 by Elon purchasing X a few things happened: - Unlocked free speech on the internet - all other social media platforms had to follow suit or loose viewership - News can be released immediately to millions uncensored from the scene vs going through MSM newsrooms - Fake news is held accountable by the people</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_775ba5fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That is exactly what’s happening</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/64f3d3ee</link>
      <description>That is exactly what’s happening</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_64f3d3ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: One fraudulent business in Minnesota that misspelled “learning” on its building received $1.9M this ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/10407ec5</link>
      <description>One fraudulent business in Minnesota that misspelled “learning” on its building received $1.9M this year while masquerading as a daycare. There are not enough words to describe the breathtaking failure that has happened under the watch of@GovTimWalz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_10407ec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This level of fraud can only happen with the approval of the state. We need trials, hearings, and ja...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8b563723</link>
      <description>This level of fraud can only happen with the approval of the state. We need trials, hearings, and jail time for everyone involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8b563723</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s easy to find</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e073b9f7</link>
      <description>It’s easy to find</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e073b9f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "There is a massive amount of corruption, effectively there’s a giant fraud loophole where the gover...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/09598fa9</link>
      <description>"There is a massive amount of corruption, effectively there’s a giant fraud loophole where the government can send money to an NGO that is then no longer the government by the laws of the U.S." 一 Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_09598fa9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Minnesota daycare fraud by Somalis is nothing new. This news report is from 2018.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c7182e3c</link>
      <description>Minnesota daycare fraud by Somalis is nothing new. This news report is from 2018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c7182e3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Similar to what's currently happening in Minnesota, an investigation into childcare facilities in Ir...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d1baff67</link>
      <description>Similar to what's currently happening in Minnesota, an investigation into childcare facilities in Ireland last year revealed that 7 of the top 10 highest paid companies responsible for looking after vulnerable kids are operated by African or Muslim migrants. It also revealed massive fraud with forged documents used to secure sums of up to €1 million per year per child. Below are the top 10 private companies paid the most by the Irish government to house vulnerable children : 1 - Baig &amp; Mirza Health Services Ltd- Muhammad Usman Baig and Farhan Mirza, foreign. 2 - Comet Care Ltd - Irish 3 - Whisbay Ltd- No info. 4 - Victoria Healthcare Org Ltd- Samson Oluseyi, foreign. 5 - Reign Healthcare - Tariro Taruvinga, foreign. 6 - Good People Homecare Ltd - Gerard and Simbonile Chimbganda, foreign. (Revealed they used fake garda vetting to hire untrained migrant staff). 7 - Ideal Care Services Ltd - Jossy and Karen Akwuobi (Foreign, convicted frauster, received 6 month suspended sentence in March for hiring unvetted staff and forging garda vetting. 8 - Mary Ademola t/a Clarion Healthcare - Adeniyi Ademola, foreign. 9 - Tender Touch Services Ltd - Sylverline Chikwe, foreign. 10- Superior Health Ltd - no info.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d1baff67</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tesla Service Mode is amazing. The amount of info you can see like the individual connector and harn...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6f58f002</link>
      <description>Tesla Service Mode is amazing. The amount of info you can see like the individual connector and harness information is wild. No other cars have this level of integration (and it’s free)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6f58f002</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c32bdaec</link>
      <description>Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. That’s how insanely awful the level of fraud actually is!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c32bdaec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
