<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-12 22:24 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:24:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: startup idea: we sell hand made artisanal code</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a03d41f7</link>
      <description>startup idea: we sell hand made artisanal code</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a03d41f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Some good lists</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cab983a9</link>
      <description>Some good lists</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cab983a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI is going for the endgame win SpaceX is building the Dyson swarm factory intelligence ~ energy th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea3a02e5</link>
      <description>xAI is going for the endgame win SpaceX is building the Dyson swarm factory intelligence ~ energy the way to unlock massive free energy is simply to get compute close to the Sun via a kinetic energy bump mass drivers on the Moon are the most effective way to do the latter</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea3a02e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It's amazing that a simple idea, such as the slope of a tangent line could have so many incredible c...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/64205c76</link>
      <description>It's amazing that a simple idea, such as the slope of a tangent line could have so many incredible consequences. Modern calculus was developed ~365 years ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_64205c76</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 𝕏 is the set of all things</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/04b21812</link>
      <description>𝕏 is the set of all things</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_04b21812</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Keynesian economists perform elaborate mathematical gymnastics to "prove" that $1 of government spen...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea46de3c</link>
      <description>Keynesian economists perform elaborate mathematical gymnastics to "prove" that $1 of government spending magically becomes $1.50 of economic growth. This fiscal multiplier fairy tale ignores what Bastiat called the "unseen" - the productive investments that never happen because resources were seized by bureaucrats first. Every bridge to nowhere represents a thousand private innovations strangled in their cribs. The seen stimulus creates jobs for government contractors and ribbon-cutting ceremonies for politicians. The unseen is the cancer research, the small businesses, the breakthrough technologies that die stillborn because capital was diverted to political pet projects. Modern economies don't multiply wealth through redistribution any more than you create water by moving it between buckets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea46de3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok gets jokesxcancel.com/i/grok/share/18a84c8e4…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e0536c69</link>
      <description>Grok gets jokesxcancel.com/i/grok/share/18a84c8e4…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e0536c69</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Not just anoether theorem. Everything follows from symmetry, except asymmetry or maybe even that too...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c40c191e</link>
      <description>Not just anoether theorem. Everything follows from symmetry, except asymmetry or maybe even that too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c40c191e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I asked ChatGPT and Grok: I want to wash my car, and the car wash is 50m away. Should I walk or driv...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ee57ce05</link>
      <description>I asked ChatGPT and Grok: I want to wash my car, and the car wash is 50m away. Should I walk or drive? Grok: Drive because the car literally needs to be at the car wash to get washed. ChatGPT: Walk! ChatGPT is so dumb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ee57ce05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Only two more senators and America gets a new lease on life</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5ff59c18</link>
      <description>Only two more senators and America gets a new lease on life</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5ff59c18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Here it is:@DOGECONFIRMS: The Illegal aliens who were issued Social Security numbers by the Biden–Ha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b8dc2521</link>
      <description>Here it is:@DOGECONFIRMS: The Illegal aliens who were issued Social Security numbers by the Biden–Harris terrorist administration. • 270,425 in 2021 • 590,193 in 2022 • 964,163 in 2023 • 2,095,247 in 2024 — on it’s way out the door. "They've been using their NGO's to dump fake voter registration forms utilizing the fake SS#'s on key county registrar's offices for the last 5-6 election cycles. Then using those fraudulent voter registrations to request ballots in the mail. Then they pay the NGO's to have their staff fill out the ballots and mail them in."@drawandstrike📝Pass the SAVE Act.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b8dc2521</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Beauty in the subtle imperfections</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2bc2e042</link>
      <description>Beauty in the subtle imperfections</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2bc2e042</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 6 years ago</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a46b9b61</link>
      <description>6 years ago</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a46b9b61</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: There are people who think telling the truth is 'literally violence', but that literal violence is j...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1e0857f6</link>
      <description>There are people who think telling the truth is 'literally violence', but that literal violence is justified against people they disagree with.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1e0857f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The most beautiful theoremsxcancel.com/i/grok/share/958f49e42…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/25bf5b4f</link>
      <description>The most beautiful theoremsxcancel.com/i/grok/share/958f49e42…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_25bf5b4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Building Grok to 10x the productivity of everyone</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ff65fa00</link>
      <description>Building Grok to 10x the productivity of everyone</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ff65fa00</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If you're a journalist interested in telling a balanced narrative and want the 'pro' orbital data ce...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1432aa4b</link>
      <description>If you're a journalist interested in telling a balanced narrative and want the 'pro' orbital data centers logic/math, we've made it VERY VERY easy. These articles are all open and ungated. You can just grok them if you need help parsing the numbers. Please take the time to understand the math and physics behind the pro case before publishing the skeptic case as fact. Launch limiters and initial math -research.33fg.com/analysis/i…Energy Cost from space -research.33fg.com/analysis/o…Location for ODCs why SSO -research.33fg.com/analysis/w…Debunking the cooling/radiator problem -research.33fg.com/analysis/d…The ODC landscape/China's role -research.33fg.com/analysis/o…explaining the Chips for ODCs -research.33fg.com/analysis/e…We take pride in anchoring our analysis in physics and math. We also try to communicate any assumptions when made. We welcome genuine feedback. It's worth noting that we layer on a lot of conservatism in our timelines. I wouldn't be all that surprised that Elon and others make our predictions look stupid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1432aa4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Expansion of consciousness to understand the universe is the reason</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/060ef1cc</link>
      <description>Expansion of consciousness to understand the universe is the reason</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_060ef1cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa93318c</link>
      <description>xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as quickly as xAI, the structure must evolve just like any living organism. This unfortunately required parting ways with some people. We wish them well in future endeavors. We are hiring aggressively. Join xAI if the idea of mass drivers on the Moon appeals to you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa93318c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
