<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-08 15:52 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:52:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wokeism &amp; victimhood ideology in one brutal experiment: Women had fake facial scars applied for job ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e14526ba</link>
      <description>Wokeism &amp; victimhood ideology in one brutal experiment: Women had fake facial scars applied for job interviews. They saw the scars in the mirror. Researchers secretly removed them before the interview. Women believed they were disfigured… and reported MASSIVE discrimination — interviewers "referencing" scars that didn't exist. 57-sec clip — Konstantin Kisin exposes how victim mindset creates its own reality 👇 If you're constantly told you're oppressed, you'll start seeing it everywhere. Your take: Self-fulfilling prophecy or something deeper?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e14526ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Mehdi Hasan is evil</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0ac96943</link>
      <description>Mehdi Hasan is evil</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0ac96943</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Enhance your posts with Grok right in the compose window on 𝕏 It can fix grammar, make your post sho...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f174effd</link>
      <description>Enhance your posts with Grok right in the compose window on 𝕏 It can fix grammar, make your post shorter, or rewrite it in different styles. All of it works with a single click. Try it now!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f174effd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That is exactly what is happening</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ee5d2d40</link>
      <description>That is exactly what is happening</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ee5d2d40</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Unless stopped, the fraud in California, Minnesota and elsewhere will keep increasing until it bankr...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/115470ac</link>
      <description>Unless stopped, the fraud in California, Minnesota and elsewhere will keep increasing until it bankrupts the entire country</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_115470ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Butterfly effect🦋</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a1b2e0ae</link>
      <description>Butterfly effect🦋</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a1b2e0ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just updated my Grok app for iOS to version 1.3.31. Look how absolutely insane this looks ✨</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3fd384db</link>
      <description>Just updated my Grok app for iOS to version 1.3.31. Look how absolutely insane this looks ✨</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3fd384db</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Terrible</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d61b4983</link>
      <description>Terrible</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d61b4983</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This wasn't murder. Renee's death in Minneapolis is tragic. But see it for what it is, not what you ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/41b0e72a</link>
      <description>This wasn't murder. Renee's death in Minneapolis is tragic. But see it for what it is, not what you want it to be. You can hate ICE. But blocking officers then speeding off in a 2-ton vehicle with people at your bumper is irrational. She rolled the dice. Sadly, she died.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_41b0e72a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Becoming multiplanetary is critical to ensuring the long-term survival of humanity and all life as ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d063e863</link>
      <description>"Becoming multiplanetary is critical to ensuring the long-term survival of humanity and all life as we know it". -Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d063e863</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok hits #1 in Norway!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ee2a77b0</link>
      <description>Grok hits #1 in Norway!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ee2a77b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: My jaw dropped watching this Journalist visited 3 locations for a Somalian owned NGO healthcare comp...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4087c109</link>
      <description>My jaw dropped watching this Journalist visited 3 locations for a Somalian owned NGO healthcare company The offices are empty, it’s clear nobody is at the locations They got $14 million dollars last year and a total of $42 MILLION over the past few years Again, $42 MLLION “Legitimately not here. What's shocking to me is that this is the third office that's listed for the Somalian Education Resource Center. They got 14 million dollars just this year There's nothing in there and it looks empty from what the guys are telling me. But where did the $14 million dollars go? This is taxpayer funding. We deserve answers.” “$14 million in a building that smells like weed — Where is the money? Because this, the organization is supposedly 42 million dollars over the past few years in taxpayer funding, and we have no access and we have no idea where it is.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4087c109</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4cfe540f</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4cfe540f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Certainly worthy of a trial to find out</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/87f30ad3</link>
      <description>Certainly worthy of a trial to find out</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_87f30ad3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: When is enough enough?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/38c8733b</link>
      <description>When is enough enough?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_38c8733b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Why the exception, given that it is the worst offender?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/82316f9b</link>
      <description>Why the exception, given that it is the worst offender?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_82316f9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tim Walz is DIRECTLY RESPONSIBLE for up to $9 BILLION IN FRAUD. He can’t just ride into the sunset. ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2f6ad22c</link>
      <description>Tim Walz is DIRECTLY RESPONSIBLE for up to $9 BILLION IN FRAUD. He can’t just ride into the sunset. HE NEEDS TO BE THROWN IN PRISON.foxnews.com/politics/dismiss…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2f6ad22c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That is exactly what they have been doing and it is sure to result in a one-party state, like Califo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9acedbf2</link>
      <description>That is exactly what they have been doing and it is sure to result in a one-party state, like California, but far worse. What holds back California, which is already a one-party supermajority state, from being far worse is that people can move to other states without leaving America. What do you think will happen when there is no escape?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9acedbf2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
