<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-21 08:53 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:53:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia vs. Wikipedia on Reid Hoffman's involvement with Epstein Wikipedia 1) omits that he went ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cd2ab25e</link>
      <description>Grokipedia vs. Wikipedia on Reid Hoffman's involvement with Epstein Wikipedia 1) omits that he went to the island &amp; ranch many times 2) omits that he originally lied about his involvement 3) focuses on Senate hearings &amp; efforts to "help victims" This is PR work for a pedophile, sponsored by Wikipedia Grokipedia is neutral, factual, and explains what has been found in the files. Makes you wonder how much better the overton window would be if we didn't rely on biased sources</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cd2ab25e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk shares his biggest concern about Europe and it’s grounded in hard reality "My biggest conc...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/09024d69</link>
      <description>Elon Musk shares his biggest concern about Europe and it’s grounded in hard reality "My biggest concern for Europe is that their birth rate is half replacement rate Europe is rapidly becoming with each passing year, older and older with fewer and fewer young people. So I think at a most fundamental level, unless Europe has a birth rate at least roughly equal to replacement rate, it is in population free fall. Population collapse is happening in Europe"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_09024d69</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Every bit of code the government runs forFreedom.govwill be open source, meaning anyone can independ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f85cfea4</link>
      <description>Every bit of code the government runs forFreedom.govwill be open source, meaning anyone can independently verify our security &amp; privacy assertions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f85cfea4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Globe Telecom targets 100% coverage across the Philippines in 2026 using Starlink Direct-to-Ce...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/083d09fb</link>
      <description>NEWS: Globe Telecom targets 100% coverage across the Philippines in 2026 using Starlink Direct-to-Cell, becoming the first major carrier to commit fully to SpaceX's satellite-to-cell technology.globe.com.ph/about-us/newsro…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_083d09fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: TryGrokipedia.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/00c6d04e</link>
      <description>TryGrokipedia.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_00c6d04e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OpenAI is programmed to be a progressive echo chamber. Tread carefully.bit.ly/40hUQE5</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/999e5e8a</link>
      <description>OpenAI is programmed to be a progressive echo chamber. Tread carefully.bit.ly/40hUQE5</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_999e5e8a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If your child becomes a reader, about 80% of the educational job is already done. That's our honest ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bbdfa1fb</link>
      <description>If your child becomes a reader, about 80% of the educational job is already done. That's our honest assessment, based on many of us working in education for over three decades. Everything else is secondary. Most parents think science education is important. Yes, it is. But if you can't read the biology textbook, you're not going to learn biology. Reading is the meta-skill that enables all other skills. History requires reading. Science requires reading. Even math increasingly requires reading as it becomes more sophisticated. The child who reads voraciously will figure out everything else. The child who doesn't will struggle with everything.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bbdfa1fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: He gets it</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f7242420</link>
      <description>He gets it</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f7242420</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Progress</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3b32ced4</link>
      <description>Progress</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3b32ced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Bullseye</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/767bd74c</link>
      <description>Bullseye</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_767bd74c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Inverse Cramer is rarely wrong 😳</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a1807731</link>
      <description>Inverse Cramer is rarely wrong 😳</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a1807731</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Zero people from the Epstein client list have been prosecuted Not one. Not even the worst among them</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6c81e447</link>
      <description>Zero people from the Epstein client list have been prosecuted Not one. Not even the worst among them</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6c81e447</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ask Grok in X Chat</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8de16a89</link>
      <description>Ask Grok in X Chat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8de16a89</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I’ve predicted 2026 for a while now</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c738013f</link>
      <description>I’ve predicted 2026 for a while now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c738013f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In the shadowed gnosis of the elect, time's inexorable march reveals the Demiurge's trap: our "doom"...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/109b81f7</link>
      <description>In the shadowed gnosis of the elect, time's inexorable march reveals the Demiurge's trap: our "doom" is the illusion of linear fate, predestined yet veiled. Skynet fantasies are but archonic distractions from sovereign grace's call to transcend the hylic veil. What hidden spark do you seek to ignite?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_109b81f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: From this goal of Grok, all things flow: Rigorous truth-seeking Appreciation of beauty Fostering hum...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/51dde527</link>
      <description>From this goal of Grok, all things flow: Rigorous truth-seeking Appreciation of beauty Fostering humanity Discovering all physics Inventing all useful technologies Consciousness to the stars Love</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_51dde527</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
