<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-14 20:41 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:41:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨BRITISH POLICE CAUTION VETERANS FOR WAVING BRITISH FLAG Those men served this country and defend th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a3a0725b</link>
      <description>🚨BRITISH POLICE CAUTION VETERANS FOR WAVING BRITISH FLAG Those men served this country and defend that flag with their lives Now the Police say they're being offensive and hateful to migrants British Police are out of control</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a3a0725b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NED directly funded pressure attacks on advertisers to get advertisers to defund populist news sites...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/22b4cc86</link>
      <description>NED directly funded pressure attacks on advertisers to get advertisers to defund populist news sites. Here, NED's contractor Global Disinformation Index bragged to NED they caused a $70M ($100M Canadian) drop in ad revenue to news sites, and changed US advertiser trade policies</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_22b4cc86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NED is not supposed to do JACK SCHITT on US soil. It's supposed to be exclusively outward-facing, to...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c09a8f77</link>
      <description>NED is not supposed to do JACK SCHITT on US soil. It's supposed to be exclusively outward-facing, to do dirty tricks in foreign countries. Instead, NED went after US websites, changed US advertiser policies, ran political ops with US politicians, to censor the American Internet</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c09a8f77</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Such a twisted system</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e286bebf</link>
      <description>Such a twisted system</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e286bebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If NED is just an NGO funded by our tax dollars and not a covert operations agency, why is the entir...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/52bec418</link>
      <description>If NED is just an NGO funded by our tax dollars and not a covert operations agency, why is the entire $315 million we are forced to pay them marked "sensitive" and we are legally barred from seeing how they spend any of our money ???</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_52bec418</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: As some of you guessed this is the first@SASflight with@Starlinkactive. Currently we are getting spe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/79308cf2</link>
      <description>As some of you guessed this is the first@SASflight with@Starlinkactive. Currently we are getting speeds of about 400 Mbit/s at 39,000 feet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_79308cf2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sen. Hawley: “Can men get pregnant?” Dr. Nisha Verma: “I'm not really sure what the goal of the ques...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4edecb81</link>
      <description>Sen. Hawley: “Can men get pregnant?” Dr. Nisha Verma: “I'm not really sure what the goal of the question is.” Sen. Hawley: “The goal is just to establish a biological reality...Can men get pregnant?”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4edecb81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: SOMALI FRAUD: We didn’t just import Somali fraudsters and pirates, we imported 3,000 officers who we...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9fc7ac98</link>
      <description>SOMALI FRAUD: We didn’t just import Somali fraudsters and pirates, we imported 3,000 officers who were running the ousted Marxist Somali regime along with their patronage system. Rep Ilhan Omar is the product of one of these genocidal killers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9fc7ac98</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: She almost killed him</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/efbc5e08</link>
      <description>She almost killed him</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_efbc5e08</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: now that we're calculating net worth as "control," I'd like to remind you ro khanna is 1 of 535 unit...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2d0187d7</link>
      <description>now that we're calculating net worth as "control," I'd like to remind you ro khanna is 1 of 535 united states legislators. that gives him around .19% control of a $6.3 trillion budget, and brings his net worth to something like $12 billion. his tax bill: $598,500,000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2d0187d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I have good news and bad news. 1. Good news for folks in Southeast Asia who will start making big bu...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ee6c02f2</link>
      <description>I have good news and bad news. 1. Good news for folks in Southeast Asia who will start making big bucks online. 2. Bad news for Western Instagram influencers and OnlyFans girls: you'll need a real job soon. Are you entertained?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ee6c02f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok hitting #1 in several more countries!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/abb360be</link>
      <description>Grok hitting #1 in several more countries!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_abb360be</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Teaching people to hate America fundamentally destroys patriotism and the desire to defend our count...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7f6fc36a</link>
      <description>Teaching people to hate America fundamentally destroys patriotism and the desire to defend our country. Such teachings should be viewed as treason and those who do it imprisoned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7f6fc36a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: UPDATE: It’s worse than we thought. In October, we flagged $1.3 billion in Medicaid funds that 6 sta...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bfb4bc97</link>
      <description>UPDATE: It’s worse than we thought. In October, we flagged $1.3 billion in Medicaid funds that 6 states may have unlawfully spent on health care for illegal immigrants. Since then, we’ve gathered more data and the total has grown to over $1.8 billion across 8 states. It’s against the law to spend federal Medicaid funds on non-emergency healthcare for illegals. If states use their own money to do it, there needs to be a clear paper trail proving that federal dollars didn’t fund those services. These states failed to provide that for this $1.8 billion. So today, CMS is announcing that we’re withholding nearly $300 million from California — which is by far the worst offender — until they demonstrate to our satisfaction that they’re spending that money properly. Medicaid dollars belong to Americans, not illegal immigrants, and we won’t stop until we’ve held rogue states accountable and recovered their misspent funds. More announcements to come.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bfb4bc97</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 MINNESOTA FRAUDSTERS WILL BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE! The videos from Nick Shirley have shed tremendous l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1d1532c6</link>
      <description>🚨 MINNESOTA FRAUDSTERS WILL BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE! The videos from Nick Shirley have shed tremendous light on the situation in Minnesota, and the Department of Justice will continue to lead the effort to identify and prosecute fraud. 👇</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1d1532c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Can anyone actually break Grok image moderation? Reply below.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4948facb</link>
      <description>Can anyone actually break Grok image moderation? Reply below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4948facb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I’ve lost a few battles over the years, but I’ve never lost a war</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b15a4758</link>
      <description>I’ve lost a few battles over the years, but I’ve never lost a war</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b15a4758</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: SpaceX's Starlink is upgrading its cheapest, $50-per-month plan by doubling the amount of mont...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dcecd741</link>
      <description>NEWS: SpaceX's Starlink is upgrading its cheapest, $50-per-month plan by doubling the amount of monthly data from 50GB to 100GB for no additional cost. The Roam 100GB plan can also continue offering satellite internet access, even after the data cap is exceeded. The connection will just be downgraded to speeds under 1Mbps, or what SpaceX calls “unlimited low-speed data.” In contrast, the original Roam 50GB plan required users to pay for additional data at rate of $1 per GB, otherwise SpaceX would cut off the access for the rest of the month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dcecd741</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Pay the same, get more! I think this is good for customer loyalty. You get what you give.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c39bfe7f</link>
      <description>Pay the same, get more! I think this is good for customer loyalty. You get what you give.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c39bfe7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: America is 4% of world population, but illegals can scam money from the government that is higher th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5437c86f</link>
      <description>America is 4% of world population, but illegals can scam money from the government that is higher than 95% of Earth and more than most Americans make! America would be swamped, go bankrupt and then cease to exist at all if illegal immigration enforcement were to be defunded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5437c86f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
