<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-16 18:59 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: So many of our sentencing guidelines and attitudes towards crime are exactly backwards. A guy who ra...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b0a3e239</link>
      <description>So many of our sentencing guidelines and attitudes towards crime are exactly backwards. A guy who randomly kills an old man because he’s having a bad day is much *more* of a public danger than someone who carefully plans the murder of a personal enemy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b0a3e239</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fact. Birth control is poison for your body and mind.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bb52e854</link>
      <description>Fact. Birth control is poison for your body and mind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bb52e854</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Peaceful protests do not result in the destruction of federal vehicles and theft of federal property...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/38b03aba</link>
      <description>Peaceful protests do not result in the destruction of federal vehicles and theft of federal property.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_38b03aba</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: An address in Atlanta Georgia has 70 people registered to vote, but the building has been closed for...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/38de0bae</link>
      <description>An address in Atlanta Georgia has 70 people registered to vote, but the building has been closed for 10 years!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_38de0bae</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: How does South Africa have 145 racist laws and it’s not considered racist and gets a free pass, but ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa9c81d2</link>
      <description>How does South Africa have 145 racist laws and it’s not considered racist and gets a free pass, but the US doesn't have any racist laws yet somehow people think it's the most racist country in the world?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa9c81d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And that plan has worked well until now</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2d4b8de0</link>
      <description>And that plan has worked well until now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2d4b8de0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The real insurrection isn’t happening in the streets of Minnesota, it’s happening in the halls of Co...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2e65a161</link>
      <description>The real insurrection isn’t happening in the streets of Minnesota, it’s happening in the halls of Congress, where Republican politicians are refusing to carry out the will of the people who elected them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2e65a161</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: During a Green Card background check at our office in San Jose, California, two simultaneous layers ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/72004824</link>
      <description>During a Green Card background check at our office in San Jose, California, two simultaneous layers of screening revealed a shocking discovery: The applicant was wanted for homicide by the Mexican government!@DEAHQ@ICEgovand@USMarshalsHQare now taking care of it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_72004824</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: GET IT DONE TO SAVE AMERICA</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/91d50111</link>
      <description>GET IT DONE TO SAVE AMERICA</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_91d50111</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Marques Brownlee has released his new Model Y Performance review. "It is the best self-driving in an...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8d81e1ff</link>
      <description>Marques Brownlee has released his new Model Y Performance review. "It is the best self-driving in any car I've ever tried; I think this is the best looking back of any Tesla ever." Full video:youtu.be/watch?v=MnjNgtPr…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8d81e1ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Obama-era ICE was “keeping communities safe". Now it's "fascism".</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f45a2011</link>
      <description>Obama-era ICE was “keeping communities safe". Now it's "fascism".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f45a2011</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ireland was never a colonial power, so “revenge” is out of the question. Yet, the entire third world...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5bbc20e5</link>
      <description>Ireland was never a colonial power, so “revenge” is out of the question. Yet, the entire third world is there now. Catching on yet?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5bbc20e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ilhan Omar committed fraud</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8d91f094</link>
      <description>Ilhan Omar committed fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8d91f094</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: At one level, one has to admire the entrepreneurial spirit of the Somali scammers — with just a few ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8078dabf</link>
      <description>At one level, one has to admire the entrepreneurial spirit of the Somali scammers — with just a few Quality Learing Centers, they built an industrial scale fraud operation nearly on par with USAID, a feat which took our best educated deep staters decades to do …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8078dabf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Tesla spotted testing the redesigned Tesla Semi for the first time in Fremont, CA. • Model Y s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7da3001a</link>
      <description>NEWS: Tesla spotted testing the redesigned Tesla Semi for the first time in Fremont, CA. • Model Y style light bar • More efficient • Increased payload capability • 1.7kWh/mile (15% improvement vs old Semi) • Designed for autonomy • 500 mile range • 1.2MW (1,200kW) peak charging speed • 800kW drive power • Side windows don't go as far back • Heavy duty metal anti-slip traction strips on side steps • A lot more under the skin improvements Volume production starts soon. Drone footage via MetGod:youtu.be/watch?v=HNJ2_25k…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7da3001a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OPENAI FOUNDERS PLOTTED TO OUST ELON IN 2017 New court docs reveal the plot was never about "safety"...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/550ac9f2</link>
      <description>OPENAI FOUNDERS PLOTTED TO OUST ELON IN 2017 New court docs reveal the plot was never about "safety" it was about getting rich Greg Brockman’s private diary from Sept 2017 exposes the scheme to kick Elon out: "This is the only chance we have to get out from Elon... Financially, what will take me to $1B?" He admitted that keeping Elon involved would "nuke the economics" for the founders They were already plotting to ditch the non-profit mission and sideline Musk- while publicly preaching "benefit humanity" They were privately calculating how to become billionaires The mask slips 🤡</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_550ac9f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: STARLINK NEWS: Globe Telecom has partnered with SpaceX to introduce Starlink Direct-to-Cell (DTC) in...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d6ae7b77</link>
      <description>STARLINK NEWS: Globe Telecom has partnered with SpaceX to introduce Starlink Direct-to-Cell (DTC) in the Philippines, marking the first deployment of this technology in Southeast Asia and the second in Asia. The service enables standard LTE smartphones to connect directly to Starlink's constellation to provide text messaging, voice, data, and internet-of-things services in remote, underserved, or no-coverage areas without requiring additional hardware or apps. A ceremonial Memorandum of Agreement signing was witnessed by Philippines President Ferdinand Marcos Jr., the initiative supports digital inclusion under the theme "Every Filipino Connected" and aims for commercial availability starting in March 2026. SpaceX's Starlink Sr Partnership Manager, Damien Innes, represented the company and signed the agreement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d6ae7b77</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Stephen Miller just CALLED OUT what's happening across America between Democrats and DHS a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/645e210e</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Stephen Miller just CALLED OUT what's happening across America between Democrats and DHS and he didn't HOLD BACK! "This is clearly an INSURGENCY against the federal government. They are describing the federal government as an occupying force." "If you were to permit individual cities and states to ratify their own immigration laws for themselves, then you wouldn't have a republic and you wouldn't have a country, and that's the proposition that Fry and Ellison and Walsh are trying to test." "They are asserting that they have the unfettered right to harbor aliens who have no right to be in this country, and to incite a violent insurrection from organized agitators against federal forces to prevent those federal forces from effectuating duly enacted immigration law." It's time to INVOKE THE INSURRECTION ACT NOW!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_645e210e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Feeling Optimustic about the future!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/627d016d</link>
      <description>Feeling Optimustic about the future!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_627d016d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
