<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-22 04:31 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:31:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: QT Green Eyes</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/847080f6</link>
      <description>QT Green Eyes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_847080f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “We were told to label newly arrived ILLEGALS as ‘PERMANENTLY disabled’ — even for headaches or back...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7cebf858</link>
      <description>“We were told to label newly arrived ILLEGALS as ‘PERMANENTLY disabled’ — even for headaches or back pain — so they’d get Social Security for LIFE.” “Once they’re classified, that’s it — they’re set FOREVER. That’s exactly what they wanted us to do.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7cebf858</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON: THE ECONOMY IS NOT A MAGIC CORNUCOPIA “Some people have this absurd view that the economy is l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1818bc6a</link>
      <description>ELON: THE ECONOMY IS NOT A MAGIC CORNUCOPIA “Some people have this absurd view that the economy is like some magic horn of plenty. Like it just makes stuff. Goods and services just come from this magic corner of plenty. And if somebody has more stuff than somebody else, it’s because they took more from this magic corner of plenty.” Source:@joerogan</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1818bc6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: WE ARE REALLY TRYING TO BRING THE WORLD TOGETHER INTO A COLLECTIVE CONSCIOUSNESS 𝕏 is kin...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fe1fe95a</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: WE ARE REALLY TRYING TO BRING THE WORLD TOGETHER INTO A COLLECTIVE CONSCIOUSNESS 𝕏 is kind of a global town square where people can say what they want to say with words, pictures, video Where there's a secure messaging system we've recently added the ability to do audio and video calls So really trying to bring the world together into a collective consciousness And that's different from just saying, 'What is the most dopamine-generating video stream that one could make?' Which I think can be a little bit of brain rot If you're just watching videos that cause dopamine hits one after another but lack substance, then I think that's not a great way to spend time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fe1fe95a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Jordan Peterson: "Second guessing Elon Musk is a fools game"</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2d0f26ed</link>
      <description>Jordan Peterson: "Second guessing Elon Musk is a fools game"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2d0f26ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "If in 10 years, all American troops stationed in Europe have not been returned to the US, then this...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b000f1e3</link>
      <description>"If in 10 years, all American troops stationed in Europe have not been returned to the US, then this whole project [NATO] will have failed… We must get these people to stand on their own feet militarily." - Dwight D. Eisenhower (1951) First Supreme Allied Commander of NATO</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b000f1e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I was interviewed by BBC along w/@ChiOnwurahabout@Keir_StarmerCOS Morgan McSweeney, who started Cent...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2f262fac</link>
      <description>I was interviewed by BBC along w/@ChiOnwurahabout@Keir_StarmerCOS Morgan McSweeney, who started Center for Countering Digital Hate (CCDH). Onwurah lied to listeners claiming "Conservatives" passed Online Safety Act, no Morgan McSweeney's CCDH. Yes, but the Conservative was Damien Collins, who was on the board of CCDH. Does Onwurah not know what's going on inside her own government?@EthanCroft98@paddymacc1@AvaSantina@WorldByWolf@jodymcintyre_@kennardmatt@Ian_Fraser@NJ_Timothy@SteveNickSmith@CharlotteCGill@JuliaHB1</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2f262fac</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Report: Parents who raised $170,000 by claiming ICE gassed their kids on the way home from a basketb...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1bcec92e</link>
      <description>Report: Parents who raised $170,000 by claiming ICE gassed their kids on the way home from a basketball game lied about the whole thingnotthebee.com/article/report…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1bcec92e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine now does 10 second videos with better video and much better audio</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/583dfdd4</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine now does 10 second videos with better video and much better audio</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_583dfdd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Is requiring photo ID to vote a reasonable measure to protect the integrity of elections? YES - All ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c05118e</link>
      <description>Is requiring photo ID to vote a reasonable measure to protect the integrity of elections? YES - All Voters: 73% Men: 69% Women: 76% 18-29: 70% 30-39: 70% 40-49: 80% 50-64: 77% 65+: 67% White: 73% Black: 70% Hispanic: 69% Other: 83% DEM: 64% IND: 69% GOP: 86%</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c05118e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Solar power is a really big deal.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/25a62fb2</link>
      <description>Solar power is a really big deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_25a62fb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine now 10 seconds with improved video &amp; audio</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b3988341</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine now 10 seconds with improved video &amp; audio</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b3988341</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: SpaceX says it is aiming to roll out its second-generation cellular@Starlinksystem in 2027, ac...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cb73895c</link>
      <description>NEWS: SpaceX says it is aiming to roll out its second-generation cellular@Starlinksystem in 2027, according to new FCC filing. "SpaceX’s first generation service is providing coverage to over 400 million people, with more than 6 million customers accessing the service each month. But this is only the beginning: SpaceX has also invested in spectrum that will enable it to launch a greatly enhanced second generation direct-to-device system in 2027."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cb73895c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Over 2,500 airplanes now have@Starlinkinstalled. Airlines/operators that are currently using or are ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/eec62f0c</link>
      <description>Over 2,500 airplanes now have@Starlinkinstalled. Airlines/operators that are currently using or are in contract to install Starlink internet on their fleet: • United Airlines • British Airways • Lufthansa Airlines • Emirates • Qatar Airlines • Air France • Hawaiian Airlines • Alaska Airlines • Virgin Atlantic • Air Baltic • Air New Zealand • flydubai • Scandinavian Airlines • WestJet • JSX • ZipAir The 2,500 number includes private planes, business jets and commercial aircraft. SpaceX has a long backlog for aviation installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_eec62f0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: STARLINK: Today, Prabhakar Jayakumar (@prabhakarpj), SpaceX's Head of Starlink India, and the Govern...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7d6aca26</link>
      <description>STARLINK: Today, Prabhakar Jayakumar (@prabhakarpj), SpaceX's Head of Starlink India, and the Government of Goa signed a non-commercial Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to explore Starlink for digital inclusion, smart governance, disaster response, coastal safety, tourism, and public services in remote areas. The agreement, witnessed by Chief Minister Dr Pramod Sawant and IT Minister Rohan Khaunte, includes piloting the service to schools, healthcare facilities, and disaster centers. More news in the EC below!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7d6aca26</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Correct</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2b1397cd</link>
      <description>Correct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2b1397cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Insurance is half price when Tesla self-driving is activated, because it increases safety so much</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3c80061d</link>
      <description>Insurance is half price when Tesla self-driving is activated, because it increases safety so much</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3c80061d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
