<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-13 03:54 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:54:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Groks Grokxcancel.com/i/grok/share/iKfOwWsQv…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/99f39ea1</link>
      <description>Grok Groks Grokxcancel.com/i/grok/share/iKfOwWsQv…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_99f39ea1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Beautiful Grok video</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/12046280</link>
      <description>Beautiful Grok video</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_12046280</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Who is excited to build a base on the Moon? Grok Imagine brought this to life</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0dee66ac</link>
      <description>Who is excited to build a base on the Moon? Grok Imagine brought this to life</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0dee66ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Anything I say, the legacy media is going to take a sound bite out of what I say, and misconstrue w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/548ec61d</link>
      <description>“Anything I say, the legacy media is going to take a sound bite out of what I say, and misconstrue what I'm saying.” Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_548ec61d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Thank you, Elon Musk. Because what he's done has helped shape society in MANY ways. The election, s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b888df68</link>
      <description>"Thank you, Elon Musk. Because what he's done has helped shape society in MANY ways. The election, so we can all speak freely in the US. You're seeing the ripple effect."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b888df68</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk’s monologue on Saturday Night Live.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/71e2f288</link>
      <description>Elon Musk’s monologue on Saturday Night Live.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_71e2f288</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Amazing timelapse of a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket booster returning to Earth from space</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ad308c18</link>
      <description>Amazing timelapse of a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket booster returning to Earth from space</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ad308c18</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The future should look like the future Robovan is 🤯</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6aed4019</link>
      <description>The future should look like the future Robovan is 🤯</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6aed4019</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Boring Company is going to end soul sucking traffic. Today traffic exists bc we keep forcing a 3D wo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b8eba4fd</link>
      <description>Boring Company is going to end soul sucking traffic. Today traffic exists bc we keep forcing a 3D world to move on 2D roads. Building and cities continue to grow upwards, while roads keep staying flat. That’s the problem this company is solving. The Boring Company goes underground where space is essentially unlimited. Think about it: • Roads are 2D • Tunnels are 3D and you can scale them as deep as you want, endlessly. When cars move through underground tunnels, 1/ Trips become straight lines 2/ Driving becomes safer 3/ Traffic disappears 4/ Commutes shrink from painful hours to peaceful minutes 5/ Stress drops significantly Boring Tunnels simplify trips. You just get in, the Tesla drives you, and then you arrive. These are one of those things that is so simple, yet so impactful. Boring Company is a game changer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b8eba4fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This has been happening for years. Ilhan Omar is the most obvious example. A large number of relativ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c31c371a</link>
      <description>This has been happening for years. Ilhan Omar is the most obvious example. A large number of relatively recently arrived Somalis will elect only a Somali to Congress in that Minnesota district. This is much more subtle, but just as bad, in many other parts of America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c31c371a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Are you sitting down? California NGOs: 213,720 $593.4 billion/year New York NGOs: 132,097 $445.8 bil...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d70e2a82</link>
      <description>Are you sitting down? California NGOs: 213,720 $593.4 billion/year New York NGOs: 132,097 $445.8 billion/year Minnesota NGOs: 41,267 $124.2 billion/year New Jersey NGOs: 56,332 $113 billion/year Washington NGOs: 44,332 $139.5 billion/year Just a few. Imagine the fraud…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d70e2a82</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You can’t legally get a tattoo until you’re 18 because it’s a "permanent decision Yet they push pube...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/42f07251</link>
      <description>You can’t legally get a tattoo until you’re 18 because it’s a "permanent decision Yet they push puberty blockers on children that permanently alter their biology It starts with indoctrination and ends with irreversible damage Those who push this on innocent children are criminals. Just as Elon said</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_42f07251</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Suicidally dumb 🤡</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/314397ad</link>
      <description>Suicidally dumb 🤡</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_314397ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: California state government spending on waste &amp; fraud will keep increasing until the GOLDEN STATE ha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/69a05ebd</link>
      <description>California state government spending on waste &amp; fraud will keep increasing until the GOLDEN STATE has COOKED all the GOLDEN GEESE. Mark my words. This has always been inevitable and is not due to Newsom or any individual. The Democratic Party is utterly controlled by the unions and the trial lawyers and California is a one-party state. Any politician nominally “in charge” of California has two choices: 1. Stop sending crazy money to the public sector unions and law firms. 2. Sacrifice the most productive citizens to pay the graft. They will always pick the second choice, because they will lose their primary if they pick the first. Only bankruptcy will force a righting of the state, but, between now and then, they will feast on the golden geese who were laying the golden eggs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_69a05ebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That’s a lot of fake voters …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/12053c7c</link>
      <description>That’s a lot of fake voters …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_12053c7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: California issues nearly $100B per year of new debt. Their current long-term liabilities are $1.37T,...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e8394008</link>
      <description>California issues nearly $100B per year of new debt. Their current long-term liabilities are $1.37T, almost half of which is unfunded pension liabilities. That's ~$34,300/person of liability. They paid $6.5B in 2025 just to service the debt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e8394008</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Live at@StarbaseTX!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/238398c3</link>
      <description>Live at@StarbaseTX!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_238398c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
