<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-11 22:31 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 22:31:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "I have the distinct honor to say that we lost white population"- former NY Rep. Charles Barron (D) ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fd6a1162</link>
      <description>"I have the distinct honor to say that we lost white population"- former NY Rep. Charles Barron (D) Listen to the crowd's reaction</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fd6a1162</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: Nothing any of my companies have done has been to stifle competition In fact, we’ve done ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/481389e7</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: Nothing any of my companies have done has been to stifle competition In fact, we’ve done the opposite So at Tesla, we have open-sourced our patents. Anyone can use our patents for free How many companies do you know who’ve done that? Can you name one? I can’t At SpaceX, we don’t use patents. Once in a while, we’ll file a patent just so some patent troll doesn’t cause trouble, but we’re not stopping anyone We’ve done nothing anti-competitive We’ve done nothing to stop our competitors. I just want to clarify for the audience, because some companies have done anti-competitive things. I think the unusual thing about SpaceX and Tesla is that we’ve done things that have helped our competition So at Tesla, we have made our Supercharger system open access. We’ve made our charger technology available for free to other manufacturers</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_481389e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the trans kiIIer who gunned down 35 kids in Canada</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/735d8881</link>
      <description>This is the trans kiIIer who gunned down 35 kids in Canada</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_735d8881</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cybertruck on the Moon</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cb70652d</link>
      <description>Cybertruck on the Moon</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cb70652d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And they’re better cars</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9fb7bdee</link>
      <description>And they’re better cars</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9fb7bdee</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starship will be able to do both the Moon and Mars. The destination, as I wrote in Rocket Dreams, do...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9ad9a2ca</link>
      <description>Starship will be able to do both the Moon and Mars. The destination, as I wrote in Rocket Dreams, doesn't matter as much as the means of ascent. The good news is: we're GOING.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9ad9a2ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I don’t need to conduct a research study to identify that there is an undeniable pattern of violence...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b8fbe26a</link>
      <description>I don’t need to conduct a research study to identify that there is an undeniable pattern of violence here. Another Trans person just shot 35 people, killing 10 in Canada. Giving mentally ill people cross sex hormones to affirm a delusion is DANGEROUS. Knowing this is COMMON SENSE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b8fbe26a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Between 2020 and 2023 California added over 24,000 regulatory restrictions. At the federal level gro...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/92472ab9</link>
      <description>Between 2020 and 2023 California added over 24,000 regulatory restrictions. At the federal level growth in regulatory restrictions has been pretty consistent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_92472ab9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NASA’s@SpaceXCrew-12 Falcon 9 rocket and Crew Dragon spacecraft are seen at sunset earlier tonight.@...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a6aa910c</link>
      <description>NASA’s@SpaceXCrew-12 Falcon 9 rocket and Crew Dragon spacecraft are seen at sunset earlier tonight.@NASAastronauts@Astro_Jessicaand@astro_hathaway,@esaastronaut@Soph_astro, and@roscosmoscosmonaut Andrey Fedyaev are scheduled to launch to@Space_Stationno earlier than Friday, Feb. 13 from Space Launch Complex 40 on Cape Canaveral Space Force Station. 📷flic.kr/s/aHBqjCK3Cd</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a6aa910c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Sauron-Appointed Judge Rules Frodo Must Return Ring To Sauronbuff.ly/LTl6zNX</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6fdb84d2</link>
      <description>Sauron-Appointed Judge Rules Frodo Must Return Ring To Sauronbuff.ly/LTl6zNX</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6fdb84d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The trans kid who murdered over ten people, and injured more, also killed his mother and younger bro...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b8694a3</link>
      <description>The trans kid who murdered over ten people, and injured more, also killed his mother and younger brother. Turns out, supporting your children in their sexual delusions will probably get you killed too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b8694a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Please contact these senators to confirm that you want voter ID required in elections in America</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a695c17e</link>
      <description>Please contact these senators to confirm that you want voter ID required in elections in America</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a695c17e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 22:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I once again hate to say I told you so</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ec6bd5cc</link>
      <description>I once again hate to say I told you so</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ec6bd5cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 22:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tesla Cybertruck is one of the best pickup trucks you can buy right now Cybertruck earned a Top Safe...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e2e6408c</link>
      <description>Tesla Cybertruck is one of the best pickup trucks you can buy right now Cybertruck earned a Top Safety Pick+ with a perfect "Good" rating in all major crash tests, making it the only pickup truck to achieve the highest IIHS safety tier in 2025 It also holds a five-star overall rating from NHTSA That’s top-level safety But it does much more: •⁠ ⁠123 kWh battery - equal to about 9 Tesla Powerwalls •⁠ ⁠Can power your house for 3–4 days during a blackout •⁠ ⁠Heavy waterproof and built for extreme conditions •⁠ ⁠Can carry heavy loads and still go faster than most pickup trucks •⁠ ⁠Ultra-Hard 30X Cold-Rolled stainless steel exoskeleton - 7x stronger than typical exterior steel • Cyberbeast: 0-60 mph in 2.6 seconds - faster than most sports cars Cyber truck is a safety + powerhouse on wheels….</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e2e6408c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 22:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok just ranked #1 in first-month new user growth ratio. Outpacing Gemini, ChatGPT, Claud...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d2aedb3b</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok just ranked #1 in first-month new user growth ratio. Outpacing Gemini, ChatGPT, Claude, and others. Momentum is accelerating. 🚀</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d2aedb3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 22:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING Senator Joni Ernst (R-IA) just signed on as a cosponsor of the SAVE America Act. With@Based...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6e5f14cb</link>
      <description>BREAKING Senator Joni Ernst (R-IA) just signed on as a cosponsor of the SAVE America Act. With@BasedMikeLeeas the sponsor &amp; 39 cosponsors, we’re up to 40 Senators in support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6e5f14cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 22:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is what happens when Elon runs your company. xAI which is only 2.5 yrs old and has a team size ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7be397a4</link>
      <description>This is what happens when Elon runs your company. xAI which is only 2.5 yrs old and has a team size that is 1/10th of many competitors, its #1 in voice, image generation, image edits, forecasting, and many intelligence leaderboards, all while having the most powerful training center in the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7be397a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 22:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa93318c</link>
      <description>xAI was reorganized a few days ago to improve speed of execution. As a company grows, especially as quickly as xAI, the structure must evolve just like any living organism. This unfortunately required parting ways with some people. We wish them well in future endeavors. We are hiring aggressively. Join xAI if the idea of mass drivers on the Moon appeals to you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa93318c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 22:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
