<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-29 14:47 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:47:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Fraud so blatant that they don’t even bother with having a show kid or sending fake pics of kids</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6de43518</link>
      <description>Fraud so blatant that they don’t even bother with having a show kid or sending fake pics of kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6de43518</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Two years ago, a British woman, distraught over the murder of 3 little girls, tweeted that she didn'...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5016d4a0</link>
      <description>Two years ago, a British woman, distraught over the murder of 3 little girls, tweeted that she didn't care if migrant hotels burned. Then she deleted it. She got 31 months in prison. Yesterday, Britain's leaders gave a hero's welcome and citizenship to an Egyptian man who's tweeted his desire to kill Jews, denied the Holocaust happened, called English people 'dogs &amp; monkeys', said police should be killed and that white people are a 'blight' that needs to be wiped out by genocide. Never deleted any of it. I know we in the US have a lot of our own problems, too, but Britain has gone completely nuts. Do these politicians have any idea how insane this all looks to the rest of the world?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5016d4a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Still no coverage in NYT, WaPo, CNN, or Minneapolis Star-Tribune of massive fraud being uncovered in...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/734c2be1</link>
      <description>Still no coverage in NYT, WaPo, CNN, or Minneapolis Star-Tribune of massive fraud being uncovered in Minnesota. The media's willingness to ignore stories that hurt Democrats is truly astonishing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_734c2be1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Whatever is incentivized will happen</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1e94f20a</link>
      <description>Whatever is incentivized will happen</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1e94f20a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Evil …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c48630cd</link>
      <description>Evil …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c48630cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk is making an exciting future.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/eda93927</link>
      <description>Elon Musk is making an exciting future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_eda93927</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 BREAKING: Elon Musk is again saying we MUST mass impeach and remove leftist judges after Somali fr...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c12c207c</link>
      <description>🚨 BREAKING: Elon Musk is again saying we MUST mass impeach and remove leftist judges after Somali fraudsters were let free despite robbing the taxpayer out of MILLIONS in Minnesota "As President Bukele eloquently articulates, there is no other option. We must impeach to save democracy." 💯 Leftist judges are a threat to our republic, and a threat to citizens and taxpayers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c12c207c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And the fraud will just keep rising unless stopped</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2a470a7c</link>
      <description>And the fraud will just keep rising unless stopped</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2a470a7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You'll find thousands of articles mentioning "Trump targeting Somalis" and how "vulnerable" they are...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b444462c</link>
      <description>You'll find thousands of articles mentioning "Trump targeting Somalis" and how "vulnerable" they are But literally zero articles about the actual Somali daycare fraud happening in broad daylight....the one that's been draining taxpayer money for years Why aren't they writing about the real story? Why is no one asking: • Where did that money go? • Why is the media protecting the fraudsters? • Why are they actively covering this up? I seriously don't understand how every outlet is collectively trying to bury this</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b444462c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yeah, it’s clear as day</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e80c346a</link>
      <description>Yeah, it’s clear as day</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e80c346a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: X is proud to support the legal case of Michelle Evans. Ms. Evans faces potential criminal charges f...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/41bdc834</link>
      <description>X is proud to support the legal case of Michelle Evans. Ms. Evans faces potential criminal charges for reposting a picture of a male transgender activist using the sink to wash his hands in the women’s restroom in the Texas State Capitol in May 2023. Ms. Evans did not even take the photo. She merely posted it on X as part of political commentary on transgender issues. Yet, shortly after, the Travis County District Attorney launched a criminal investigation into her post. The First Amendment protects Ms. Evans' speech, yet in a 2-1 vote, the Fifth Circuit Court of Appeals issued a misguided and dangerous opinion allowing the criminal investigation to go forward. X is therefore assisting Ms. Evans in pursuing an appeal before all 17 judges of the Fifth Circuit. We look forward to the full Fifth Circuit correcting this wrong and preserving free speech, which is the foundation of American democracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_41bdc834</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Waymo does not respond to sirens from police cars or firetruck. However, Tesla vehicles respond to t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f6b53c42</link>
      <description>Waymo does not respond to sirens from police cars or firetruck. However, Tesla vehicles respond to those sirens and stop the vehicle on the shoulder. We have seen these things through many videos. Tesla is the only vehicle that understands the real world best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f6b53c42</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This one doesn’t exactly require Sherlock Holmes to figure it out, just someone who is brave and car...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b16b021b</link>
      <description>This one doesn’t exactly require Sherlock Holmes to figure it out, just someone who is brave and cares</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b16b021b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good to know I’ve been slaving away for 2+ decades … taking on 100% of the bankruptcy risk, litigati...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/58ccde2a</link>
      <description>Good to know I’ve been slaving away for 2+ decades … taking on 100% of the bankruptcy risk, litigation risk, tax risk, audit risk, With all the daily headaches of matters of: •employment, •sales, •accounting, •legal, •insurance, •software, •vendors, •platforms, to form and run a law-abiding business, to earn a mediocre income, that I’ve created from 0 to 1, entirely by myself, bootstrapped out of my own savings, which has provided hundreds of jobs and livelihoods to employees and contractors that have touched our circle…. when all along I could’ve simply •created a shell corporation •with misspelled signage, •locked doors, •blacked out windows, •took in millions in fraudulent revenue, •payable 100% to me, never having to work an honest day, never improving the community around me, never benefiting others all in exchange for my vote. Sham. And shame. Everyone should be outraged because there’s 100% chance this is happening in your state too and everyone playing by the rules is getting rag dolled by a system that lies, cheats, steals from the builders and providers to *give* to those that can leverage that payoff into a vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_58ccde2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The fraud of your taxpayer money is happening nationwide and is liberally applied to attract illegal...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d36ac803</link>
      <description>The fraud of your taxpayer money is happening nationwide and is liberally applied to attract illegal (and some legal) immigrants who will reliably vote Democrat. The more you look, the more you find. And you don’t need to be a world-class detective to figure it out. This is brazen, daylight robbery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d36ac803</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. T...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c32bdaec</link>
      <description>Even requiring a tiny amount of work for fraudulent payments would have a massive positive effect. That’s how insanely awful the level of fraud actually is!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c32bdaec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
