<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-16 03:54 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:54:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NED is and has been #1 coordinator of Internet censorship since 2017, responsible for building the c...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/eeb33424</link>
      <description>NED is and has been #1 coordinator of Internet censorship since 2017, responsible for building the censorship state in Brazil, shaping the EU Digital Censorship Act, building the disinformation studies beat in journalism &amp; academia, + much more. It was set up first for the CIA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_eeb33424</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yale University has finally achieved the academic version of Nirvana, a state of perfect peace and e...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9b70ded8</link>
      <description>Yale University has finally achieved the academic version of Nirvana, a state of perfect peace and enlightenment. A recent study found that the faculty had finally purged every Republican donor from its faculty ranks.jonathanturley.org/2026/01/1…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9b70ded8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: But them both!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fda80937</link>
      <description>But them both!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fda80937</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Singularity Part VIII: Kilowatts in Space Humanity needs power to survive and grow, and we will ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/139dbacd</link>
      <description>The Singularity Part VIII: Kilowatts in Space Humanity needs power to survive and grow, and we will turn to the same source that all terrestrial life has relied upon: the Sun. Our star produces 3.828 × 10^{26} watts of power. This is enough to power all of humanity’s current needs for approximately 617,000 years. The Sun represents 99.86% of the mass of the solar system and virtually all of its energy potential. Seriously considering any other source is absurd. With cheap lift capacity rockets provided by@SpaceXStarship and virtually free raw materials from@Grok-controlled and@Tesla_Optimus-operated asteroid mines and space factories, humanity will finally be able to utilize a fraction of the Sun’s power. This harnessing of solar abundance will fuel the computational explosion driving the Singularity, powering AI minds and human expansion across the stars—unlocking potentials we can scarcely imagine today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_139dbacd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: American mother says her daughter is 1 of only 4 children in her entire math class that speaks Engli...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1a2f1273</link>
      <description>American mother says her daughter is 1 of only 4 children in her entire math class that speaks English “She doesn't get to learn math because there's 20 plus other kids who don't know English and the teacher has to accommodate them” “Why am I paying property taxes? Why am I paying income tax? Why am I paying taxes for anything for my children to have a the right to a free and public education? — This this is what they get. You don't get to learn math because you know English, so you just don't get to learn math.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1a2f1273</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: German courts just decided the Iraqi migrant who pushed 16-year-old Liana to her death in ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1dc21671</link>
      <description>BREAKING: German courts just decided the Iraqi migrant who pushed 16-year-old Liana to her death in front of a train in Freidland will serve no prison time after he was determined to be suffering from “ill mental health”. Instead, he will spend time at a psychiatric facility at taxpayers' expense, and will not be deported. "Due to a diagnosis of schizophrenia, the accused was deemed not criminally responsible at the time of the offense," prosecutors stated. (Source@RMXnews)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1dc21671</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ilhan Omar calls for dismantling the Minneapolis Police Department. All while anti-ICE rioters ransa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/261fe0ae</link>
      <description>Ilhan Omar calls for dismantling the Minneapolis Police Department. All while anti-ICE rioters ransack federal vehicles and steal weapons. Democrats are the pro-criminal party. President Trump, invoke the Insurrection Act!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_261fe0ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "California’s wealth tax is only on billionaires!" That’s how the income tax started too. Only for t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e116661b</link>
      <description>"California’s wealth tax is only on billionaires!" That’s how the income tax started too. Only for the ~1%… until it wasn’t. When you allow the government to introduce new taxes, they never shrink, only expand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e116661b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 2008. Obama slams the Bush Administration for not doing enough to combat the problem of illegal immi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bf80c4de</link>
      <description>2008. Obama slams the Bush Administration for not doing enough to combat the problem of illegal immigration. 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bf80c4de</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is real-time</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ff35298a</link>
      <description>Grok is real-time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ff35298a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: How can@Yalestudents learn about the world if they are taught by faculty from only one side of the a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cdb21f45</link>
      <description>How can@Yalestudents learn about the world if they are taught by faculty from only one side of the aisle?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cdb21f45</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tragic. But it’s not too late for@paramountplusto save the franchise. Step 1: Reconcile with@William...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7dc3e230</link>
      <description>Tragic. But it’s not too late for@paramountplusto save the franchise. Step 1: Reconcile with@WilliamShatnerand give him total creative control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7dc3e230</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: TryGrokipedia.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6d17aa3b</link>
      <description>TryGrokipedia.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6d17aa3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: If ICE backs down now, they’ll be teaching these criminals that their illegal tactics work. Send mor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dd68aa72</link>
      <description>If ICE backs down now, they’ll be teaching these criminals that their illegal tactics work. Send more agents. Send the national guard. Arrest them all on federal charges so local juries can’t let them off. Enough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dd68aa72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thank you, Scott Adams. You lost your son to a fentanyl and made it one of your missions to stamp it...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3cba8c80</link>
      <description>Thank you, Scott Adams. You lost your son to a fentanyl and made it one of your missions to stamp it out. You did it, Scott, you did it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3cba8c80</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Immortality can be yours!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3af9bd70</link>
      <description>Immortality can be yours!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3af9bd70</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Feeling Optimustic about the future!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/627d016d</link>
      <description>Feeling Optimustic about the future!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_627d016d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
