<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-29 14:34 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:34:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Tesla Model S and Model X are amazing vehicles. Get them while still available!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/52620f1e</link>
      <description>The Tesla Model S and Model X are amazing vehicles. Get them while still available!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_52620f1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Technology progress is a jagged exponential</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3dc9c53b</link>
      <description>Technology progress is a jagged exponential</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3dc9c53b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Between Catwoman and Jessica Rabbit, Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/16a53988</link>
      <description>Between Catwoman and Jessica Rabbit, Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_16a53988</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We are beings of light! Let your light shine, be happy in your life! Grok Imagine</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/11e1bf88</link>
      <description>We are beings of light! Let your light shine, be happy in your life! Grok Imagine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_11e1bf88</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is wild. They literally had an EXCEL/SPSS column that was just "minority - but NOT Asian."</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e0a077c1</link>
      <description>This is wild. They literally had an EXCEL/SPSS column that was just "minority - but NOT Asian."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e0a077c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Eric Adams in 2023: If we keep spending money on migrants like this it's gonna blow a $12 billion ho...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4ab1dac5</link>
      <description>Eric Adams in 2023: If we keep spending money on migrants like this it's gonna blow a $12 billion hole in the budget Mamdani in 2023: that's right wing propaganda Mayor Mamdani in 2026: Eric Adams without warning left us a $12 billion deficit</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4ab1dac5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: You can’t make it up. The FCC will vote on requiring that federal subsidies flow only to people that...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/464aa801</link>
      <description>You can’t make it up. The FCC will vote on requiring that federal subsidies flow only to people that are both living and lawful beneficiaries. Dems oppose.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_464aa801</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is incredible… Billionaire Chamath Palihapitiya, once a MEGA Donor to the Democrat Party, says ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7752a817</link>
      <description>This is incredible… Billionaire Chamath Palihapitiya, once a MEGA Donor to the Democrat Party, says he was totally brainwashed by the NYT, WSJ, CNN, CNBC, MSNBC, CBS etc… and he believed every lie about President Trump as soon as he came down the escalator “Over the course of 6 or 7 years, I realized that some of those fundamental things that I was told about him was totally false… and it started with the Charlottesville lie — then I started to go down that rabbit hole.” Cliprumble.com/v74ztte-billionai…Katie Miller Podcastxcancel.com/katiemillerpod/status/…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7752a817</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 15-year-old girl raped in a School bathroom by trans boy dressed in girls' clothes. The School cover...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32c8a389</link>
      <description>15-year-old girl raped in a School bathroom by trans boy dressed in girls' clothes. The School covers it up so it doesn't interfere with their pride agenda...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32c8a389</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk on the Tesla Cybercab Today “It does not have steering wheel or pedals. It either drives i...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/347d3112</link>
      <description>Elon Musk on the Tesla Cybercab Today “It does not have steering wheel or pedals. It either drives itself or it does not drive”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_347d3112</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine is so advanced you don’t even need to write a prompt Just upload an image - it analyzes...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/07c71cd5</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine is so advanced you don’t even need to write a prompt Just upload an image - it analyzes the visual, infers intent, completes the prompt, and generates the video, voice, and relevant narration automatically At most, you just type a simple prompt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_07c71cd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 Dude is spot on! FYI… “Fun little fact, Tim Walz can't stop ICE from enforcing immigration law in ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/82e706c3</link>
      <description>🚨 Dude is spot on! FYI… “Fun little fact, Tim Walz can't stop ICE from enforcing immigration law in Minnesota because the Obama administration sued the state of Arizona and the Supreme Court ruled that the Feds have ultimate authority over immigration enforcement. Karma, man.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_82e706c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thanks to the API provided by xAI you can generate videos from 1 to 15 seconds! Grok Imagine is so i...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6a0f0742</link>
      <description>Thanks to the API provided by xAI you can generate videos from 1 to 15 seconds! Grok Imagine is so impressive</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6a0f0742</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: While everyone was marveling at the fact that Tesla solved FSD, we missed the fact that they've seem...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/42fed9d2</link>
      <description>While everyone was marveling at the fact that Tesla solved FSD, we missed the fact that they've seemingly solved 4680 cells and dry electrode coating as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_42fed9d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Imagine is crushing it right now, hands down the best out there. With the new 10s generations as wel...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aaa8a1a0</link>
      <description>Imagine is crushing it right now, hands down the best out there. With the new 10s generations as well, it's especially amazing. I've been generating all images and videos in there now, no need to go anywhere else.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aaa8a1a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We are excited about partnering with@falon the new Grok Imagine API!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0d1e118f</link>
      <description>We are excited about partnering with@falon the new Grok Imagine API!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0d1e118f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The next cities for our Robotaxi service</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/32c4f70d</link>
      <description>The next cities for our Robotaxi service</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_32c4f70d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Congrats to the@Neuralinkteam for helping many people who have lost use of their body with our Telep...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0494bb18</link>
      <description>Congrats to the@Neuralinkteam for helping many people who have lost use of their body with our Telepathy implant that enables computer use simply by thinking! The next generation Neuralink cybernetic augment with 3X capability will be ready later this year. Pending regulatory approval, we are also ready to do our first Blindsight augment that will enable those who have even complete loss of vision to see in low resolution at first, leading to high resolution over time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0494bb18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
