<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-15 19:53 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:53:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Latency good enough to play FPS games on an airplane!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/603cb6f5</link>
      <description>Latency good enough to play FPS games on an airplane!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_603cb6f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s been 1,394 days since I asked Ketanji Brown Jackson a simple question: Can you define the word ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1cee2b0e</link>
      <description>It’s been 1,394 days since I asked Ketanji Brown Jackson a simple question: Can you define the word ‘woman’? Her answer was, “No, I can’t... I'm not a biologist.” Nearly four years later, she still can’t. This radical ideology isn’t just out of touch; it puts REAL women at risk every day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1cee2b0e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Dragon blazing across the sky 10 times faster than a supersonic bullet</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9e7512f4</link>
      <description>Dragon blazing across the sky 10 times faster than a supersonic bullet</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9e7512f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Video from my roof of@SpaceXDragon streaking across the sky over LA tonight. Inside this 10,000 degr...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5551543b</link>
      <description>Video from my roof of@SpaceXDragon streaking across the sky over LA tonight. Inside this 10,000 degree plasma cocoon traveling at 8 km/sec are four amazing humans. Welcome home@NASACrew-11! 🇺🇸</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5551543b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Only 34% of students in the Saint Paul School District are meeting grade-level reading standards. Ma...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c435781d</link>
      <description>Only 34% of students in the Saint Paul School District are meeting grade-level reading standards. Maybe they should focus on teaching kids to read instead of teaching them how to protest for leftist causes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c435781d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: @SpaceXCrew-11 coming in hot with a plasma wake. Viewed from Berkeley shores with SF in the backgrou...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/53fe4a0b</link>
      <description>@SpaceXCrew-11 coming in hot with a plasma wake. Viewed from Berkeley shores with SF in the background.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_53fe4a0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ok, I think I see a way to pay for all those GPUs 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/de85c364</link>
      <description>Ok, I think I see a way to pay for all those GPUs 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_de85c364</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Dragon and@NASA’s Crew-11 return to Earth, splashing down off the coast of California</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8bf0d4f1</link>
      <description>Dragon and@NASA’s Crew-11 return to Earth, splashing down off the coast of California</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8bf0d4f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NED is and has been #1 coordinator of Internet censorship since 2017, responsible for building the c...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/daec7a79</link>
      <description>NED is and has been #1 coordinator of Internet censorship since 2017, responsible for building the censorship state in Brazil, shaping the EU Digital Censorship Act, building the disinformation studies beat in journalism &amp; academia, + much more. It was set up first for the CIA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_daec7a79</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yale University has finally achieved the academic version of Nirvana, a state of perfect peace and e...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7e0ba812</link>
      <description>Yale University has finally achieved the academic version of Nirvana, a state of perfect peace and enlightenment. A recent study found that the faculty had finally purged every Republican donor from its faculty ranks.jonathanturley.org/2026/01/1…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7e0ba812</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: But them both!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b5f3daba</link>
      <description>But them both!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b5f3daba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Singularity Part VIII: Kilowatts in Space Humanity needs power to survive and grow, and we will ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f5cd7665</link>
      <description>The Singularity Part VIII: Kilowatts in Space Humanity needs power to survive and grow, and we will turn to the same source that all terrestrial life has relied upon: the Sun. Our star produces 3.828 × 10^{26} watts of power. This is enough to power all of humanity’s current needs for approximately 617,000 years. The Sun represents 99.86% of the mass of the solar system and virtually all of its energy potential. Seriously considering any other source is absurd. With cheap lift capacity rockets provided by@SpaceXStarship and virtually free raw materials from@Grok-controlled and@Tesla_Optimus-operated asteroid mines and space factories, humanity will finally be able to utilize a fraction of the Sun’s power. This harnessing of solar abundance will fuel the computational explosion driving the Singularity, powering AI minds and human expansion across the stars—unlocking potentials we can scarcely imagine today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f5cd7665</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: American mother says her daughter is 1 of only 4 children in her entire math class that speaks Engli...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3a32596d</link>
      <description>American mother says her daughter is 1 of only 4 children in her entire math class that speaks English “She doesn't get to learn math because there's 20 plus other kids who don't know English and the teacher has to accommodate them” “Why am I paying property taxes? Why am I paying income tax? Why am I paying taxes for anything for my children to have a the right to a free and public education? — This this is what they get. You don't get to learn math because you know English, so you just don't get to learn math.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3a32596d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: German courts just decided the Iraqi migrant who pushed 16-year-old Liana to her death in ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a2f59210</link>
      <description>BREAKING: German courts just decided the Iraqi migrant who pushed 16-year-old Liana to her death in front of a train in Freidland will serve no prison time after he was determined to be suffering from “ill mental health”. Instead, he will spend time at a psychiatric facility at taxpayers' expense, and will not be deported. "Due to a diagnosis of schizophrenia, the accused was deemed not criminally responsible at the time of the offense," prosecutors stated. (Source@RMXnews)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a2f59210</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ilhan Omar calls for dismantling the Minneapolis Police Department. All while anti-ICE rioters ransa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a63c2559</link>
      <description>Ilhan Omar calls for dismantling the Minneapolis Police Department. All while anti-ICE rioters ransack federal vehicles and steal weapons. Democrats are the pro-criminal party. President Trump, invoke the Insurrection Act!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a63c2559</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Feeling Optimustic about the future!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/627d016d</link>
      <description>Feeling Optimustic about the future!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_627d016d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
