<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-24 22:41 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:41:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tesla is putting a lot of training effort into protecting pets</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5d6c0e47</link>
      <description>Tesla is putting a lot of training effort into protecting pets</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5d6c0e47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Am changing the Tesla mission wording from: Sustainable Abundance To Amazing Abundance</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9193e0e3</link>
      <description>Am changing the Tesla mission wording from: Sustainable Abundance To Amazing Abundance</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9193e0e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The latter is more joyful</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a9ee5ac0</link>
      <description>The latter is more joyful</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a9ee5ac0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: But I was told population replacement was an extremely dangerous far-right conspiracy theory. Wake u...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/93af418f</link>
      <description>But I was told population replacement was an extremely dangerous far-right conspiracy theory. Wake up already, we are losing our only homelands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_93af418f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Humor makes life better</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/259c8db2</link>
      <description>Humor makes life better</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_259c8db2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It seems this post went over the heads of some of the socialists, so let me put it as simply as poss...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/57e9d178</link>
      <description>It seems this post went over the heads of some of the socialists, so let me put it as simply as possible: 1. If the US had not "given" (using Socialist jargon here) Musk $38b, they would have had to have "given" Boeing, Lockheed Martin and other "Aerospace" companies $78b (and they probably would not have been able to have got delivery the products &amp; services in time, or ever, anyway). 2. Elon Musk's companies deliver between $100b to $140b of taxes and added value to the US and it's citizens every year (more than the GDP of a small state), and these contributions are growing faster than the US economy every year. 3. To spell it out to the unbelievers, the US (and particularly Elon's 140,000 employees) is earning an enormous return from Elon Musk's wealth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_57e9d178</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A Tesla with no safety monitor in the car and me sitting in the passenger seat took me all around Au...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/34b2692b</link>
      <description>A Tesla with no safety monitor in the car and me sitting in the passenger seat took me all around Austin on Sunday with perfect driving</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_34b2692b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: New articles have been added to Grokipedia Grokipedia now has over 1,239,341 articles, with 61,500+ ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/812bd2e6</link>
      <description>New articles have been added to Grokipedia Grokipedia now has over 1,239,341 articles, with 61,500+ Grok-approved edits</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_812bd2e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Merry (Space)Xmas! 🎄🛰️❤️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/42e2bea7</link>
      <description>Merry (Space)Xmas! 🎄🛰️❤️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_42e2bea7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Arrakis is so beautiful when the sun is low. Rolling over the sands, you can see spice in the air</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9d86176f</link>
      <description>Arrakis is so beautiful when the sun is low. Rolling over the sands, you can see spice in the air</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9d86176f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: EU technocrats are more upset at being told they can’t censor Europeans than they were at the Batacl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/912afdc5</link>
      <description>EU technocrats are more upset at being told they can’t censor Europeans than they were at the Bataclan Massacre.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_912afdc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Still one of the most BAD ASS moments ever!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/45b41cfb</link>
      <description>Still one of the most BAD ASS moments ever!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_45b41cfb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Thanks to an assist from@grokBooster 19 now is appropriately decorated. Merry Christmas.@SpaceX@elon...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/954c2bae</link>
      <description>Thanks to an assist from@grokBooster 19 now is appropriately decorated. Merry Christmas.@SpaceX@elonmusk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_954c2bae</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink is a total gamechanger</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9a3f3595</link>
      <description>Starlink is a total gamechanger</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9a3f3595</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI will have more AI compute than everyone else combined in &lt;5 years</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fc3557e5</link>
      <description>xAI will have more AI compute than everyone else combined in &lt;5 years</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fc3557e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok usage is exploding month over month, with people using it more than ever DAUs reached 6.12M in ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2d9193c2</link>
      <description>Grok usage is exploding month over month, with people using it more than ever DAUs reached 6.12M in August 2025, then climbed to 10.17M over the last 28 days, a 66.2% increase This surge follows rapid rollouts of new features, stronger voice and vision capabilities, and growing daily use across the platforms</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2d9193c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is What Winning Looks Like From Space Satellite imagery just caught xAI doing something no pres...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/be87c0ca</link>
      <description>This is What Winning Looks Like From Space Satellite imagery just caught xAI doing something no press release ever could: painting MACROHARD across the roof of its Colossus 2 datacenter in Tennessee. A building-sized wink at Microsoft, visible from orbit, impossible to ignore. It reads like a joke, until you look at what’s underneath. ⚆ Colossus 2 isn’t a concept site or a slide in a deck. Power and cooling infrastructure are expanding in lockstep, with the campus pushing toward ~400 MW of active capacity in the near term. Gas turbines are arriving. Cooling towers are multiplying. The build is loud because the progress is real. ⚆ More importantly, this early ramp sits on a much larger foundation. xAI has secured a clear path towards large scale on-site generation, creating a credible trajectory toward more than 2 GW of IT capacity over time. This isn’t aspirational: it’s ordered hardware, permitted infrastructure, and steel on the ground. The subtext is clear: while others debate timelines, this campus is already running. The roof says MACROHARD. The infrastructure says we’re ahead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_be87c0ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: How to edit images on X with Grok</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/10ffd750</link>
      <description>How to edit images on X with Grok</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_10ffd750</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The goal of@SpaceXis expansion of consciousness to the stars so that we may understand what question...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d9f17670</link>
      <description>The goal of@SpaceXis expansion of consciousness to the stars so that we may understand what questions to ask about the answer that is the Universe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d9f17670</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
