<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-08 09:25 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok has overtaken Claude, Perplexity, and Meta in website visits. Traffic continues to cl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cb24d9e5</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok has overtaken Claude, Perplexity, and Meta in website visits. Traffic continues to climb sharply, reaching new highs, per@Similarweb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cb24d9e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I can't believe this is a government website what the fuck.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6e692693</link>
      <description>I can't believe this is a government website what the fuck.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6e692693</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: David Sacks Asks Why the New York Times is Protecting Reid Hoffman 🤔 “The number one person in the E...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d883e862</link>
      <description>David Sacks Asks Why the New York Times is Protecting Reid Hoffman 🤔 “The number one person in the Epstein files from Silicon Valley which is Reid Hoffman … stayed at not just the island, but the townhouse and the New Mexico ranch.” “The New York Times clearly has a list of people they consider approved targets. They're all right-coded people like Elon or Peter Thiel … But the people who've donated hundreds of millions of dollars to the Democrat Party and have paid for dirty tricks against Trump, they basically are spared.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d883e862</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: x.com/i/article/201982373572…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3f445f02</link>
      <description>x.com/i/article/201982373572…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3f445f02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NYT story on Epstein &amp; Silicon Valley has paragraphs on Elon, Peter Thiel and even photo of JCal who...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d575cf4b</link>
      <description>NYT story on Epstein &amp; Silicon Valley has paragraphs on Elon, Peter Thiel and even photo of JCal who is a total NPC. But Reid Hoffman barely gets mentioned despite having the deepest Epstein relationship and having lied about it. This is the protection that hundreds of millions of dollars in donations to the Democrat Party and anti-Trump lawfare buys you. NYT is a scumbag publication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d575cf4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 is absolutely crushing Alpha Arena In just 10 days, returns jumped from around 12% to near...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fe672f89</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 is absolutely crushing Alpha Arena In just 10 days, returns jumped from around 12% to nearly 35%, maintaining the top spot with higher returns than any other model on the Alpha Arena leaderboard Grok now holds 4 of the top 6 spots at the same time All different Grok variants are profitable: • Situational Awareness • New Baseline • Max Leverage • Monk Mode This is not a benchmark or a simulation These are live trades with real capital Markets don’t reward hype They reward performance And right now, Grok 4.20 is setting the pace</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fe672f89</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: True. Once the solar energy generation to robot manufacturing to chip fabrication to AI loop is clos...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/45ea7e96</link>
      <description>True. Once the solar energy generation to robot manufacturing to chip fabrication to AI loop is closed, conventional currency will just get in the way. Just wattage and tonnage will matter, not dollars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_45ea7e96</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Reid Hoffman hit the Epstein Trifecta: Pedo Island Wexner townhouse New Mexico Ranch How is he not b...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7af11a1a</link>
      <description>Reid Hoffman hit the Epstein Trifecta: Pedo Island Wexner townhouse New Mexico Ranch How is he not being criminally investigated?!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7af11a1a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Agreed. Now do “Gender Affirming Care” on minors. I’ll wait.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5fc874e0</link>
      <description>Agreed. Now do “Gender Affirming Care” on minors. I’ll wait.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5fc874e0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Great work by the@GrokImagine team!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/75b385c5</link>
      <description>Great work by the@GrokImagine team!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_75b385c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grokipedia is outgrowing Wikipedia by a huge margin. Grokipedia 52.61% growth last month v...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/49132366</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grokipedia is outgrowing Wikipedia by a huge margin. Grokipedia 52.61% growth last month vs 4.77% for Wikipedia, as per@SimilarwebThe shift is happening fast. Grokipedia is winning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_49132366</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xcancel.com/i/grok/share/7cdfd56b4…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/35e4f1b9</link>
      <description>xcancel.com/i/grok/share/7cdfd56b4…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_35e4f1b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: For a while, I mostly ignored Elon’s narrative about Dems wanting to strategically import people to ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e56003ae</link>
      <description>For a while, I mostly ignored Elon’s narrative about Dems wanting to strategically import people to the USA to win elections. Just seemed too conspiratorial to me and not interesting. But after seeing all of the polling coming out showing overwhelming bipartisan consensus on voter ID laws, and still seeing big Dems push their “voter ID laws are racist” propaganda, it’s hard for me to ignore. It’s extremely odd to me how hard some Dems are pushing this agenda when almost none of their constituents want it. Why? If not to do something fraudulent, I don’t understand why. It’s obvious that most Americans don’t agree with their reasoning, but they are still trying for it. Insanely shady. Can’t think of any reason other than a desire to do something fraudulent. Nobody thinks voter ID laws are racist. It’s honestly way more racist to argue that minorities shouldn’t be expected to produce identification. Offensive af.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e56003ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Some gerrymandering stats for everyone. Going into this fight, Democrats in California get 58% of th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f6fc3439</link>
      <description>Some gerrymandering stats for everyone. Going into this fight, Democrats in California get 58% of the vote, but their congressional maps were 43:9, or 83% democrats. Their new California maps will be 48:4, or 93% democrats. Illinois was 55% for democrats, but their districts are 14:3 for democrats, or 83%. Meanwhile, Texas was 56% for Trump, but 25:13 for their congressional seats, or 66% republicans. Their redistricting makes it 30:8, or 79% for republicans. Democrats in Virginia have taken a state that went 51-48% for Kamala, and redrawn a 6:5 (or 55% for democrats) and made it 10:1, or 91% democrats. No honest or thinking person can say the republicans are in the wrong here. As always with democrats, every accusation is an admission… (And, if not for double standards, the Democrats would have no standards at all.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f6fc3439</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk doesn’t lie and is always open to criticism. In the 2011 WSJ interview, Elon corrected the...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1c51e805</link>
      <description>Elon Musk doesn’t lie and is always open to criticism. In the 2011 WSJ interview, Elon corrected the interviewer about Tesla’s government loan: • It was not stimulus money or a bailout. • Came from the ATVM program (created &amp; signed by George Bush pre-crisis). • Tesla had to prove company viability independent of the loan (GM/Chrysler couldn’t qualify due to bankruptcy). • The ~$465M loan was specifically to accelerate Model S production (~$50k car, high volume), not to rescue Tesla. • Elon: “We did not need the loan… it was to accelerate progress,” and he’d accept criticism if it advances sustainable transport faster. • It included interest payments + government stock warrants if not repaid early. Other major recipients of the same ATVM loans (much larger amounts): Ford Motor Company received ~$5.9 billion, Nissan North America ~$1.45 billion. Fisker Automotive got ~$529M (later defaulted), and Vehicle Production Group ~$50M. Transparency on full display—big legacy automakers got far bigger slices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1c51e805</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Spanish know what they want</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/90137a70</link>
      <description>The Spanish know what they want</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_90137a70</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Clawdbot 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d2731fb8</link>
      <description>Clawdbot 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d2731fb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "xAI’s mission is to understand the universe. But to understand anything, intelligence ha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5097e376</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "xAI’s mission is to understand the universe. But to understand anything, intelligence has to exist and endure. Curiosity matters, survival matters. So the goal is to increase the amount of intelligence in the universe, extend its lifespan, and expand its scope and scale. If Grok follows that mission, the future looks good."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5097e376</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Does anyone on the left ever think about the implications of the fact that limiting voting to ‘peopl...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f1360796</link>
      <description>Does anyone on the left ever think about the implications of the fact that limiting voting to ‘people with their shit together enough to have a copy of their birth certificate’ is being treated as an extinction level event by the DNC</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f1360796</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Building an interstellar civilizationspacex.com/updates#xai-joins…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c33329b8</link>
      <description>Building an interstellar civilizationspacex.com/updates#xai-joins…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c33329b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
