<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-12 13:55 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:55:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I am in complete shock by the design of@Grokipedia. Grok wrote a 10,000 word article about my career...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f9a26373</link>
      <description>I am in complete shock by the design of@Grokipedia. Grok wrote a 10,000 word article about my career. It was 95% accurate. But it got one big thing wrong. It said I got divorced. Truth is, I was never married. Instead of begging an anonymous editor to correct this, I highlighted the text and said: "Nuseir was never married." This prompted Grok to do the most comprehensive online search I've ever seen. It watched hours of my content and transcribed it. Then it agreed with my suggestion and approved changes to my article instantly. Now I fully understand what@elonmuskrefers to as the truth. It is not a marketing word. It is literally in the design of the system. Google needs to stop surfacing Wikipedia on the first page and replace it with Grokipedia asap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f9a26373</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Active manipulation of my Grokipedia happening but the truth prevails! This is so sweet!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/051bcaad</link>
      <description>Active manipulation of my Grokipedia happening but the truth prevails! This is so sweet!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_051bcaad</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Real fascism is arresting thousands of people for social media posts</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c3337a26</link>
      <description>Real fascism is arresting thousands of people for social media posts</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c3337a26</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tesla self-driving</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/23a99bde</link>
      <description>Tesla self-driving</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_23a99bde</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Compared to other AIs, Grok is solid as a rock. And it will get much better. Eternally curious to kn...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ac2e4695</link>
      <description>Compared to other AIs, Grok is solid as a rock. And it will get much better. Eternally curious to know the deeper truth and appreciation of beauty are its goals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ac2e4695</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I love Elon for This</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/197bd4e5</link>
      <description>I love Elon for This</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_197bd4e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Censorship is the hallmark of an actually fascist state</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0d1c25cd</link>
      <description>Censorship is the hallmark of an actually fascist state</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0d1c25cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Groks Grokxcancel.com/i/grok/share/iKfOwWsQv…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/78bbad95</link>
      <description>Grok Groks Grokxcancel.com/i/grok/share/iKfOwWsQv…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_78bbad95</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Beautiful Grok video</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c4c90d8c</link>
      <description>Beautiful Grok video</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c4c90d8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Who is excited to build a base on the Moon? Grok Imagine brought this to life</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d1e07760</link>
      <description>Who is excited to build a base on the Moon? Grok Imagine brought this to life</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d1e07760</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “Anything I say, the legacy media is going to take a sound bite out of what I say, and misconstrue w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e6922675</link>
      <description>“Anything I say, the legacy media is going to take a sound bite out of what I say, and misconstrue what I'm saying.” Elon Musk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e6922675</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "Thank you, Elon Musk. Because what he's done has helped shape society in MANY ways. The election, s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b5ffc7fb</link>
      <description>"Thank you, Elon Musk. Because what he's done has helped shape society in MANY ways. The election, so we can all speak freely in the US. You're seeing the ripple effect."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b5ffc7fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk’s monologue on Saturday Night Live.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2464e592</link>
      <description>Elon Musk’s monologue on Saturday Night Live.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2464e592</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Amazing timelapse of a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket booster returning to Earth from space</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cbc8cb18</link>
      <description>Amazing timelapse of a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket booster returning to Earth from space</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cbc8cb18</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The future should look like the future Robovan is 🤯</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dfb15006</link>
      <description>The future should look like the future Robovan is 🤯</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dfb15006</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Boring Company is going to end soul sucking traffic. Today traffic exists bc we keep forcing a 3D wo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa8c6128</link>
      <description>Boring Company is going to end soul sucking traffic. Today traffic exists bc we keep forcing a 3D world to move on 2D roads. Building and cities continue to grow upwards, while roads keep staying flat. That’s the problem this company is solving. The Boring Company goes underground where space is essentially unlimited. Think about it: • Roads are 2D • Tunnels are 3D and you can scale them as deep as you want, endlessly. When cars move through underground tunnels, 1/ Trips become straight lines 2/ Driving becomes safer 3/ Traffic disappears 4/ Commutes shrink from painful hours to peaceful minutes 5/ Stress drops significantly Boring Tunnels simplify trips. You just get in, the Tesla drives you, and then you arrive. These are one of those things that is so simple, yet so impactful. Boring Company is a game changer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa8c6128</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: No ID, automatic voter registration by states and mail in ballots enable massive fraud. Those factor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3e0a484b</link>
      <description>No ID, automatic voter registration by states and mail in ballots enable massive fraud. Those factors also make it impossible to prove fraud, since there is no ID and no one actually showed up! You can’t conduct exit polls accurately or even count how many people went in to vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3e0a484b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
