<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-04 14:44 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:44:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I updated Grok to version 1.3.28 on iOS and it’s mind blowing 🤯 Update your Grok app.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/afb56d52</link>
      <description>I updated Grok to version 1.3.28 on iOS and it’s mind blowing 🤯 Update your Grok app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_afb56d52</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Searches for X has reached an all-time high according to Google Trends! People around the world are ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e85975c2</link>
      <description>Searches for X has reached an all-time high according to Google Trends! People around the world are following the news from X!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e85975c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Interesting</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/55b05898</link>
      <description>Interesting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_55b05898</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: We now have the confirmed and finalized homicide rate for El Salvador in 2025. 1.19. 38% and about 7...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/40bdf897</link>
      <description>We now have the confirmed and finalized homicide rate for El Salvador in 2025. 1.19. 38% and about 75% lower than the rates in Canada and the U.S., respectively, in 2024. This even beats some European countries, like France. This is staggering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_40bdf897</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Protesters who are paid should be required to disclose that they are being paid and by whom. Protest...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f6410fc9</link>
      <description>Protesters who are paid should be required to disclose that they are being paid and by whom. Protests are political speech/advertising. Why are they exempt from the same disclosures required for political advertising?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f6410fc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: That’s all the difference in the world</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bab801b3</link>
      <description>That’s all the difference in the world</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bab801b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: How to use@GrokImagine to create amazing images and videos</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/77e29e25</link>
      <description>How to use@GrokImagine to create amazing images and videos</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_77e29e25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 JUST IN: The Fake News is FURIOUS after videos spread of COUNTLESS major cities being flooded with...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ceafcbcc</link>
      <description>🚨 JUST IN: The Fake News is FURIOUS after videos spread of COUNTLESS major cities being flooded with real Venezuelans who love what Donald Trump just pulled off with Maduro The white Democrat who loves Maduro is clueless. FREEDOM IS RINGING! 🔥</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ceafcbcc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: “I couldn't think of anything more exciting, fun, and inspiring for the future than to ha...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0dad1e19</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: “I couldn't think of anything more exciting, fun, and inspiring for the future than to have a base on Mars" At The Mars Society, August 2012</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0dad1e19</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia now has over 2.3M articles New topics are being added every day, with transparent edits a...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cf1e5c84</link>
      <description>Grokipedia now has over 2.3M articles New topics are being added every day, with transparent edits and clear reasoning behind every change Anyone can contribute, and accuracy is checked in real time Open knowledge, built in public, and growing super fast</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cf1e5c84</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine 💫</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/24fc572e</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine 💫</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_24fc572e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Love worth celebrating ❤️</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c8ed10af</link>
      <description>Love worth celebrating ❤️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c8ed10af</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 BOOM! President Trump posts Scott Presler blowing the whistle on potential MAJOR VOTER FRAUD in Mi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c25ab08c</link>
      <description>🚨 BOOM! President Trump posts Scott Presler blowing the whistle on potential MAJOR VOTER FRAUD in Minnesota by letting ONE person "vouch" for EIGHT migrant voters who have not been verified "Did you know that in 2008, 500,000 voters, or nearly 19% of all voters in Minnesota, registered on election day?!" "And did you know that former Senator Al Franken was elected by 312 votes?" "What I am saying is that this vouching system, which clearly opens the door for potential fraud, could swing statewide elections!"@ScottPreslerThis law must be overturned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c25ab08c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Prompt Share: Highly detailed fantasy portrait of a beautiful ethereal woman with pale skin, bold re...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c8fdfe36</link>
      <description>Prompt Share: Highly detailed fantasy portrait of a beautiful ethereal woman with pale skin, bold red lips, intense gaze, long voluminous curly dark brown hair flowing wildly, wearing an elaborate ornate golden headdress crown with intricate filigree and spikes, dangling gold earrings, choker necklace, and a deep black off shoulder gown with lavish gold embroidery and baroque patterns, deep plunging neckline, surrounded by swirling dramatic smoke and clouds in muted beige and blue tones, intricate textures, baroque fantasy art style, dramatic lighting, masterpiece, ultra detailed, cinematic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c8fdfe36</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yes, at massive scale! It is the biggest vote-buying fraud scheme in the history of America.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aad3bf88</link>
      <description>Yes, at massive scale! It is the biggest vote-buying fraud scheme in the history of America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aad3bf88</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
