<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-22 20:48 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:48:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Robotaxi rides without any safety monitors are now publicly available in Austin. Starting with a few...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/918147a6</link>
      <description>Robotaxi rides without any safety monitors are now publicly available in Austin. Starting with a few unsupervised vehicles mixed in with the broader robotaxi fleet with safety monitors, and the ratio will increase over time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_918147a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Quality of life improvement</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f3df6011</link>
      <description>Quality of life improvement</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f3df6011</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "I'd like to understand the meaning of life. Is the standard model of physics correct reg...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a21f5677</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "I'd like to understand the meaning of life. Is the standard model of physics correct regarding the beginning of existence &amp; the end of the universe? What questions do we not know to ask that we should ask? AI will help us with these things."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a21f5677</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Teams encapsulated the@USSpaceForce’s GPS III-9 satellite into Falcon 9’s fairing ahead of arriving ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b0f0158</link>
      <description>Teams encapsulated the@USSpaceForce’s GPS III-9 satellite into Falcon 9’s fairing ahead of arriving at the hangar at pad 40 in Florida. Liftoff is targeted for 11:46 p.m. ET on Sunday, January 25 →spacex.com/launches/gpsiii9</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b0f0158</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Easily</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fa54f753</link>
      <description>Easily</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fa54f753</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Falcon 9 launches 25@Starlinksatellites from California</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5904f8ea</link>
      <description>Falcon 9 launches 25@Starlinksatellites from California</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5904f8ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon's closing in Davos: “I would encourage everyone to be optimistic and excited about the future, ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ff144d8b</link>
      <description>Elon's closing in Davos: “I would encourage everyone to be optimistic and excited about the future, and generally for quality of life, it’s better to er on the side of being an optimist and being wrong, than a pessimist and right”xcancel.com/i/status/2014371322365…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ff144d8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 1995: Elon Musk is replacing a broken side window himself with parts from a junkyard because he coul...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/58e9c93d</link>
      <description>1995: Elon Musk is replacing a broken side window himself with parts from a junkyard because he couldn’t afford repairs. 2026: A Tesla Robotaxi driving fully autonomously on busy roads in Austin with no safety monitor in the car.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_58e9c93d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly. Thank you for speaking up.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/66c4d299</link>
      <description>Exactly. Thank you for speaking up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_66c4d299</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: IS GERMANY’S FREE SPEECH DOOMED? Not at all! One of the most internationally covered free speech tri...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c0af7144</link>
      <description>IS GERMANY’S FREE SPEECH DOOMED? Not at all! One of the most internationally covered free speech trials in Germany just resulted in VICTORY: David Bendels (@Deu_Kurier), after having been sentenced to 7 months on probation for a MEME, is FREE. It seems, U.S. attention on the case intimidated the authorities…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c0af7144</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Tesla is now offering FSD (Supervised) V14 ride alongs in Spain and Finland. Spain sign up:tes...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a6bfb982</link>
      <description>NEWS: Tesla is now offering FSD (Supervised) V14 ride alongs in Spain and Finland. Spain sign up:tesla.com/events/fsd-supervi…Finland sign up:tesla.com/events/fsd-supervi…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a6bfb982</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "I've been asked a few times like, do I want to die on Mars? And I'm like, Yes, but just ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/85eac0bf</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "I've been asked a few times like, do I want to die on Mars? And I'm like, Yes, but just not on impact." 🤣</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_85eac0bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A driverless Tesla Robotaxi. No one in the car. No safety driver. Fully autonomous. This is actually...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a3fd2024</link>
      <description>A driverless Tesla Robotaxi. No one in the car. No safety driver. Fully autonomous. This is actually happening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a3fd2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Protect the light of consciousness</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dbb57370</link>
      <description>Protect the light of consciousness</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dbb57370</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: VP JD Vance in Minneapolis: “We're not trying to send a political message. We're trying to enforce t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/03d23715</link>
      <description>VP JD Vance in Minneapolis: “We're not trying to send a political message. We're trying to enforce the law.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_03d23715</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: "In the future, the robots will make so many robots, that they will actually saturate all...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5b193867</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: "In the future, the robots will make so many robots, that they will actually saturate all human needs, meaning you won't be able to even think of something to ask the robot for at a certain point, like there will be such an abundance of goods and services. There'll be more robots than people. I think everyone on earth is going to have one humanoid robot because you would want a robot to watch over your kids, take care of your pet, take care of elderly parents. I'm very optimistic about the future. I think we're headed for a future of amazing abundance, which is very cool. Definitely we are in the most interesting time in history."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5b193867</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Use video mode (turn on camera) and Grok voice will explain everything you’re looking at</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1c459c06</link>
      <description>Use video mode (turn on camera) and Grok voice will explain everything you’re looking at</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1c459c06</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
