<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-11 09:44 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:44:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Terrible</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b06266a</link>
      <description>Terrible</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b06266a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A message for@elonmuskon behalf of the people of Iran</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7e6e53bb</link>
      <description>A message for@elonmuskon behalf of the people of Iran</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7e6e53bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Spoke to a NASA staffer yesterday and asked how she feels: - Isaacman is working around the clock - ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a533ec53</link>
      <description>Spoke to a NASA staffer yesterday and asked how she feels: - Isaacman is working around the clock - She’s been formally asked, for the first time in seven years, “how is bureaucracy holding you back, and how can I help?” - She’s never been more excited to work at NASA</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a533ec53</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is what a mind virus looks like in America👇🏽 Obama deployed ICE and deported over 5 million ill...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3198071b</link>
      <description>This is what a mind virus looks like in America👇🏽 Obama deployed ICE and deported over 5 million illegals during his presidency: Not a single protest, not a single word from the media. Not a single activist. Not a single ICE agent harassed or killed. Not a single judge prohibited the deportations in the court. FYI, Clinton deported over 12 million. Obama facilitated the bombing of Libya, FOR 7 MONTHS, with no congressional permission: Not a single word from the media. Not a single word from the activists. Not a single protest held. Not a word from politicians. Trump deploys ICE to deport people in our country illegally: weekly protest, judges inhibiting courts, media demonizing ICE and the president, activists leading the harassment of agents and officers, ICE agents threatened, ambushed and killed. Trump goes into Venezuela in under 3 hours and extracts a monstrous dictator, who had a bounty on his head even under Biden and brings him back to the states to face trial: Media demonizes the president, mass protests, Trump is a dictator, vigils… The mind virus in America, folks. I could go all day with more examples. All day. All day long. Pray for those who are afflicted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3198071b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Huge improvements have been made to Grok Imagine It keeps getting better</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/839b1a74</link>
      <description>Huge improvements have been made to Grok Imagine It keeps getting better</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_839b1a74</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Half a million known fraudulent voters?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/62888038</link>
      <description>Half a million known fraudulent voters?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_62888038</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Correct</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0d87cf36</link>
      <description>Correct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0d87cf36</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Minnesota was 98% White in 1973. As Time magazine noted, little corruption in politics, low crime, h...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3a72282f</link>
      <description>Minnesota was 98% White in 1973. As Time magazine noted, little corruption in politics, low crime, high civic pride. What happened to the state was done deliberately and with malicious intent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3a72282f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Unfortunately, this is where America is headed</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4fe32e5e</link>
      <description>Unfortunately, this is where America is headed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4fe32e5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I will not rest until Ilhan Omar is expelled from THE COUNTRY. We are fed up with this madness.JohnS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/92ba0c2e</link>
      <description>I will not rest until Ilhan Omar is expelled from THE COUNTRY. We are fed up with this madness.JohnStrand.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_92ba0c2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Did you remember to upgrade your@grokApp today?</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7df8460d</link>
      <description>Did you remember to upgrade your@grokApp today?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7df8460d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Iranians are using the X Platform to get their freedom..so the U.K., Canada and Australia plan to ba...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2ea68e71</link>
      <description>Iranians are using the X Platform to get their freedom..so the U.K., Canada and Australia plan to ban it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2ea68e71</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Real charmer …</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a2686f57</link>
      <description>Real charmer …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a2686f57</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
