<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-09 17:48 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: &gt;tap &gt;tap again &gt;tap tap tap tap &gt;this should be Sidney Sweeney@LoopitAi</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/431b5af5</link>
      <description>&gt;tap &gt;tap again &gt;tap tap tap tap &gt;this should be Sidney Sweeney@LoopitAi</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_431b5af5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Watching Elon Musk on Charlie Rose in 2009 is surreal. Back then: • Tesla delivering ~1,000 Roadster...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bcb09d2b</link>
      <description>Watching Elon Musk on Charlie Rose in 2009 is surreal. Back then: • Tesla delivering ~1,000 Roadsters/year • Model S just unveiled, promised for 2011 at ~$50k • SpaceX had reached orbit once, Falcon 9 about to fly, hoping to end US reliance on Russian rockets post-2010 • Splitting time evenly between Tesla &amp; SpaceX As of February 2026: • Tesla: Pioneering groundbreaking tech like scaled dry-electrode 4680 batteries (major breakthrough cutting costs/energy/use, boosting scalability &amp; energy density), advanced AI for Full Self-Driving (FSD nearing unsupervised autonomy), Cybercab/Robotaxi rollout accelerating, Optimus humanoid robots heading toward mass production &amp; even Mars missions • SpaceX: 165 orbital launches in 2025 (world record!), ~15 so far in 2026; Crew Dragon standard (no Russian dependency); Starlink &gt;9M subscribers (expected to double again) • Hot update: Focus on “self-growing city” on Moon (&lt;10 years); Mars delayed a bit; IPO rumors at ~$1.5T valuation? Same visionary drive from 2009. Execution: now planetary + AI/robotics scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bcb09d2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: India's ‌Gujarat state has signed ‌a letter of intent with Starlink to provide ‌high-speed, sa...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c77724e</link>
      <description>NEWS: India's ‌Gujarat state has signed ‌a letter of intent with Starlink to provide ‌high-speed, satellite-based internet connectivity across remote and ⁠underserved regions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c77724e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Civilization on the Moon!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d13cec9c</link>
      <description>Civilization on the Moon!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d13cec9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEW: Democrat Sen. John Fetterman calls for Voter ID, pummeling his own party.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fe53f960</link>
      <description>NEW: Democrat Sen. John Fetterman calls for Voter ID, pummeling his own party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fe53f960</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Happy to share that the Government of Gujarat has exchanged a Letter of Intent with@Starlink, a subs...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f077dfb4</link>
      <description>Happy to share that the Government of Gujarat has exchanged a Letter of Intent with@Starlink, a subsidiary of@SpaceX, to strengthen digital connectivity across the state. This LoI will enable high-speed satellite-based internet connectivity in remote, border, tribal and underserved areas with limited telecom infrastructure, accelerating Gujarat’s Digital Connectivity Mission and strategic digital initiatives. Inspired by the visionary leadership of Hon'ble Prime Minister Shri@narendramodiJi and his#DigitalIndiamission, this collaboration will support e-governance and Common Service Centres, schools, primary health centres, tele-medicine services, disaster management systems, ports, wildlife sanctuaries and key government institutions. The initiative will ensure reliable digital service delivery in aspirational and tribal districts, strengthen education and healthcare outreach, enhance disaster preparedness and security systems, and improve access to government services for citizens. In view of the need for seamless and easy connectivity across the state, a Joint Working Group comprising representatives of the Government of Gujarat and Starlink will be constituted to ensure the effective implementation of this LoI - contributing to the vision of#ViksitBharat2047.@elonmusk@LaurenDreyer@prabhakarpj</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f077dfb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk has figured out the Soros racket. It doesn’t involve Soros spending his own money. It invo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d806f9d0</link>
      <description>Elon Musk has figured out the Soros racket. It doesn’t involve Soros spending his own money. It involves Soros making a seed investment so he can get his hands on your money. He then makes you pay, through the government, to fund your own destruction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d806f9d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Other than the Founding Fathers, no one has done more for free speech rights, and the first amendmen...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6aeec9ae</link>
      <description>Other than the Founding Fathers, no one has done more for free speech rights, and the first amendment then ⁦@elonmusk⁩</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6aeec9ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: “The purpose of not voter ID is obviously to conduct fraud in elections.”</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7584846d</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: “The purpose of not voter ID is obviously to conduct fraud in elections.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7584846d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Indeed, it is the bare minimum for any PM. Starmer needs to step up or step out.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/db32e70e</link>
      <description>Indeed, it is the bare minimum for any PM. Starmer needs to step up or step out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_db32e70e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk: The purpose of no voter ID is obviously to conduct fraud in elections “The same people th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/05ea5792</link>
      <description>Elon Musk: The purpose of no voter ID is obviously to conduct fraud in elections “The same people that demanded vaccine IDs, if you want to travel or do anything, are the same ones who say no voter ID is required. Obviously hypocritical. It's so that fraud cannot be proven. So it enables large-scale fraud and no way to prove it, because how would you prove it? It's literally impossible. No ID. You're not even allowed to show your ID. It's insane. The purpose of no voter ID is obviously to conduct fraud in elections. They come up with some nice-sounding thing. Their common rebuttal is like, it's racist to require ID, which is insane. I think it's actually racist and patronizing to say that people can't figure out how to get an ID. You need an ID for everything. Like, the list of the things you need an ID for is basically everything, except voting.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_05ea5792</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Bannon is evil</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8729f847</link>
      <description>Bannon is evil</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8729f847</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok has surpassed 2 billion website visits. The growth continues as Grok recorded a fourt...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/72d2a801</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok has surpassed 2 billion website visits. The growth continues as Grok recorded a fourth straight month of traffic growth, as per@Similarweb</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_72d2a801</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Given how close Steve Bannon and Epstein were up to Epstein's arrest, Bannon was likely involved in ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a685f450</link>
      <description>Given how close Steve Bannon and Epstein were up to Epstein's arrest, Bannon was likely involved in nearly every illegal activity that Epstein engaged in. At the very least, he had detailed knowledge of numerous crimes and never reported them. It's time to investigate Bannon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a685f450</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Use 𝕏 Chat!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/48172c65</link>
      <description>Use 𝕏 Chat!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_48172c65</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In the next few months, we will be doing rigorous security tests of 𝕏 Chat and will open source all ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a943560d</link>
      <description>In the next few months, we will be doing rigorous security tests of 𝕏 Chat and will open source all the code</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a943560d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The fact that Steve Bannon was a Trump-hating degenerate and an ally who was trying to clear the “go...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4b66ae4c</link>
      <description>The fact that Steve Bannon was a Trump-hating degenerate and an ally who was trying to clear the “good name” of Jeffrey Epstein through the production of a documentary is only the tip of filth-encrusted iceberg. He is a fraudster of the highest order, from the start ‘til now, and has been involved in numerous scams with convicted Chinese fraudster Miles Guo who pretended to be a billionaire while simultaneously fleecing his own followers for over a billion dollars through a web of investment scams as he masqueraded as an anti-CCP crusader. It’s all money that went to fund his extravagant lifestyle… and Bannon’s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4b66ae4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Starlink Super Bowl ad! Affordable Internet anywhere.Starlink.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f35fd529</link>
      <description>Starlink Super Bowl ad! Affordable Internet anywhere.Starlink.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f35fd529</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
