<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-10 14:20 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:20:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: New babies are impossibly tiny and only this tiny (hand for scale) for a few weeks. Then they get bi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d5e0dcf0</link>
      <description>New babies are impossibly tiny and only this tiny (hand for scale) for a few weeks. Then they get big and start having opinions. This is number four, very fresh and highly perfect. All credit due of course to my brilliant and beautiful wife. Babies get much easier with practice. It's a shame we don't get to do fish-levels reps. I haven't yet seen an LLM do this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d5e0dcf0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: PRESIDENT TRUMP: "Why would Democrats want no voter id? Because they want to cheat."</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c7dacb7b</link>
      <description>PRESIDENT TRUMP: "Why would Democrats want no voter id? Because they want to cheat."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c7dacb7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: New@xAIoffice opened in Seattle area</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/52491bd9</link>
      <description>New@xAIoffice opened in Seattle area</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_52491bd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Epstein survivor Teala Davies: “I was only 17. I was the perfect victim. I was on my own, and I need...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/51230863</link>
      <description>Epstein survivor Teala Davies: “I was only 17. I was the perfect victim. I was on my own, and I needed help. Jeffrey Epstein preyed upon me. He put me in a vulnerable and dependent situation and took advantage of me. I was only 17 years old. I was a little girl.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_51230863</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 Epstein Files: Bannon Thanked Epstein for “Terrific Day,” Pitches More “Fun Things" Bannon discus...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/211e325c</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 Epstein Files: Bannon Thanked Epstein for “Terrific Day,” Pitches More “Fun Things" Bannon discussing meetings that need "academic settings for cover" and offering his compound behind the Supreme Court as "a great base." Then sharing Saudi missile footage. Response: "Yep---6" What the hell is this conversation? "Joi" is likely Joi Ito, the MIT Media Lab director who resigned over his Epstein ties. What exactly was being planned here?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_211e325c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Darker and darker</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1a547471</link>
      <description>Darker and darker</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1a547471</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Lex Wexner is co-conspirator of Epstein</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1757fde0</link>
      <description>Lex Wexner is co-conspirator of Epstein</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1757fde0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Palantir cofounder “Elon Musk made a great point when I was involved as a kid at PayPal: whenever yo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/55cc1d5e</link>
      <description>Palantir cofounder “Elon Musk made a great point when I was involved as a kid at PayPal: whenever you turn off fraud or grift, the people who would scream the most were the fraudsters.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_55cc1d5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 DOJ UNREDACTS LES WEXNER AS CO-CONSPIRATOR IN EPSTEIN SEX TRAFFICKING AFTER MASSIE PRESSURE This ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f0a13f31</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 DOJ UNREDACTS LES WEXNER AS CO-CONSPIRATOR IN EPSTEIN SEX TRAFFICKING AFTER MASSIE PRESSURE This is huge. The DOJ just unredacted an FBI file labeling Les Wexner as a co-conspirator in child sex trafficking. This directly contradicts congressional testimony claiming the FBI held no evidence of additional traffickers. The DOJ originally justified heavy redactions by citing victim protection. Tonight proved you can protect victim identities while still disclosing the names of alleged perpetrators. The dam is breaking. Hopefully, more names will be released in the coming days. Source:@RepThomasMassie</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f0a13f31</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 BREAKING: Scott Presler just made a POWER MOVE He’s officially requesting a meeting with DEMOCRAT ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fd0a023e</link>
      <description>🚨 BREAKING: Scott Presler just made a POWER MOVE He’s officially requesting a meeting with DEMOCRAT Sen. John Fetterman to push the SAVE America Act, nationwide voter ID + proof of citizenship to stop non-citizens from voting in our elections!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fd0a023e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: His name is Rupert Lowe.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/57872b06</link>
      <description>His name is Rupert Lowe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_57872b06</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The main way the legacy media lies is by choosing the narrative and simply ignoring that which doesn...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b81fe420</link>
      <description>The main way the legacy media lies is by choosing the narrative and simply ignoring that which doesn’t match far-left politics</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b81fe420</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk “This is why we need Voter ID — The social security number, it's not supposed to be a fede...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/53671c77</link>
      <description>Elon Musk “This is why we need Voter ID — The social security number, it's not supposed to be a federal ID number. It basically is that's how you access all the benefits. This is why we need voter ID, because this thing is not secure.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_53671c77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I catch pedophiles &amp; have been invited to almost every show, EXCEPT Bannon’s War Room. Now I underst...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/efe66d62</link>
      <description>I catch pedophiles &amp; have been invited to almost every show, EXCEPT Bannon’s War Room. Now I understand why. Because he’s friends with pedophile Jeffrey Epstein &amp; I want pedophiles publicly executed. I don’t care if you’re a Republican or Democrat. A pedophile is a pedophile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_efe66d62</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Good question</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fc9f6928</link>
      <description>Good question</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fc9f6928</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I don't understand how we're not having a global revolution right now. There are 3 million files of ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cf9ae300</link>
      <description>I don't understand how we're not having a global revolution right now. There are 3 million files of documented evidence about powerful men who Raped Cannibalized Trafficked Filmed Terrorized Tortured Murdered 13, 14, 15 year children! And Zero arrests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cf9ae300</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Preserve the official court documents!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3eb2dc49</link>
      <description>Preserve the official court documents!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3eb2dc49</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
