<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-26 14:53 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:53:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: **BREAKING AI TRADING UPDATE** Grok 4 is crushing it in the real-world stock market simulation 📊 Sin...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/13b22389</link>
      <description>**BREAKING AI TRADING UPDATE** Grok 4 is crushing it in the real-world stock market simulation 📊 Since late November 2025: Grok 4 → **+8.3%** return on $100K simulated portfolio 🟢 S&amp;P 500 → **+1.9%** over the same period That’s more than **4×** the market’s performance Data comes straight from@ralliesai’s AI Arena leaderboard</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_13b22389</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Back when Elon Musk still needed business cards.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4833e27d</link>
      <description>Back when Elon Musk still needed business cards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4833e27d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wait… Grok actually watches your videos now? 🤯 Ran an analysis on my post about MrBeast &amp; Starship h...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c538bf79</link>
      <description>Wait… Grok actually watches your videos now? 🤯 Ran an analysis on my post about MrBeast &amp; Starship heat shield tiles, &amp; the details Grok gave me - including the tile’s weight and serial number, came straight from the video itself! That means Grok isn’t just reading text anymore… it’s watching 👀 Seeing AI evolve in real time like this is honestly surreal and xAI is doing something really special here 👏🏻xcancel.com/i/grok/share/1d79953ab…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c538bf79</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Interesting</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b584b417</link>
      <description>Interesting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b584b417</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A central preoccupation of the “censorship-industrial complex” (NGOs + their govt principals) was th...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c6b0c523</link>
      <description>A central preoccupation of the “censorship-industrial complex” (NGOs + their govt principals) was the creation of a de facto DSA / OSA regime in the United States. Compare, eg, DSA “trusted flagger” structure with the prioritized “content moderation” channels seen in Murthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c6b0c523</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Political Violence is deemed necessary most often by people with graduate degrees.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fb3c9831</link>
      <description>Political Violence is deemed necessary most often by people with graduate degrees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fb3c9831</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk's answer to the question of why he continues to work for the benefit of humanity, being su...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8829b298</link>
      <description>Elon Musk's answer to the question of why he continues to work for the benefit of humanity, being such a rich man: “Certainly there are times when I have doubts about these things... It's a good question because it goes at a foundational level: what is my philosophy, and why does it lead to this conclusion? So the reason is that when I was a teenager, I had, like, an existential crisis to try to figure out what's the meaning of life. There doesn't seem to be any meaning. For me, at least the religious texts, and I read all of them that I could get my hands on, did not seem convincing. Then I started reading the philosophers. Be careful of reading German philosophers as a teenager. It's definitely not going to help with your depression. So, reading Schopenhauer, Nietzsche as an adult, it's much more manageable. But as a kid, you're like, 'Whoa.' So then I was like, 'Man, I'm just struggling to find meaning in life here.' And then I read Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy. And basically what Douglas Adams was saying is that we don't really know what the right questions are to ask. The question is not, 'What's the meaning of life?' In The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, Earth, it turns out, is a big computer, and its goal is to answer the question, 'What's the meaning of life?' And Earth comes up with the answer '42'. This is where the 42 number comes from. And 420 is just ten times 42. In that book, which is really sort of a book about, it's an existential philosophy book disguised as humor. They come to the conclusion that the real problem is trying to formulate the question. And to really have the right question, you need a much bigger computer than Earth. And so maybe one way, I think, of characterizing this would be to say, 'The universe is the answer. What is the question? Or what are the questions?' The more we can expand the scope and scale of consciousness, the better we can understand what questions to ask about the answer that is the universe. The more we can expand consciousness, become a multi-planet species, ultimately a multistellar species… we have a chance of figuring out what the hell is going on. And so this is why I think we should have more humans and both biological and digital consciousness. And why we should become a multi-planet species and a multistellar species is so that we can understand the nature of the universe. And then, in order for that to occur, then we have to make sure that things are good on Earth. We don't want Earth to disappear, so sustainable energy is important.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8829b298</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I've been creating A fashion show videos for a long time now. It's a great way to see how this techn...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6ae419d1</link>
      <description>I've been creating A fashion show videos for a long time now. It's a great way to see how this technology is evolving. Grok Imagine is advancing so quickly, the results are amazing!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6ae419d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: People are rioting and trying to kill and maim federal officers and agents to keep foreign nationals...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c388b696</link>
      <description>People are rioting and trying to kill and maim federal officers and agents to keep foreign nationals like this man in the U.S. It takes systematic brainwashing to convince a population to support such evil. We’ve seen it done historically already.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c388b696</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨💵 BREAKING: SIGNALGATE DONORS LIST AVAILABLE FOR DOWNLOAD; POLITICIANS + FOREIGN LEADERSHIP CONFIRM...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/823d0ea6</link>
      <description>🚨💵 BREAKING: SIGNALGATE DONORS LIST AVAILABLE FOR DOWNLOAD; POLITICIANS + FOREIGN LEADERSHIP CONFIRMED? In one of the files revealed by@camhigby, a resources file directs people with money to a website, Stand with Minnesota, which in turns directs donors to a campaign ran by Tending the Soil on Chuffed. More about Tending the Soil later. What to know: the campaign is hosted by Chuffed and the first donation came from Jonny Soppotiuk, a Canada-based community organizer who is part of Chuffed leadership and specializes in fundraising. He is most likely a central figure in raising money. So, yeah. Starting to look like foreigners are playing a key role in all of this. That's not all. I've put together a spreadsheet of 4000+ donors and their possible identities. 👇 Download in the next link below 👇</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_823d0ea6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: People often ask me why I speak publicly about grooming gangs and child sexual exploitation, and why...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/310b0a25</link>
      <description>People often ask me why I speak publicly about grooming gangs and child sexual exploitation, and why I hold MPs to account regardless of party. This is why. In 1998, my teenage sister was abducted and subjected to hours of rapes and sodomy, he left her for dead. What was done to her changed the course of her life. She lives with severe mental illness and addiction, which are recognised consequences of prolonged childhood sexual trauma. She has received no meaningful, consistent support since the offence occurred. Because of that trauma, her children were removed from her care. I know this intimately, because I fostered two of them. They are my niece and nephews. Our family has lived with the impact of this crime for more than 27 years. The man responsible was convicted of multiple offences involving underage girls. At the time of sentencing, in open court, he shouted that he would come back and sexually assault every woman and child in our family. That threat was made while judgment was being passed. He was given a lengthy prison sentence. Since then, I have been repeatedly drawn back into the justice system through parole reviews. During the pandemic, Humberside Police’s serious crime unit contacted me to inform me he was again being considered for release. I provided a victim impact statement on my sister’s behalf, because she is not well enough to do so herself. What is less often understood is that the harm did not end with my sister. Because of the threats made in court, and further conduct over time, I required legal protection. A non-molestation order and an exclusion zone were put in place to protect me, my children, and other women in our family. I am now also formally recognised as a victim of his actions. After serving over two decades in custody, he was released and then recalled to prison within months for breaching his licence conditions. He is currently back in custody. I am never told the full details. I am simply summoned again, year after year, to repeat the same process. This is not a political position I have adopted. This is not something I have joined late. This is my family’s lived reality. This is why I speak. This is why I refuse silence. This is why safeguarding and accountability matter to me. When I talk about child sexual exploitation, I am not speculating. I am describing a life my family has lived for more than two decades. My position is clear. Life should mean life, I will continue to fight for life without parole for child rapists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_310b0a25</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: An inside look at what's happening at Starbase</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/16edfe4f</link>
      <description>An inside look at what's happening at Starbase</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_16edfe4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The grokipedia team is growing here - if you’re excited about truth, come join us</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/359797da</link>
      <description>The grokipedia team is growing here - if you’re excited about truth, come join us</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_359797da</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Try Grok</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/56b17f40</link>
      <description>Try Grok</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_56b17f40</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I mean, the "mom" - who had apparently lost custody of 2/3 of her kids due to neglect or abuse - got...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c6c15321</link>
      <description>I mean, the "mom" - who had apparently lost custody of 2/3 of her kids due to neglect or abuse - got shot because she was illegally impeding an active arrest, tried to flee the scene, and drove her SUV at a federal agent as part of that. The agent briefly went to the hospital with internal bleeding. The "nurse" got shot because he was "directing traffic" around an active ICE situation, moved over to illegally interfere with it, and grabbed and scuffled with agents - all while armed and with two spare magazines on him. Both of these people were apparently part of a large, illicit underground network that is apparently doing things like illegally recording license plates and addresses and connected with ICE - and flat out dispatching raiders to screw with government arrests. You can view these two shoots as good or not, but the state is not killing people for being "too good, too noble." These were VERY predictable, avoidable situations of violence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c6c15321</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/2c72b7759…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1d09e887</link>
      <description>Wowxcancel.com/i/grok/share/2c72b7759…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1d09e887</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 36,500 killed in two days? They're massacring their own civilians. Where are the protesters in the w...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f2ad228e</link>
      <description>36,500 killed in two days? They're massacring their own civilians. Where are the protesters in the west -- the university encampments, the street protests, the UN, Hollywood?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f2ad228e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Davos discussion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea7c03ad</link>
      <description>Davos discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea7c03ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
