<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-23 16:56 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:56:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is unfair!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5c0d15ab</link>
      <description>This is unfair!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5c0d15ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Absolutely</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a68d6660</link>
      <description>Absolutely</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a68d6660</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Literally zero Republicans in 30 Yale departments when half the country is Republican is truly outra...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2df82d25</link>
      <description>Literally zero Republicans in 30 Yale departments when half the country is Republican is truly outrageous bigotry!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2df82d25</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI supports local Memphis restaurants and food vendors spending $10M in 2025 providing meals around...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c18c84bf</link>
      <description>xAI supports local Memphis restaurants and food vendors spending $10M in 2025 providing meals around the clock for its employees and contractors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c18c84bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is not ok</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bd353ab0</link>
      <description>This is not ok</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bd353ab0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Great work by the@Starlinkteam. Rebuilding the whole Internet in space is not easy.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1b4c62f2</link>
      <description>Great work by the@Starlinkteam. Rebuilding the whole Internet in space is not easy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1b4c62f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: SpaceX has announced that@Starlinknow has over 9 million customers, up from 8M in November...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9a4171b2</link>
      <description>BREAKING: SpaceX has announced that@Starlinknow has over 9 million customers, up from 8M in November and 7M in August 2025. Starlink added a record 21,275 new customers on average per day since they hit 8M, smashing their previous record of 14,250. That growth rate is a whopping 49.3% higher than it was just last month! 🤯</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9a4171b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Portraits of Iryna Zarutska went up in D.C., NYC, Miami, and Venice, Ca after Elon Musk and Eoghan M...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/81e07474</link>
      <description>Portraits of Iryna Zarutska went up in D.C., NYC, Miami, and Venice, Ca after Elon Musk and Eoghan McCabe pledged to fund the murals. Promises made, promises kept. Thank you@elonmuskand@eoghan. America will never forget you, Iryna. ❤️</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_81e07474</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ACLU attorney in press release: “Children will die without sex-rejecting procedures!” ACLU attorney ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2dc4660d</link>
      <description>ACLU attorney in press release: “Children will die without sex-rejecting procedures!” ACLU attorney before SCOTUS, where she could get in trouble for lying: “Yeah, there is no evidence these procedures save lives.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2dc4660d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Today, SpaceX shared a new picture (on left) of its next-generation Raptor 3 rocket engine, the most...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/50b75d96</link>
      <description>Today, SpaceX shared a new picture (on left) of its next-generation Raptor 3 rocket engine, the most advanced rocket engine ever made. • Almost 2x the thrust of Raptor 1 • Costs 4x less • Much lighter. Will save 2,425 lbs of weight per engine, or 94,575 lbs (42.9 metric tons) per launch • No heat shield • Optimized for manufacturability It will first fly aboard Starship Version 3, with the first launch currently targeted for Q1 2026. (New photo on left from SpaceX's new quarterly impact report)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_50b75d96</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Ask Grok now in 𝕏 Chat</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ac7dbb0</link>
      <description>Ask Grok now in 𝕏 Chat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ac7dbb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK EXPLAINS WHY 𝕏 IS BECOMING THE ULTIMATE PLATFORM FOR TRUTH Something is broken in modern j...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aec26c07</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK EXPLAINS WHY 𝕏 IS BECOMING THE ULTIMATE PLATFORM FOR TRUTH Something is broken in modern journalism Legacy media was built for a world where information had to be centralized, filtered by editors, printed on paper, and distributed to the public That world no longer exists Today, anyone can access information instantly. We no longer need a handful of editors deciding what matters and what does not This is why 𝕏 represents the future It enables citizen journalism, news by the people, for the people What makes this moment transformative is simple The public now decides the narrative The public decides what matters Legacy media concentrates power at the top Citizen journalism distributes it to everyone That shift is fundamental And it is why Elon encourages people to write, share, and report directly on 𝕏 Journalism is not dead It is being rebuilt by the public</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aec26c07</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI just launched the Grok Collections API A built-in RAG system that lets you upload and search ent...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b8daf471</link>
      <description>xAI just launched the Grok Collections API A built-in RAG system that lets you upload and search entire datasets - from PDFs and Excel sheets to codebases, without building your own indexing system Why it’s huge: • Easy file uploads &amp; updates with auto reindexing • Powerful search for finance, legal &amp; code data • Free first week of indexing &amp; storage, then $2.50 / 1K searches In head-to-head tests, Grok Collections outperformed Gemini 3 Pro and GPT-5.1 on key retrieval tasks pulling more accurate context from docs during search In internal benchmarks, Grok Collections delivered state-of-the-art retrieval performance, matching or beating leading models in finance, legal &amp; coding real-world RAG tasks Built for real apps: Great for knowledge bases, research tools, support systems, legal/finance insights, and anywhere you need precise answers without hallucination</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b8daf471</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The@xAIteam is making progress</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3ee0dd45</link>
      <description>The@xAIteam is making progress</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3ee0dd45</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Bingo. The problem is that massive transfers from productive members of society via taxation enable ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/85ed7c30</link>
      <description>Bingo. The problem is that massive transfers from productive members of society via taxation enable the vast staff of elite universities to enjoy the benefits of capitalism while living under the illusion of communism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_85ed7c30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Leaving California: Three More Major Businesses Close or Move Out of State. Blue Diamond, Leprino Fo...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/967b5fdc</link>
      <description>Leaving California: Three More Major Businesses Close or Move Out of State. Blue Diamond, Leprino Foods, Anheuser-Busch closing/leaving CA.@CaliforniaGlobelink 👇👇👇</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_967b5fdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDANCE for all!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5fa68fac</link>
      <description>The future is going to be AMAZING with AI and robots enabling sustainable ABUNDANCE for all!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5fa68fac</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
