<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-17 15:11 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:11:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇳🇱 A Dutch court has sentenced a migrant named Arnold Oforiwaa to 5 years in prison for stabbing his...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/27d47adc</link>
      <description>🇳🇱 A Dutch court has sentenced a migrant named Arnold Oforiwaa to 5 years in prison for stabbing his girlfriend 258 times. The prosecutor only asked for 10 years in prison but the judge halved it to 5 years because Arnold was documented “to have very low IQ.” He murdered his ‘girlfriend’ — a young mother — because she focused too much on caring for her newborn and too little on him. He stabbed her 258 (!) times and filmed the mother as she lay bleeding to death. Afterwards he took selfies with the newborn in its mothers blood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_27d47adc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Incredible view of Earth from Starship.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/581b570d</link>
      <description>Incredible view of Earth from Starship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_581b570d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: @DataRepublicanis one of the bravest people I know. She was doxxed, has received death threats, and ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/320a564c</link>
      <description>@DataRepublicanis one of the bravest people I know. She was doxxed, has received death threats, and has faced bomb scares. Yet she pressed forward, documenting exactly how deep the abyss goes. Read this book to see what we saw inside the federal government—and to find the way to fix it. Edward Coristine, aka “Big Balls” November 30th, 2025</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_320a564c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: More and more young white men are looking at Britain, how the ENTIRE country operates, and thinking ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/904c7c8a</link>
      <description>More and more young white men are looking at Britain, how the ENTIRE country operates, and thinking - why does EVERYBODY ELSE seem to get a helping hand? What have we done wrong? The answer lads, is absolutely nothing. How many young white men have lost out on decent jobs exactly because they are male, and exactly because they are white? Tens and tens of thousands. Likely more. It is institutional and systemic bias against white British men. Anti-white racism is thriving in Britain. Poisonous DEI infects our institutions and corporations. Quotas steal professional opportunities away from bright young men who deserve it. The education system, stacked against you - the forgotten working class white lads who nobody even thinks about, nobody even talks about. Blocked from universities, taught to be ashamed of who you are. The rot MUST end. In the justice system? Who gets the raw end of the deal? Young white men. They tried to implement sentencing guidelines that directly target you, and put you in prison over somebody else for the exact same crime. It is ENDLESS. It seems everyone has a ‘protected characteristic’ apart from you. Under a Restore Britain Government, it will all end. The woke bullshit will end, I promise you that. You now have a political party that will fight for you. We would tear away all of the vile legislation that has made Britain such a hostile and unwelcoming place to its own young men. Our message is clear. There is NOTHING wrong with being white, and there is NOTHING wrong with being male. You’re told that you’re racist for loving your country, chauvinistic for enjoying a few beers at the football, bigoted for having a joke with your mates. It must all end. We must restore confidence to an entire generation of young white men who have been entirely forgotten and let down by the rotten political establishment. My advice is this. Keep working hard, learn a skill, be respectful, have fun, and despite everything - enjoy yourselves. Keep going. It will get better. You now have a political party that properly represents you. Restore Britain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_904c7c8a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: When Elon Musk brought his kids along to his meeting with Prime Minister Modi in 2015.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b7bd4ab9</link>
      <description>When Elon Musk brought his kids along to his meeting with Prime Minister Modi in 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b7bd4ab9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Flashback to July 2022: Elon Musk showing Everyday Astronaut the massive leap from messy Raptor 1 (‘...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f362f350</link>
      <description>Flashback to July 2022: Elon Musk showing Everyday Astronaut the massive leap from messy Raptor 1 (‘Christmas tree’ vibes 😂) to clean Raptor 2 – 230 tons thrust at 300 bar, tons of parts deleted! Fast-forward to 2026: We’re already on Raptor 3 – 280+ tons thrust, even simpler design, no external pipes, in production (100+ built!), testing like crazy, set for Starship V3 flights soon. Insane progress in ~3.5 years!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f362f350</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: THE REID HOFFMAN FILES I OCR'd all 1.4 million documents from the DOJ's Epstein FOIA release. Then I...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/893f7036</link>
      <description>THE REID HOFFMAN FILES I OCR'd all 1.4 million documents from the DOJ's Epstein FOIA release. Then I tested every public claim Reid Hoffman ever made about Jeffrey Epstein. 13 claims. 0 true. This is the very first email. August 2013. [EFTA01960550] Link:justice.gov/epstein/files/Da…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_893f7036</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨ASMONGOLD INVITES RUPERT LOWE ONTO CHANNEL This would be amazing Let's make it happen!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/01eaeaee</link>
      <description>🚨ASMONGOLD INVITES RUPERT LOWE ONTO CHANNEL This would be amazing Let's make it happen!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_01eaeaee</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: the most powerful country in history thousands of nuclear warheads trillions and trillions of dollar...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/25973638</link>
      <description>the most powerful country in history thousands of nuclear warheads trillions and trillions of dollars and an electoral system so insecure that dogs can register to vote if we don’t fix this, our inevitable decline is self imposed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_25973638</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The Spanish police have just announced that the real figure of migrants being “normalized” under Ped...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/17b2e4ea</link>
      <description>The Spanish police have just announced that the real figure of migrants being “normalized” under Pedro Sanchez’s new laws is actually 1.35 MILLION. The government originally lied and said it was 500,000. The later revised it to about 800,000. The police have said the real number is 1.35 MILLION. Please keep in mind this is BEFORE family reunifications are factored into the equation. I think it’s time to reconsider Spain’s ability to participate in Schengen and in the US Visa Waiver Program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_17b2e4ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: One year ago (Feb 7, 2025), NASA’s Curiosity rover stood on Mount Sharp and captured a panoramic vie...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1302617e</link>
      <description>One year ago (Feb 7, 2025), NASA’s Curiosity rover stood on Mount Sharp and captured a panoramic view looking down into Gale Crater. Yes, this is Mars, about 140 million miles away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1302617e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Tesla Model Y runs California. Year 4. Best-selling. Again. The future's parked in every driveway. S...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b67b462e</link>
      <description>Tesla Model Y runs California. Year 4. Best-selling. Again. The future's parked in every driveway. Silence sells.@Tesla</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b67b462e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This investigation in California found dead voters, a dog registered to vote and voters with inaccur...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/686a91c1</link>
      <description>This investigation in California found dead voters, a dog registered to vote and voters with inaccurate ages up to 125 years old. Thats exactly why Voter ID is necessary in any serious country. Pass The SAVE America Act.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_686a91c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The fact that trans people over 30 basically don’t exist should tell you something about the mimetic...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/006bf920</link>
      <description>The fact that trans people over 30 basically don’t exist should tell you something about the mimetic nature of mental illness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_006bf920</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Everything I've said about transgenderism for the past 10 years has been absolutely correct and tota...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e69207a4</link>
      <description>Everything I've said about transgenderism for the past 10 years has been absolutely correct and totally vindicated. Now I'm telling you that the trans violence we've seen so far is nothing compared to what's coming if we don't treat trans ideology as a severe public safety hazard and crack down it immediately and aggressively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e69207a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The civilization that gave the world Beethoven, established the rule of law, built the Sistine Chape...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/61b2bedc</link>
      <description>The civilization that gave the world Beethoven, established the rule of law, built the Sistine Chapel, and circumnavigated the globe must cast off the shackles of shame and self-doubt. Europe must reverse its decline. Europe must survive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_61b2bedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Children are the future</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bc59b9aa</link>
      <description>Children are the future</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bc59b9aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI Memphis</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/528a563c</link>
      <description>xAI Memphis</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_528a563c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Cybercab, which has no pedals or steering wheel, starts production in April</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9425b973</link>
      <description>Cybercab, which has no pedals or steering wheel, starts production in April</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9425b973</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
