<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-31 08:56 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:56:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Somalia ranks 179th out of the 180 countries ranked on the Corruption Perceptions Index</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f7c009d7</link>
      <description>Somalia ranks 179th out of the 180 countries ranked on the Corruption Perceptions Index</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f7c009d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Even assuming there was no fraud, none of this makes sense. How is it that we have been funding bill...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/67c879a1</link>
      <description>Even assuming there was no fraud, none of this makes sense. How is it that we have been funding billions of dollars of daycare for Somali immigrants in Minnesota 81% of which (according to Gemini) are on welfare? In other words, if mom and dad don’t work, why the need for child care? Perhaps you could say the welfare statistics include some subsidies for working parents, but still in this case, the child care does not appear to be needed as the daycare centers are empty. Furthermore, why is Federal funded childcare provided to recent immigrants on welfare versus long-standing American working families who are not on welfare? How does this make sense?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_67c879a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I like how he just tries to slide in the phrase “White men commit the most crime” like it’s a given ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b87a52c1</link>
      <description>I like how he just tries to slide in the phrase “White men commit the most crime” like it’s a given Here’s the homicide data for the state of Minnesota, and the total crime data for Hennepin county Not only do white people not commit the most crime, they don’t even commit most of the crimeS You have 5x as many white people in Minnesota as black people. Somehow the 169K black people committed almost twice the total number of crimes that 857K white people did over the same time span I get that it’s tacky to bring up crime stats but this is utter horseshit, and an outright, bald-faced lie. I’m not going to just sit here and accept him saying this and not push back</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b87a52c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok just surpassed 79 million posts on 𝕏. Grok is turning into a daily companion for mill...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5739607a</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok just surpassed 79 million posts on 𝕏. Grok is turning into a daily companion for millions of people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5739607a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok takes the #1 spot on the OpenAI LLM Leaderboard for December. Ranked #1 for the month...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/eb60e306</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok takes the #1 spot on the OpenAI LLM Leaderboard for December. Ranked #1 for the month, this week, and today rankings. 🔥</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_eb60e306</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk discusses the pervasive issue of NGO money laundering on Fox News, advocating for accounta...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a00671b8</link>
      <description>Elon Musk discusses the pervasive issue of NGO money laundering on Fox News, advocating for accountability. "NGO and money laundering are almost synonymous."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a00671b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I went to 4 more Somali childcare locations today. Two told me they weren’t childcares despite recei...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c32ce4b0</link>
      <description>I went to 4 more Somali childcare locations today. Two told me they weren’t childcares despite receiving hundreds of thousands of tax payer dollars. One which claimed they weren’t a childcare received over $800,000 since 2023. It’s all on camera. It will be uncovered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c32ce4b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/92a5d75e</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_92a5d75e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEWS: Tesla has revealed that the Model Y was #1 best-selling car overall in the world in 2025 for t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/aa066be4</link>
      <description>NEWS: Tesla has revealed that the Model Y was #1 best-selling car overall in the world in 2025 for the third year in a row. World's best-selling car: • 2023: Tesla Model Y • 2024: Tesla Model Y • 2025: Tesla Model Y 🔥</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_aa066be4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Leading the world in scientific discovery, pursuing the space economy and making final preparations ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/37ac8e6a</link>
      <description>Leading the world in scientific discovery, pursuing the space economy and making final preparations for America's return to the moon... 2025 was a strong year for NASA and I am incredibly proud of the team, but this is just the beginning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_37ac8e6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is a must download. It’s the most resourceful tool on my phone. There isn’t a day that I don’t ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/80f1017c</link>
      <description>Grok is a must download. It’s the most resourceful tool on my phone. There isn’t a day that I don’t use it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_80f1017c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Only about 6 months ago, Giga Berlin produced the 8 millionth vehicle globally and now we hit the 9 ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6acdf7fa</link>
      <description>Only about 6 months ago, Giga Berlin produced the 8 millionth vehicle globally and now we hit the 9 million vehicles milestone! Insane accomplishment by our 4 factories around the globe! Cannot wait for the 10 millionth car to be produced!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6acdf7fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s this simple, folks: stop all illegal immigration. Deport all illegal aliens here now. Enact Vot...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/90699bb4</link>
      <description>It’s this simple, folks: stop all illegal immigration. Deport all illegal aliens here now. Enact Voter ID laws. That will solve every problem America has. We will reduce taxes, stop crime, fraud, Democrat DEI scams, inflation, homelessness, and the housing crisis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_90699bb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: This is the way</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a47fef99</link>
      <description>This is the way</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a47fef99</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Turning off payments and forcing verification before taxpayer money flows out the door is one of the...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d4b32be8</link>
      <description>Turning off payments and forcing verification before taxpayer money flows out the door is one of the most important steps we can take to end the fraud in Minnesota. But there will be many more to come. Great job to@HHS_Jimand@SecKennedy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d4b32be8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grandma, you rock</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1165d20b</link>
      <description>Grandma, you rock</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1165d20b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Once we restore honest elections in America—Every. Other. Problem. Is. Solved.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4834d229</link>
      <description>Once we restore honest elections in America—Every. Other. Problem. Is. Solved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4834d229</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: It’s not "white supremacy" to investigate fraud. This attack no longer works.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1dbd3543</link>
      <description>It’s not "white supremacy" to investigate fraud. This attack no longer works.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1dbd3543</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/723dfe9f</link>
      <description>xAI has bought a third building called MACROHARDRR. Will take@xAItraining compute to almost 2GW. Try@Grok. Download latest app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_723dfe9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
