<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-02 14:43 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:43:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Over the last week, SBA has reviewed thousands of potentially fraudulent pandemic-era PPP and EIDL l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e0850425</link>
      <description>Over the last week, SBA has reviewed thousands of potentially fraudulent pandemic-era PPP and EIDL loans approved in Minnesota. Today, our agency took action to suspend 6,900 Minnesota borrowers amid suspected fraudulent activity. In total, these borrowers were approved for 7,900 PPP and EIDL loans worth approximately $400M. These individuals will be banned from all SBA loan programs, including disaster loans, going forward. We will also refer every case, where appropriate, to federal law enforcement for prosecution and repayment. After years, the American people will finally begin to see the criminals who stole from law-abiding taxpayers held accountable - and this is just the first state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e0850425</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Clinton committed a heinous crime against the American people</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/341ce8fb</link>
      <description>Clinton committed a heinous crime against the American people</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_341ce8fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: A state that never allowed slavery wants to make residents who never owned slaves pay reparations to...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/84c77256</link>
      <description>A state that never allowed slavery wants to make residents who never owned slaves pay reparations to people who never were slaves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_84c77256</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Double-standard</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/33127415</link>
      <description>Double-standard</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_33127415</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is awesome</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/861ac4a2</link>
      <description>Grok is awesome</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_861ac4a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Our last chance to stop the ongoing invasion</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c130904a</link>
      <description>Our last chance to stop the ongoing invasion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c130904a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 CATHERINE HERRIDGE: CBS WALKED AWAY FROM ELON BECAUSE THEY COULDN’T CONTROL HIM Catherine reveale...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1a62b61a</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 CATHERINE HERRIDGE: CBS WALKED AWAY FROM ELON BECAUSE THEY COULDN’T CONTROL HIM Catherine revealed CBS passed on what could have been one of the biggest interviews in modern media, not because Elon refused, but because the network did. She said discussions were underway after her work connected to the Twitter Files, and an opportunity emerged to interview Elon live on his own platform. That’s when everything stalled. “I went to the CBS executives and I said, this is the opportunity that we have. He’s saying, I want to do it live and on my platform. He’s one of the most influential human beings on the planet. And the reaction from the executives was, well, we can’t do it live. And I was like, what do you mean we can’t do it live? They said, we don’t know what he’s going to say. And I’m thinking, isn’t that the point of journalism? They said it has to be taped. We have to be able to edit it. It has to be on our platform. We have to control the platform. Everything just got shut down. It was one of the biggest interviews you could ever have. I felt ashamed. I never went back to Elon to say they want to do it, but only if they can control it. I couldn’t do that to someone whose DNA is free speech.” Source:@C__Herridge</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1a62b61a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨🇺🇸 DOGE ACCOUNT CONNECTS THE DOTS: FROM BLACK HAWK DOWN TO MINNESOTA FRAUD, 30 YEARS IN THE MAKING ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/81b6347a</link>
      <description>🚨🇺🇸 DOGE ACCOUNT CONNECTS THE DOTS: FROM BLACK HAWK DOWN TO MINNESOTA FRAUD, 30 YEARS IN THE MAKING The official DOGE State account just dropped a brutal history lesson. October 3, 1993. Mogadishu, Somalia. US elite forces, Delta operators and Rangers, drop in for what was supposed to be a 30-minute raid to capture lieutenants of warlord Mohamed Farrah Aidid, who was hijacking UN food aid. Things went sideways fast. Somali militias with RPGs blasted two Black Hawk helicopters out of the sky. A quick op turned into an 18-hour urban nightmare. Block-by-block fighting against thousands. 18 US troops killed. 73 wounded. Somali losses in the hundreds. The worst part: mobs dragged American bodies through the streets, mutilating and parading them on television. Images that horrified the world and crushed US public support overnight. Clinton pulled forces out by 1994. Then came resettlement. Tens of thousands of Somalis brought to the US throughout the '90s. Major communities built in Minnesota and Ohio. Fast forward 30 years. Those same communities are now ground zero for the largest fraud scandal in American history. $9 billion allegedly siphoned from Minnesota alone. Daycare schemes. Nutrition program fraud. Money sent to Kenya and allegedly to Al-Shabaab. DOGE's point: These policies have consequences that span decades. From Black Hawk Down to the Quality Learing Center. The thread is longer than most realize. Source: HistoryState, Slate, PBS Video:@WarMonitorClips</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_81b6347a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨🇺🇸 FRAUD INVESTIGATION SPREADS TO WASHINGTON STATE: DAYCARE WITH 7 KIDS RECEIVED $81,000 IN ONE MON...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/34227895</link>
      <description>🚨🇺🇸 FRAUD INVESTIGATION SPREADS TO WASHINGTON STATE: DAYCARE WITH 7 KIDS RECEIVED $81,000 IN ONE MONTH Minnesota. Ohio. Now Washington. Citizen journalist Cam Higby uncovered what appears to be the same playbook operating in Washington State. Amira Child Care LLC, owned by Ahmed Amira and listed as Somali-speaking, donated $1,000 cash in 2021 to Shukri Olow, a Somali-born candidate for King County Council and Washington State House. That donation triggered a Public Disclosure Commission investigation. PDC Case #96266 alleged Olow's campaign accepted contributions exceeding statutory limits. The case was closed with a "reminder" after Olow refunded the over-limit portions. The PDC noted she was a "first-time candidate." The timing and amount, $1,000 in 2021, align with the reported violations. Now follow the money: 2021-2023: Ahmed Amira Abdi received $383,000 in grants from the Department of Children, Youth and Families. 2023-2025: Amira Child Care LLC received $363,000. July-November 2025 alone: $355,000. December not yet reported. The math doesn't add up. Licensed capacity: 12 children. Currently enrolled: 7 children. September 2025 payment: $81,263. That's $11,600 per child for one month. Higby's conclusion: "What it appears to be is a child care organization owned by a Somali person donating to Somali political candidates with taxpayer dollars." Three states. Same pattern. Massive subsidies. How deep does this go? Source:@camhigby/ Washington PDC Case #96266</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_34227895</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Yes, it is the biggest crime in American history</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8c34748e</link>
      <description>Yes, it is the biggest crime in American history</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8c34748e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Proud of the tremendous work by the@Starlinkteam in 2025! Read the progress report herestarlink.com/...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c1f18f7d</link>
      <description>Proud of the tremendous work by the@Starlinkteam in 2025! Read the progress report herestarlink.com/progress</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c1f18f7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia is growing rapidly. Will far exceed Wikipedia this year.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7317e749</link>
      <description>Grokipedia is growing rapidly. Will far exceed Wikipedia this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7317e749</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🧠 Why Neuralink is a game-changer for people with disabilities: For millions living with paralysis, ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7c39f0b2</link>
      <description>🧠 Why Neuralink is a game-changer for people with disabilities: For millions living with paralysis, ALS, or severe motor/speech impairment, simple things like using a computer, communicating, or creating are impossible without constant help. Neuralink’s brain implant changes that—letting users control devices purely with thoughts. Noland, paralyzed below the shoulders from a diving accident, used to rely on a painful mouth stick and family caregivers. Now he independently browses, plays games like Civilization, and studies math, philosophy, &amp; languages daily—reclaiming his autonomy and planning to return to school. Alex, quadriplegic after a car crash, lost his passion for designing auto parts. With Neuralink, he’s back to 3D CAD modeling, graphics, and even coding—pushing creative boundaries again. Brad, in late-stage ALS and unable to speak/move, was trapped indoors by unreliable eye-tracking tech. Now he communicates outdoors, attends his kid’s soccer games, and dreams of travel. This isn’t sci-fi. Real patients are already living more independent, connected lives. Future steps: robotic arms, speech restoration, even vision. Neuralink restores dignity, freedom, and hope. It’s one of the most important advancements for the disabled today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7c39f0b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I can't imagine any other president fixing the massive fraud problem. First, he had to dismantle the...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9daef51f</link>
      <description>I can't imagine any other president fixing the massive fraud problem. First, he had to dismantle the DEI mind virus. Second, he had to not be in on the scams, directly or indirectly. Third, you need balls of steel to block these good-sounding-but-corrupt schemes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9daef51f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Then it is war</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/dabf3dd9</link>
      <description>Then it is war</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_dabf3dd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
