<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-02-19 10:36 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:36:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: Grok website visits just surpassed 800 million worldwide, up around 16% in the latest@Simi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/fe507b5b</link>
      <description>BREAKING: Grok website visits just surpassed 800 million worldwide, up around 16% in the latest@Similarwebdata. The web version is taking off too, with Grok website now ranking among the top 70 most visited sites globally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_fe507b5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: And there will be noticeable improvements every week</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5de5cd05</link>
      <description>And there will be noticeable improvements every week</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5de5cd05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: In case you missed it the first time around</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4d94c729</link>
      <description>In case you missed it the first time around</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4d94c729</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The only AI to unequivocally say that President Trump is NOT a racist is@grok. 77 million Americans ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/463259f6</link>
      <description>The only AI to unequivocally say that President Trump is NOT a racist is@grok. 77 million Americans voted for President Trump — yet three other products parrot Democrat and Legacy media points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_463259f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ChatGPT is racist</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ea1fc7dc</link>
      <description>ChatGPT is racist</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ea1fc7dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok is fair to all</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/bd868f3d</link>
      <description>Grok is fair to all</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_bd868f3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The world’s first video game, played on its original 1957 hardware. In October 1958, physicist Willi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/0f2d6a0b</link>
      <description>The world’s first video game, played on its original 1957 hardware. In October 1958, physicist William Higinbotham developed what is widely recognized as the first video game, Tennis for Two, to entertain visitors at a public exhibition at Brookhaven National Laboratory. Unlike later digital consoles, the game ran on a Donner Model 30 analog computer and displayed graphics on a five-inch oscilloscope. Players controlled the action with custom aluminum controllers featuring a knob to set the ball’s angle and a button to hit it over a simulated net. While earlier electronic creations like the 1947 Cathode-Ray Tube Amusement Device or 1950’s Bertie the Brain existed, Tennis for Two is notable as the first game designed purely for entertainment, rather than research or technical demonstration. Although the original hardware was dismantled in 1959, and no intact version survives, modern replicas have been built to celebrate this groundbreaking moment in gaming history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_0f2d6a0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 💯 would have happened 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e4adccf7</link>
      <description>💯 would have happened 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e4adccf7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 60 MINUTES CALLED TESLA A “SMALL STARTUP” - AND NO ONE HAD A CLUE WHAT WAS COMING The year is 2008...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/98d1300e</link>
      <description>🚨 60 MINUTES CALLED TESLA A “SMALL STARTUP” - AND NO ONE HAD A CLUE WHAT WAS COMING The year is 2008. 60 Minutes introduces Elon Musk as the chairman of a small Northern California startup called Tesla, with "no experience at all in the car business." He shows her the original Tesla Roadster. They run through the details like it’s nothing: • 0–60 in 4 seconds • 200+ miles on a charge • 6,000 laptop batteries • No gas. No oil. • Plugged into a normal wall outlet • Price: $109,000 She emphasizes how expensive the car is, noting that people like George Clooney and Arnold Schwarzenegger could afford those prices. That Roadster wasn’t small. It was the first move. The world had no idea. What stands out to you watching this 18 years later?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_98d1300e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: OMG. Alexander Lamar Banks Jr. was arrested in Michigan after he reportedly ran down White family wi...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/58afd61f</link>
      <description>OMG. Alexander Lamar Banks Jr. was arrested in Michigan after he reportedly ran down White family with his car, K*LLING the couple's 3-year-old daughter. Court documents of the incident describe how Banks then got out of the car with a shotgun and shot the parents. He also brutally assaulted a 72-year-old woman who showed up at the scene. The mother and father are currently in the hospital in stable condition. The 72-year-old woman is currently in critical condition. Why isn't this national news???</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_58afd61f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 💯 that’s what it means 😂</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/789b9764</link>
      <description>💯 that’s what it means 😂</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_789b9764</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Physics is beautiful - woke up to find my truck covered in fern frost. A rare phenomenon that occurs...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/ebb73188</link>
      <description>Physics is beautiful - woke up to find my truck covered in fern frost. A rare phenomenon that occurs in just the right conditions. Surface temp drops below the freezing point of nearby humid air, ice crystals form propagating out from nucleation sites making these cool patterns</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_ebb73188</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok 4.20 beta example Years ago, I made a crypto wallet but missed writing a few seed phrase words....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/629fb19d</link>
      <description>Grok 4.20 beta example Years ago, I made a crypto wallet but missed writing a few seed phrase words. This account has a measly 40$ but I keep asking AI to try opening it for fun Grok 4.1 spent 6 days of trying and failed Grok 4.20 cracked it in 492 seconds, correctly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_629fb19d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Elon Musk showing Tesla Roadster to Arnold Schwarzenegger in 2008.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cdcfb3eb</link>
      <description>Elon Musk showing Tesla Roadster to Arnold Schwarzenegger in 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cdcfb3eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Just asked the 16 Grok 4.20 Heavy agents to build me a GLSL shader, no libraries. Alien bioluminesce...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a7838746</link>
      <description>Just asked the 16 Grok 4.20 Heavy agents to build me a GLSL shader, no libraries. Alien bioluminescent ocean floor. Hydrothermal vents, caustic light, rising particles, layered noise terrain. Mouse = underwater flashlight. 60fps. Collapsible control panel with uniforms. It cooked. &gt;&gt;&gt; grok 4.20 heavy prompt Build a single HTML page with a full-screen GLSL fragment shader rendered via WebGL. No libraries raw WebGL setup with a full-screen quad. The shader should render an alien bioluminescent ocean floor imagine deep sea hydrothermal vents with pulsing organic light. Use layered simplex/value noise for undulating terrain, glowing particles rising like volcanic embers, caustic light patterns rippling across the surface, and color palettes shifting between deep indigo, electric cyan, magenta, and molten gold. The mouse position should act as an underwater flashlight illuminating nearby terrain and revealing hidden details. Include a subtle camera drift so it feels like you're slowly gliding over the seabed. Everything should be smooth at 60fps. Add a small collapsible control panel in the corner with sliders for: glow intensity, drift speed, color temperature, and particle density these should feed into the shader as uniforms. The page background should be black with no scrollbars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a7838746</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 100 men? Even in high school, it was hard getting 10 guys together if we had to fight another squad....</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/de15f429</link>
      <description>100 men? Even in high school, it was hard getting 10 guys together if we had to fight another squad. It was hard getting ten guys together for a BASEBALL GAME. Do you know ONE man you could invite over for some rape or domestic violence?! What type a' animals are we dealing with here?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_de15f429</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4a98afd8</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4a98afd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grokipedia.com</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7e9fcc06</link>
      <description>Grokipedia.com</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7e9fcc06</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
