<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2025-12-30 17:42 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:42:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Create videos in the 5 most common aspect ratios</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a61798bf</link>
      <description>Create videos in the 5 most common aspect ratios</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a61798bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Exactly</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/92a5d75e</link>
      <description>Exactly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_92a5d75e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🚨 BREAKING: In a JAW-DROPPING revelation, HUD Sec. Scott Turner just found over $5 BILLION in potent...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7146ac7c</link>
      <description>🚨 BREAKING: In a JAW-DROPPING revelation, HUD Sec. Scott Turner just found over $5 BILLION in potential FRAUDULENT payments for thousands of non-citizens and deceased people Up to 30,000 THOUSAND of them. A "large concentration" of these rental assistance payments went to BLUE jurisdictions: New York, California and DC, per the New York Post CANCEL AND CLAW BACK ALL OF IT! “A massive abuse of taxpayer dollars not only occurred under President Biden’s watch, but was effectively incentivized by his administration’s failure to implement strong financial controls resulting in billions worth of potential improper payments." Here's Scott Turner a few weeks ago confirming a MASSIVE betrayal under Biden: Illegals were getting taxpayer-backed MORTGAGES over US citizens. All of it needs to be canceled and people need to go to jail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7146ac7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK “The single biggest thing Democrats are worried about is turning off fraudulent payments t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/2c25ec83</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK “The single biggest thing Democrats are worried about is turning off fraudulent payments to illegals. By using entitlements fraud, the Democrats have been able to attract and retain vast numbers of illegal immigrants, and buy voters.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_2c25ec83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: 🇺🇸 ELON: GOVERNMENT WAS WASTING TAXPAYER MONEY ON "TRANSGENDER ANIMAL SURGERIES" Elon cited official...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/c73bd29d</link>
      <description>🇺🇸 ELON: GOVERNMENT WAS WASTING TAXPAYER MONEY ON "TRANSGENDER ANIMAL SURGERIES" Elon cited official government audits documenting massive federal waste while running DOGE, calling out absurd expenditures including taxpayer-funded transgender procedures for animals: "If you look at the Inspector General reports and the Government Accountability Office, there have been many audits that pointed out a tremendous amount of waste and fraud in the government. There was a report issued by the GAO last year under the Biden administration. We're trying to get that number down to a much smaller figure, save money for the American taxpayer, stop money being spent on things that very few taxpayers would agree make sense. Transgender animal surgeries. Why are American tax dollars being spent on this?" Source:@elonmusk/ Fox</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_c73bd29d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: BREAKING: I’m calling for the denaturalization and deportation of every Somali engaged in fraud in M...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3a237005</link>
      <description>BREAKING: I’m calling for the denaturalization and deportation of every Somali engaged in fraud in Minnesota. Read my full statement below: “I have three words regarding Somalis who have committed fraud against American taxpayers: Send them home. If they’re here illegally, deport them immediately; if they’re naturalized citizens, revoke their citizenship and deport them quickly thereafter. If we need to change the law to do that, I will. Our nation will not tolerate those who take advantage of our charity and refuse to assimilate into our culture. Additionally, if any naturalized Somalis had undisclosed ties to terrorist organizations like Al-Shabaab, I want to see their citizenship revoked and their asses sent back immediately. Same goes for anyone who is found to have committed marriage fraud during the immigration process.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3a237005</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Very big file</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/692a3689</link>
      <description>Very big file</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_692a3689</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: The wildest thing about the Somali daycare scandal is that apparently the government’s goal was to s...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/cd6c7798</link>
      <description>The wildest thing about the Somali daycare scandal is that apparently the government’s goal was to subsidize daycares for random immigrants while tax paying American parents have been complaining for years they can barely afford childcare with two incomes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_cd6c7798</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: xcancel.com/i/grok/share/bXqu2uyL0…</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/9d2888c9</link>
      <description>xcancel.com/i/grok/share/bXqu2uyL0…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_9d2888c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Traitor Tim Walz</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4406c0ad</link>
      <description>Traitor Tim Walz</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4406c0ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Today's cover: A bombshell video puts Tim Walz under fire over the alleged Somali daycare scheme in ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/5fb5ed95</link>
      <description>Today's cover: A bombshell video puts Tim Walz under fire over the alleged Somali daycare scheme in Minnesota.trib.al/Aci1uFn</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_5fb5ed95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: MORE IN MINNEAPOLIS. Our investigative agents are conducting a massive operation to identify, arrest...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e8b94347</link>
      <description>MORE IN MINNEAPOLIS. Our investigative agents are conducting a massive operation to identify, arrest, and remove criminals who are defrauding the American people. We will root out this rampant fraud plaguing Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e8b94347</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie availab...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/d8e32a22</link>
      <description>My sister,@ToscaMusk, is posting 10 minute teasers of@PassionFlixmovies, with the full movie available to subscribers. I recommend taking this approach for text/image/video content on 𝕏.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_d8e32a22</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
