<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter - @elonmusk</title>
    <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk</link>
    <description>自动生成的Twitter RSS - 最后更新: 2026-01-22 01:12 UTC | 来源实例: https://xcancel.com</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Simple Twitter RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:12:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Requiring citizenship to vote isn’t controversial- it’s common sense. Senate Republicans need to pas...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f2b86d7d</link>
      <description>Requiring citizenship to vote isn’t controversial- it’s common sense. Senate Republicans need to pass the SAVE Act now!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f2b86d7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON: TRUTH AND CURIOSITY KEEP AI SANE “Truth will prevent AI from going insane. Curiosity will fost...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/6e10af10</link>
      <description>ELON: TRUTH AND CURIOSITY KEEP AI SANE “Truth will prevent AI from going insane. Curiosity will foster any form of sentience. We’re more interesting than a bunch of rocks. If it’s curious, it will foster humanity. If it has a sense of beauty, it will be a great future. That applies to AI just as it applies to biological life.” Source:@ianmiles</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_6e10af10</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Minnesotas Department of Human Services has given over $724,000,000 to an NGO(s) who’s name has been...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/4697206c</link>
      <description>Minnesotas Department of Human Services has given over $724,000,000 to an NGO(s) who’s name has been protected as “Masked to protect Not Public Data” This is suspicious because other NGOs have their name but this certain NGO has been protected. Expose all the fraud</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_4697206c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: NEW: Shocking details emerge in this triple homicide out of Florida Turns out Ahmad Jihad Bojeh shot...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b2d1f7fd</link>
      <description>NEW: Shocking details emerge in this triple homicide out of Florida Turns out Ahmad Jihad Bojeh shot up a Wawa in 2021 where one victim was shot several times and nearly died. A judge let him back out into the community on an insanity plea. The judge has the blood of three innocent people on his hands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b2d1f7fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Finding someone “not guilty by reason of insanity” and then releasing them on to the street to murde...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/e04d1aaf</link>
      <description>Finding someone “not guilty by reason of insanity” and then releasing them on to the street to murder innocent people is utterly insane</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_e04d1aaf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: AI is a supersonic tsunami</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/b4d01103</link>
      <description>AI is a supersonic tsunami</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_b4d01103</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON: AI PROGRESS IS BLOWING MY MIND MULTIPLE TIMES A WEEK “We're in the singularity. We're at the t...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/013b097e</link>
      <description>ELON: AI PROGRESS IS BLOWING MY MIND MULTIPLE TIMES A WEEK “We're in the singularity. We're at the top of the rollercoaster, and you're about to go down. I don't just have courtside seats: I'm on the court. And it blows my mind, and it still blows my mind, sometimes multiple times a week. I'm like, wow and then two days later, more wow! I think we'll hit AGI next year in 2026.” Source:@elonmuskin Moonshot – Discussion with@PeterDiamandisand@DavidBlundin, January 2026</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_013b097e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: QT Green Eyes</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/42eb1bcd</link>
      <description>QT Green Eyes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_42eb1bcd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: “We were told to label newly arrived ILLEGALS as ‘PERMANENTLY disabled’ — even for headaches or back...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/985e7d6b</link>
      <description>“We were told to label newly arrived ILLEGALS as ‘PERMANENTLY disabled’ — even for headaches or back pain — so they’d get Social Security for LIFE.” “Once they’re classified, that’s it — they’re set FOREVER. That’s exactly what they wanted us to do.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_985e7d6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON: THE ECONOMY IS NOT A MAGIC CORNUCOPIA “Some people have this absurd view that the economy is l...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8827769c</link>
      <description>ELON: THE ECONOMY IS NOT A MAGIC CORNUCOPIA “Some people have this absurd view that the economy is like some magic horn of plenty. Like it just makes stuff. Goods and services just come from this magic corner of plenty. And if somebody has more stuff than somebody else, it’s because they took more from this magic corner of plenty.” Source:@joerogan</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8827769c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: ELON MUSK: WE ARE REALLY TRYING TO BRING THE WORLD TOGETHER INTO A COLLECTIVE CONSCIOUSNESS 𝕏 is kin...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/7bcb4fe0</link>
      <description>ELON MUSK: WE ARE REALLY TRYING TO BRING THE WORLD TOGETHER INTO A COLLECTIVE CONSCIOUSNESS 𝕏 is kind of a global town square where people can say what they want to say with words, pictures, video Where there's a secure messaging system we've recently added the ability to do audio and video calls So really trying to bring the world together into a collective consciousness And that's different from just saying, 'What is the most dopamine-generating video stream that one could make?' Which I think can be a little bit of brain rot If you're just watching videos that cause dopamine hits one after another but lack substance, then I think that's not a great way to spend time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_7bcb4fe0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Jordan Peterson: "Second guessing Elon Musk is a fools game"</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/23fb00a0</link>
      <description>Jordan Peterson: "Second guessing Elon Musk is a fools game"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_23fb00a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: "If in 10 years, all American troops stationed in Europe have not been returned to the US, then this...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/addbee98</link>
      <description>"If in 10 years, all American troops stationed in Europe have not been returned to the US, then this whole project [NATO] will have failed… We must get these people to stand on their own feet militarily." - Dwight D. Eisenhower (1951) First Supreme Allied Commander of NATO</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_addbee98</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: I was interviewed by BBC along w/@ChiOnwurahabout@Keir_StarmerCOS Morgan McSweeney, who started Cent...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/459e08b0</link>
      <description>I was interviewed by BBC along w/@ChiOnwurahabout@Keir_StarmerCOS Morgan McSweeney, who started Center for Countering Digital Hate (CCDH). Onwurah lied to listeners claiming "Conservatives" passed Online Safety Act, no Morgan McSweeney's CCDH. Yes, but the Conservative was Damien Collins, who was on the board of CCDH. Does Onwurah not know what's going on inside her own government?@EthanCroft98@paddymacc1@AvaSantina@WorldByWolf@jodymcintyre_@kennardmatt@Ian_Fraser@NJ_Timothy@SteveNickSmith@CharlotteCGill@JuliaHB1</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_459e08b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Report: Parents who raised $170,000 by claiming ICE gassed their kids on the way home from a basketb...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1687bfd3</link>
      <description>Report: Parents who raised $170,000 by claiming ICE gassed their kids on the way home from a basketball game lied about the whole thingnotthebee.com/article/report…</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_1687bfd3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Grok Imagine now does 10 second videos with better video and much better audio</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/a1c74574</link>
      <description>Grok Imagine now does 10 second videos with better video and much better audio</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_a1c74574</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Is requiring photo ID to vote a reasonable measure to protect the integrity of elections? YES - All ...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/8ece1a22</link>
      <description>Is requiring photo ID to vote a reasonable measure to protect the integrity of elections? YES - All Voters: 73% Men: 69% Women: 76% 18-29: 70% 30-39: 70% 40-49: 80% 50-64: 77% 65+: 67% White: 73% Black: 70% Hispanic: 69% Other: 83% DEM: 64% IND: 69% GOP: 86%</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_8ece1a22</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Solar power is a really big deal.</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/f59e9d8d</link>
      <description>Solar power is a really big deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_f59e9d8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@elonmusk: Insurance is half price when Tesla self-driving is activated, because it increases safety so much</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/3c80061d</link>
      <description>Insurance is half price when Tesla self-driving is activated, because it increases safety so much</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">twitter_elonmusk_3c80061d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
